<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<xmloutfile>
<header>
<TYPE>XLFT</TYPE>
<DN>C04460</DN>
<KW>WRITE_LS_DOC</KW>
<FLG>API_MY_ALLPUB_Sandbox.fld,04/04/2018,30/09/2018</FLG>
<MNY>,0</MNY>
<ROWNB>91</ROWNB>
<COLNB>14</COLNB>
<MASK>12</MASK>
<MDL>WRITE_LS_DOC</MDL>
<LANG>CODE_GB</LANG>
<CUTVALUE>0</CUTVALUE>
<RIGHTSERIESNB>0</RIGHTSERIESNB></header>
<table>
<row>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Company Name</column>
<column>Target Price</column>
<column>Rating</column>
<column>Is Top Idea</column>
<column>Synopsis</column>
<column>Subtitle 1</column>
<column>Paragraph 1</column>
<column>Subtitle 2</column>
<column>Paragraph 2</column>
<column>Subtitle 3</column>
<column>Paragraph 3</column>
<column>Subtitle 4</column>
<column>Paragraph 4</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>AAC Technologies</column>
<column>90.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>D/G to HOLD from BUY w/ TP cut 40% to HKD90 on lowered earnings and target P/E to 15x 2019E (historical avg.) from 21x. 2Q18 earnings missed massively and the 2H18 outlook could be worse than already-lowered expectations due to demand weakness, competition and slow hybrid lenses development progress. Further, the valuation multiple premium to the historical avg. will not be sustained, offsetting the positive impact of strong but risky EPS growth ahead. We prefer Largan (3008 TT) in components.</column>
<column>D/G to HOLD; 2H18 remains tough after 2Q18 miss</column>
<column>D/G to HOLD from BUY and cut TP 40% to HKD90 with lowered earnings (Fig. 2) and target P/E to 15x 2019E (historical avg.) from 21x previously. 2Q18 earnings missed massively, and the 2H18 outlook could be worse than already-lowered expectations due to demand weakness, intense competition and slow hybrid lenses development progress. We also believe the valuation multiple premium to the historical average will not be sustained, thus offsetting the positive impact of strong but risky EPS growth in 2H18/2019E. We prefer Largan (3008 TT) for components pick.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Key takeaways from 2Q18 results&#38;#13;</column>
<column>2Q18 earnings missed massively (Fig. 1), and the biggest disappointment was its gross margin. 2Q18/1H18 gross margins were 35.2%/36.7%. AAC suggested CNY appreciation caused a 300bps gross margin dip, but if we reverse the FX impact 2Q18 gross margin would still be below 40% for the first time since 4Q08, and EPS would have still declined YoY, the first since 3Q14. Negative impact from iPhone production cut and weak demand for high-end Android handsets (particularly Samsung, Oppo and Vivo) was more severe than we had anticipated. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>2H18 remains challenging, 2018 a down year&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We anticipate a strong 2H18 sales recovery with 52% HoH sales growth and 40%+ gross margin driven by seasonality and CNY depreciation. However, such earnings estimates are still below the already-lowered consensus. Sept-2018 could be the first time that AAC has &#38;#60;50% allocation for acoustics and haptics with declining ASP (YoY) for new iPhones; this is because of limited spec upgrades for TFT-LCD based iPhone and competitors’ aggressive pricing. Hybrid lens capacity expansion has also been pushed back. We now believe 2018F sales/earnings will decline YoY. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Still some positives, but not enough to drive upside&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Speaker box ASP still grew YoY thanks to SLS (high-end) adoption, while AAC remains positive for spec upgrade and wider adoptions for all its products in 2019F. We estimate sales and earnings bottomed on a YoY basis in 2Q18. Given the earnings cuts and miss in hybrid lens development – a key re-rating driver for AAC - we believe its previous P/E premium will be hard to sustain. Thus, we believe the share price upside will be capped.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Alibaba Group</column>
<column>190.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>We maintain Street’s only HOLD as we believe the stock is fairly valued for its core business growth based on our DCF analysis. While it is easy to be enamourered over 61% revenue growth as reported in 1QFY19, we remain cautious as the profitable core commerce business provided just 33% growth and the company had already guided for 60% growth for the full year 2019. Moreover, we note that losses from unprofitable businesses are widening. Given this, we opt to wait for a better entry point.</column>
<column>HOLD: Revenue growth driven by unprofitable units</column>
<column>We maintain the Street’s only HOLD as we believe the stock is fairly valued for its core business growth based on our DCF analysis. While it is easy to be enamoured over 61% revenue growth as reported in 1QFY19, we remain cautious as the profitable core commerce business provided just 33% growth and the company had already guided for 60% growth for the full year 2019. Moreover, we note that losses from unprofitable businesses are widening. Given this, we opt to wait for a better entry point at a later time. We tweaked our earnings estimates to factor in weaker profits reported in 1QFY19 (Fig. 10). TP remains unchanged.   &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Decelerating customer management revenue growth&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Customer management revenue and commissions make up 83% of China Commerce revenue, which is the only profitable segment for Alibaba, and 61% of total revenues. The two combined generated just 33% growth, coming in below our expectation, and this will further decelerate. Management has stated that 38-40% growth is achievable in FY19. Barring another ad load, the growth now sounds like a tall order. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Margins are falling rapidly&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Consolidated EBITA margin came in at 33% in 1QFY19, a steep drop from 47% in 1QFY18. Even for the only profitable segment, core commerce, EBITA margin fell from 63% to 47% despite an increase in revenue  to CNY69.2b from CNY43.0b. Incremental revenue of CNY26.1b only generated an EBITA of just CNY6b. Factor in the SBC, and the incremental revenue generated a loss of CNY1.8b. This was due to New Retail, but we find it difficult to give credit for the growth.   &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Consolidating ele.me &#38;#38; Koubei into a new company&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Alibaba could potentially see some upside if the market is willing to assign a higher value for its investments in the two units. Company has created a holding company for the two units and will seek third party investors. Alibaba together with Softbank has committed to invest USD3b. This could be savvy accounting as revaluation gains are possible in FY19.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Alliance Bank</column>
<column>5.000000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>1QFY19 results were within expectations and we see positive traction from the group’s restructuring efforts and investment in new products. 1QFY19 ROE of 10.2% was slightly ahead of management’s 10% target. Our forecasts are maintained, with an unchanged TP of MYR5.00 pegged to a CY19 PBV of 1.3x (CY19E ROE: 10%). Maintain BUY.</column>
<column>1QFY19 ROE slightly ahead of target</column>
<column>1QFY19 results were within expectations and we see positive traction from the group’s restructuring efforts and investment in new products. 1QFY19 ROE of 10.2% was slightly ahead of management’s 10% target. Our forecasts are maintained, with an unchanged TP of MYR5.00 pegged to a CY19 PBV of 1.3x (CY19E ROE: 10%). Maintain BUY.</column>
<column>Within expectations</column>
<column>Alliance Bank’s 1QFY19 core net profit of MYR136m (+1% YoY, +21% QoQ) was in-line at 25%/24% of our full-year forecast/consensus respectively. What is positive is the robust 21% YoY expansion in its high risk-adjusted returns (RAR) loan portfolio, which has contributed to improving yields. This was, however, offset by rising funding costs in 1QFY19, resulting in a 7bps QoQ compression in NIM. One negative is that asset quality continued to weaken, but credit costs have been relatively stable.</column>
<column>Positive traction on restructuring efforts</column>
<column>The group’s transformation is beginning to bear fruit in that i) loan approvals for its high-yielding Alliance One Account are on the rise, ii) SME lending is being ramped up, and iii) its recent VSS/MSS is expected to give rise to cost savings of over MYR20m p.a.. We maintain our forecasts.  </column>
<column>Manageable MFRS9 impact</column>
<column>The Day 1 MFRS9 impact to Alliance Bank was manageable, as total provisions rose 22% YoY. This had a 20bp negative impact to capital. Even so, the group’s CET1 ratio of 12.8% is comfortable, as is its total capital ratio of 17.8%.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Allianz Malaysia</column>
<column>15.500000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>Allianz’s 2Q18 results were within expectations and we maintain our BUY for exposure to one of the largest general insurance companies and a fast growing life insurer in the country. Our SOP-derived TP is raised to MYR16.05 from MYR15.50 on the back of a higher embedded value for the life division, offering a 27% upside to current share price.</column>
<column>Raising our TP to MYR16.05, BUY maintained</column>
<column>Allianz’s 2Q18 results were within expectations and we maintain our BUY for exposure to one of the largest general insurance companies and a fast growing life insurer in the country. Our SOP-derived TP is raised to MYR16.05 from MYR15.50 on the back of a higher embedded value for the life division, offering a 27% upside to current share price.</column>
<column>Results within expectations</column>
<column>Allianz’s 2Q18 core net profit of MYR90m (+25% YoY, +3% QoQ) took 1H18 core net profit to MYR177m (+22% YoY). Pretax profit was within expectations at 51% of our full-year estimates and while net profit was higher at 54%, this was because of a lower-than-expected tax rate which we do not expect to be sustainable. Overall as such, we deem the results to be within expectations and our forecasts are maintained.</column>
<column>A lower tax rate</column>
<column>2Q18 saw Allianz’s general insurance division report a 3.5% YoY increase in operating revenue on the back of higher gross earned premiums (primarily from motor) and investment income. Its life division reported a stronger 15% YoY growth in operating revenue, led by growth in premiums across all key distribution channels. The effective tax rate in 2Q18 was just 22% versus 37% in 2Q17, on account of unrecognized investment losses on its investment-linked accounts, which resulted in a lower deferred tax provision. </column>
<column>A higher embedded value</column>
<column>The embedded value (EV) for the life division has since burgeoned much faster than anticipated and currently stands at MYR1.8b as at end-Jun 2018, versus our initial estimate of MYR1.6b by end-2018. This has largely been driven by the stable growth in new business, which has averaged about MYR150m per annum. Correspondingly, we have upgraded our SOP to reflect this higher valuation for the life business, and attached a P/EV of just 1x (unchanged). As such, our SOP-derived TP is raised to MYR16.05 from MYR15.50.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>AMMB Holdings</column>
<column>4.650000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>AMMB’s 1QFY19 results were within expectations with several operational positives during the quarter. Cost savings are beginning to filter through and this should provide some buffer against any potential reversal in the prevailing net credit recovery situation that the group continues to enjoy. We maintain our forecasts and our TP of MYR4.65, pegged to a CY19 PBV of 0.8x (CY19E ROE of 8%). Providing support to share price is its current FY19E yield of 4.5% - BUY. </column>
<column>BUY maintained</column>
<column>AMMB’s 1QFY19 results were within expectations with several operational positives during the quarter. Cost savings are beginning to filter through and this should provide some buffer against any potential reversal in the prevailing net credit recovery situation that the group continues to enjoy. We maintain our forecasts and our TP of MYR4.65, pegged to a CY19 PBV of 0.8x (CY19E ROE of 8%). Providing support to share price is its current FY19E yield of 4.5% - BUY. </column>
<column>Results within expectations&#38;#13;</column>
<column>AMMB reported a core net profit of MYR348m in 1QFY19 (+1% YoY, -2% QoQ) which was within expectations at 26%/27% of our full-year forecast/consensus. Positives for the quarter include (i) faster loan growth of 9% annualized, (ii) stable QoQ NIM, (iii) operating efficiencies from the recent MSS and (iv) ongoing credit recoveries. On the flip side, NOII contracted YoY and QoQ due to weak capital markets.</column>
<column>Still seeing credit recoveries&#38;#13;</column>
<column>AMMB reported a net credit recovery in 1QFY19 versus a credit charge of 5bps in 4QFY18. Excluding recoveries, credit cost was 51bps in 1QFY19 versus 48bps in 4QFY18. Management’s guidance this round seems to point to much effort to keep credit costs down this FY and it remains to be seen if overall credit cost will be lower than what we have factored in of 20/25bps for FY19/FY20. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Closer to targets&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1QFY19 saw AMMB reporting a cost/income ratio of 51%, which is well within the group’s FY19 target of &#38;#60;55%. 1QFY19 ROE was 8.3% versus its target of =&#38;#62;8.5%. As it stands, we continue to maintain a more conservative ROE estimate of 7.9% for FY19 and undoubtedly any positive surprises would be a re-rating catalyst.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>ANTA Sports Products</column>
<column>49.200000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>ANTA and FountainVest announced an offer of EUR40/sh to acquire the entire share capital of Amer Sports (AMEAS FH, Not-rated), a Finland-based sportswear and sports gear company. This proposal fits in with ANTA’s ambition to become a global company revolving around a multi-brand strategy. ANTA aims to hold more than 50% of Amer with the remainder to be held by FountainVest and other future consortium partners. ANTA will use its cash on hand to finance the deal (no placement).</column>
<column>ANTA is ready to play ball in the global market&#38;#13;</column>
<column>ANTA and FountainVest announced an offer of EUR40/sh to acquire the entire share capital of Amer Sports (AMEAS FH, NR), a Finland-based sportswear and sports gear company. This proposal fits in with ANTA’s ambition to become a global company revolving around a multi-brand strategy. ANTA aims to hold more than 50% of Amer with the remainder to be held by FountainVest and other future consortium partners. ANTA will use its cash on hand and bank borrowings to finance the deal (no placement). Initially, ANTA will only focus on growing Amer’s China and Asia business, and will keep overseas management unchanged.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Expensive?  Not if you look at the strategic upside &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Paying a premium valuation relative to one’s own multiple may seem an expensive acquisition, but not if you consider: 1) the more attractive consolidated PE after the successful acquisition; 2) the enhanced ROE; and 3) the potential upside in value if ANTA is able to leverage the new brands to capture a greater slice of the sports gear and athletic wear market in China. Based on the proposed acquisition price, Amer’s implied FY19 PE is ~25x, which is at a premium to ANTA’s own FY19E PE of ~17x (MKE estimate), and its consolidated pro-forma PE will be at an attractive ~14x, even before considering the strategic upside. The deal is earnings accretive even if it is 100% debt financed, as Amer’s earnings contribution will more than offset the acquisition interest expense. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>ROE may increase, thanks to better use of cash</column>
<column>ANTA has been holding a considerable amount of cash for potential M&#38;#38;A; its net cash by end of Jun 2018 was ~CNY9b. As long as this deal goes through, we estimate its FY19E ROE will increase from 27.1% to 31.5%. Based on our discussions, the company is likely to distribute the extra cash as special dividends if the acquisition falls through.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Amer’s China possibility is there, reiterate BUY</column>
<column>We believe the potential acquisition can provide significant value upside to ANTA if management can replicate FILA’s success on Amer’s China business. While margins will be diluted until Amer’s China sales pick up, pro-forma consolidated operating profits may outgrow ANTA standalone after 5 years as long as ANTA can grow Amer China at a rate above 50% and raise its OPM. We have not revised our earnings forecasts for ANTA pending the successful acquisition. Our TP remains unchanged, peg 26x FY18/19E blended PE, in line with international peers’ 3-year average. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>ASM Pacific Technology</column>
<column>130.000000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain BUY but lower TP from HKD155 to HKD130 (4.2x 2018F P/BV, mid-cycle P/BV). Though its margin expansion is behind our previous forecast, its structural revenue growth remains intact. Earlier bottoming of book-to-billing (BB) ratio in 2Q-3Q18 could form a good re-entry point. ASMP will attend our London conference on 21-22 Jun.</column>
<column></column>
<column>Maintain BUY but lower TP from HKD155 to HKD130 (4.2x 2018F P/BV, mid-cycle P/BV). Though its margin expansion is behind our previous forecast, its structural revenue growth remains intact. Earlier bottoming of book-to-billing (BB) ratio in 2Q-3Q18 could form a good re-entry point. ASMP will attend our London conference on 21-22 Jun.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Structural revenue growth to continue&#38;#13;</column>
<column>ASMP’s record 1Q18 booking (USD754m) and 2Q18 guidance (single digit % YoY growth) suggest its booking continues to trend up YoY, as well as its billing. We are confident this trend is sustainable thanks to ASMP’s diversified exposure. For instance, AA (active alignment) may not grow this year because of slow 3D sensing adoption by the Android camp, but advanced packaging and LED equipment should make up for this, according to our estimates. IC Insights also just reiterated the organization expects global semiconductor capex to grow 14% YoY in 2018F. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Margin expansion slowed &#38;#13;</column>
<column>1Q18’s gross margin of 37.6% (-167bps QoQ, -234bps YoY) was the lowest since 4Q16. While the firm attributed the margin erosion to FX, we believe product mix is another key reason. LED equipment, the key growth driver in 1H18, carries lower margins, while higher-margin AA sales are trending south. The two new acquisitions, NEXX and Amicra, are also potentially margin dilutive before a full integration. ASMP indicated gross margin should rise in 2Q18, but we only anticipate it to go back to 40%+ by 2H18. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Re-entry point is just around the corner&#38;#13;</column>
<column>With the BB ratio peaking earlier than expected in 1Q18 and concerns about the sale of ASM International, shares have been prevented from going up recently. Trading at 3x P/BV (8-yr low except 2015/16 when operating margins were below 10%), with structural sales growth and an estimated 18-21% in operating margins, the shares are undervalued. We revise down our 2018/19F earnings by 8-11% but we are still 2-12% ahead of Bloomberg consensus. In the near term, BB ratio should bottom in 2Q-3Q18 (1-2qtr earlier than usual) and could form a bottoming-out signal.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Axiata Group</column>
<column>4.597834</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Axiata’s exclusion of Idea’s associate losses from its FY18 normalised net profit will enhance dividends, all else equal. Adjusting for this new definition, 1H18 core earnings were below our expectation, with the variance attributable mainly to Robi. Downgrade to HOLD (from BUY) with a lower MYR4.60 TP (-4%) following the recent share price recovery. </column>
<column>Redefining “normalised” </column>
<column>Axiata’s exclusion of Idea’s associate losses from its FY18 normalised net profit will enhance dividends, all else equal. Adjusting for this new definition, 1H18 core earnings were below our expectation, with the variance attributable mainly to Robi. Downgrade to HOLD (from BUY) with a lower MYR4.60 TP (-4%) following the recent share price recovery. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Below expectation</column>
<column>With Idea’s merger almost completed, Axiata will exclude Idea’s contribution (1H18: MYR95m loss) from its FY18 normalised net profit (1Q18 figure has been restated). On this new definition, 2Q18 core net profit of MYR264m (-25% YoY, -19% QoQ) brings 1H18 core net profit to MYR591m (-8% YoY), 38% of our (adjusted) full-year forecast. Note that 2Q18 reported net profit included a MYR3.4b impairment charge for Idea, and that 2Q18 core net profit would have been sequentially higher had Idea’s contribution been included. 1H18 EBITDA of MYR4.1b (-8% YoY) was 46%/44% of our/consensus forecasts respectively. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>A mixed bag  </column>
<column>Celcom was in line, having delivered sequential service revenue growth (+3.0% QoQ) and margin expansion (+1.2ppt QoQ) in 2Q18. XL (Indonesia) delivered sequential EBITDA growth, but slipped into net losses having previously enjoyed tax credits in 1Q18. Robi’s (Bangladesh) revenue has yet to pick up materially post-merger, and would likely post net losses in FY18 with interest expense still elevated. The performances of Dialog (Sri Lanka), Ncell (Nepal) and Smart (Cambodia) were in line.&#38;#13;</column>
<column></column>
<column>We revise our FY18/19/20 core earnings by +11%/-14%/-15% having lowered Robi’s forecasts and excluded Idea’s FY18 associate losses. We lower our SOP-based TP to MYR4.60 (MYR4.80 previously) following our earnings revisions and having incorporated consensus TP for Idea (DCF previously). Downgrade to HOLD (from BUY).</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Beijing Tong Ren Tang CM</column>
<column>18.900000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain BUY. Our thesis that BJTRT will benefit from potential ASP hike and a recovery in HK retail sales has materialized, as share price jumped 70% since 4Q17. Stronger 1Q18 sales prompted us to lift NPAT by 5-7% in FY18-19F, and we introduce our FY20 forecast. Stock transfer from GEM board to mainboard on 29 May should help boost liquidity and market attention. New TP is pegged to 27x FY18F P/E (1 s.d. above hist.l trading avg.), from 22x P/E (hist. trading avg.), in view of positive updates</column>
<column>Thesis plays out well, but more upside still ahead&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Maintain BUY. Our thesis that BJTRT will benefit from potential ASP hike and a recovery in HK retail sales has materialized, as share price jumped 70% since 4Q17. Stronger 1Q18 sales prompted us to lift NPAT by 5-7% in FY18-19F, and we introduce our FY20 forecast. Stock transfer from GEM board to mainboard on 29 May should help boost liquidity and market attention. Our new TP is pegged to 27x FY18F P/E (1 s.d. above historical trading average), from 22x P/E (hist. trading average), in view of positive updates.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Angong ASP raised for first time in two years&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We note that retail ASP of Angong Niuhuang pills, BJTRT’s signature product, was raised from HKD720 to HKD770 in early Mar 2018. While there’s no disclosure, we believe wholesale price adjustment should be similar at ~7%. This is the first ASP hike in two years. Management indicated any further ASP hike is subject to cost and other factors, and as an SOE, they bear a certain social responsibility. Given Angong’s uniqueness, as very few products are able to use natural musk as an input ingredient, we believe it has strong price bargaining power in the long run. We expect ASP hike will be better reflected in upcoming quarters with resilient volume.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Solid demand from both tourists and locals &#38;#13;</column>
<column>1Q18 revenue growth of 20% was the highest since 4Q15, and we believe this was driven by continued recovery in retail and tourism. Other than that, BJTRT’s efforts in capturing greater local demand such as opening new stores and offering promotions also helped. A&#38;#38;P and R&#38;#38;D expenses rose significantly in 2017, although the base was still low at just 2.5% of total sales. We estimate half of its HK sales will come from local demand and the rest from tourists (mainly PRC), which will ease future volatility.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Strengthening overseas presence &#38;#13;</column>
<column>As the dedicated overseas arm of TRT group, BJTRT plans to increase its presence along “one belt one road” countries as well as developed countries such as Japan, Korea and Germany. M&#38;#38;A in relevant TCM (traditional Chinese medicine) sectors will be considered, supported by its strong cash balance and cash flow conversion capability. In terms of store expansion, BJTRT will continue to add 10 new stores p.a. overseas. As of end 2017, BJTRT had a total store count of 80 in 21 countries and regions (26 in HK). It will moderately expand in HK given market maturity and high operating cost. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Bermaz Auto Berhad</column>
<column>2.600000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>Despite lower car prices from GST zero-rating (two out of three months in 1QFY19), volume sales contracted 15% QoQ in Malaysia, leading to lower QoQ earnings in the quarter (-18% QoQ). We take the cautious stance of softer sequential quarter sales as most car buyers would have bought during the zero-rated GST period. Incorporating lower sales volume and higher JPY100/MYR forex, we lower our earnings FY19-21 by 10%-23%. Correspondingly, our TP is lowered to MYR2.60 (-10%); maintain BUY.</column>
<column>Unable to capitalise on zero-rated GST </column>
<column>Despite lower car prices from GST zero-rating (two out of three months in 1QFY19), volume sales contracted 15% QoQ in Malaysia, leading to lower QoQ earnings in the quarter (-18% QoQ). We take the cautious stance of softer sequential quarter sales as most car buyers would have bought during the zero-rated GST period. Incorporating lower sales volume and higher JPY100/MYR forex, we lower our earnings FY19-21 by 10%-23%. Correspondingly, our TP is lowered to MYR2.60 (-10%), pegged to an unchanged 14.5x CY19 PER (mean); maintain BUY. </column>
<column>Some challenges ahead</column>
<column>1QFY19 core net profit of MYR50m (+146% YoY) fell 18% QoQ on the back of lower volume sales due to low inventory holdings (typically ~two months inventory) and the inability to quickly raise production as minor hiccups due to a flood obstructed part of Mazda’s Hiroshima plant. As a result, production in Malaysia also scaled down more than what we had initially expected; associate earnings (i.e. MMSB, Inokom) fell 65% QoQ. While supply chain issues have since been resolved, we see another headwind in the coming quarter as the SST regime kicks in, taking car prices higher again, albeit still slightly lower (1%-3%) than under the previous SST regime for CKD models. In order to preserve its sales volume in Malaysia, Bermaz has offered to absorb the SST for consumers who have made bookings before 1 Sep 2018. While this should somewhat sustain sales in the coming quarter, we caution of lower margins, possibly further exacerbated by the recent weakness in MYR against JPY.</column>
<column>Cut earnings forecasts by 23%/10%/10%</column>
<column>We cut our sales forecasts by 8%-12%, on expectations of a challenging immediate outlook and softer economic growth in the coming two years. Alongside lower margin from higher A&#38;#38;P expenses and JPY100/MYR at 3.70 (from 3.65), we cut our FY19/20/21 net profit forecasts by 23%/10%/10%. Nonetheless, forward growth will still be driven by higher sales from new model launches and a jump in associate earnings as exports scale up.</column>
<column>Still a growth stock with undemanding valuations&#38;#13;</column>
<column>At 11.5x CY19 PER currently, BAuto is undervalued for its growth (23% 3-year earnings CAGR) and dividend angles (5.6% for FY19 on 80% DPR).</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>BIMB Holdings</column>
<column>4.300000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>While BIMB’s 1H18 results were marginally above expectations, there are uncertainties at this stage at both the bank and takaful units. Until there is a little more clarity, we see little catalyst for the stock and downgrade BIMB to HOLD with a lower SOP-derived TP of MYR4.30 (MYR4.80 previously). Dividend yields of &#62;4% provide support.</column>
<column>Little catalyst at this stage, downgrade to HOLD</column>
<column>While BIMB’s 1H18 results were marginally above expectations, there are uncertainties at this stage at both the bank and takaful units. Until there is a little more clarity, we see little catalyst for the stock and downgrade BIMB to HOLD with a lower SOP-derived TP of MYR4.30 (MYR4.80 previously). Dividend yields of &#38;#62;4% provide support.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Results marginally above expectations</column>
<column>BIMB’s 2Q18 net profit of MYR150m (+11% YoY, -13% QoQ) took 1H18 net profit to MYR322m (+12% YoY). The results were marginally above expectations at 53%/52% of our full-year estimates/consensus. Its profit spread held up better than expected, while credit costs were lower QoQ. We raise our FY18-20 group net profit forecasts by 1-3% to factor in better margins at Bank Islam, offset by a 1% (FY18E) and 4-5% (FY19-20E) cut in STMB’s earnings estimates on an assumed reduction in wakalah fee transfers.</column>
<column>Some uncertainties at this stage</column>
<column>An uncertainty at this stage is the possible restructuring of the BIMB group which we think could involve the transfer of BIMB’s listing status to Bank Islam, and a possible rights issue to repay a shareholder debt of MYR1.3b. Discussions are still preliminary at stage. Bank Islam, meanwhile, has yet to replace its Retail and Commercial Banking Heads while its Acting CEO has yet to be confirmed. At STMB, there is a need to preserve capital at the general takaful division, which could, in our view, result in a lower wakalah fee transfer ratio to shareholders.</column>
<column>Lowering our SOP to MYR4.30</column>
<column>On updating our valuation parameters, we have lowered our Sum-of-Parts valuation for BIMB by 50sen to MYR4.30, to reflect the uncertainties above. Our 2019F PBV target for Bank Islam is lowered to 1.2x from 1.4x, supported by an est. ROE of 11.5% (11.9% previously). STMB currently trades at a historical Jun 2018 PBV of 3.4x, which is what we have applied to valuations (4.2x Dec 2017 PBV previously).</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Boustead Plantations</column>
<column>1.220000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>BPLANT recorded its first quarterly core loss since 4Q15, mainly on low output and low CPO ASP, amidst rising cost pressures. We expect better operational results in 2H18 and a potential land disposal gain of MYR116m to lift overall sentiment. Only consolation this quarter is a 2nd interim DPS of 2.5sen (ex-date: 6 Sept). Keeping our earnings forecasts for now pending update. No change to our HOLD call and RNAV-based TP of MYR1.22.</column>
<column>Expect better 2H18 performance </column>
<column>BPLANT recorded its first quarterly core loss since 4Q15, mainly on low output and low CPO ASP, amidst rising cost pressures. We expect better operational results in 2H18 and a potential land disposal gain of MYR116m to lift overall sentiment. Only consolation this quarter is a 2nd interim DPS of 2.5sen (ex-date: 6 Sept). Keeping our earnings forecasts for now pending update. No change to our HOLD call and RNAV-based TP of MYR1.22. </column>
<column>2Q18 results disappointed</column>
<column>BPlant slipped into the red with 2Q18 core loss of MYR22m (2Q17: +MYR9m, 1Q18: +MYR5m), which dragged 1H18 into a core loss of MYR17m (1H17: +MYR38m). Against our MYR72m core PATMI forecast for FY18, results were below expectation. The weak 2Q18 was due to (i) decline in CPO ASP to MYR2,421/t (-13% YoY, -3% QoQ) and (ii) lower FFB output (-11% YoY, -9% QoQ) as oil palm trees appear to enter into biological rest. 2Q18 EBIT was a negative which could be compounded by higher fertilising activities and losses from consolidation of Dutaland estates (completed on 16 May 2018).</column>
<column>1H18 output behind forecast for now</column>
<column>For 1H18, FFB output of 431,349 MT (-2% YoY) met only 42% of our full-year forecasts. This is below the historical 1H:2H ratio of 46:54. The crop pattern may have changed somewhat this year and we suspect output will only pick up strongly towards year end. For now, we are keeping our +5% YoY growth forecasts for FY18.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>2H18 headline profits to be lifted by disposal gains</column>
<column>Pending an update with management, we are keeping our earnings forecasts for now. 2H18 headline profits may be lifted by a one-off net disposal gain of MYR116m following a proposed disposal of a Penang land announced in Jan 2018 measuring 139ha for MYR136m cash (note: we have yet to factor this disposal gain into our forecasts). Operationally, 2H results should be stronger on higher output and lower fertilising costs. Nonetheless, we reckon BPlant needs to continue monetising even more prime estates to sustain its high dividend payout. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Bursa Malaysia</column>
<column>7.250000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Bursa’s 1H18 net profit was slightly ahead of our estimates, while a special dividend also surprised on the upside. We however make no change to our earnings forecasts, expecting activities to ‘normalise’. Our TP is also unchanged at MYR7.25 as we continue to peg on a 25x PER (average of peers) on current year earnings.</column>
<column>Maintaining forecasts, HOLD call</column>
<column>Bursa’s 1H18 net profit was slightly ahead of our estimates, while a special dividend also surprised on the upside. We however make no change to our earnings forecasts, expecting activities to ‘normalise’. Our TP is also unchanged at MYR7.25 as we continue to peg on a 25x PER (average of peers) on current year earnings.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Earnings marginally ahead</column>
<column>Bursa’s 2Q18 net profit of MYR58m (-2% YoY, -9% QoQ) lifts 1H18 net profit to MYR122m (+5% YoY), at 52% of our FY18E. The slight earnings outperformance was due to 2Q18 equity ADV remaining high at MYR2.88b (we expected MYR2.6b; 1Q18: MYR2.93b) as May 2018’s ADV reached a record high of MYR3.74b. Heavy foreign participation post GE14 on 9 May (we estimate 26% foreign participation in May, 33% in June, 28% in 2Q18 vs. 23% in 1Q18) boosted trades. 1H18 equity ADV rose 9% YoY to MYR2.9b. Derivative total contracts contracted 3% YoY in 2Q18, and 8% YoY in 1H18. Trading revenue from equity/derivative made up 53%/14% of operating revenue in 1H18 (1H17: 52%/15%). Cost items were stable.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Special dividend surprise &#38;#13;</column>
<column>A first interim DPS of 14sen (1H17: 13.3sen, after adjusting for a 1-for-2 bonus issue completed on 13 Apr 2018) and a special 8sen (1H17: 10sen - adjusted) were declared; ex- on 16 Aug. The interim dividend represents a 93% DPR which was in-line, but the special dividend (for the second sequential year) was a surprise. Total cash payout would amount to MYR177m, we estimate, vs. MYR312m cash balance as at end-Jun 2018. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>No change to our assumptions for now&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We maintain our MYR2.7b equity ADV forecast for FY18 for now, which implies MYR2.5b equity ADV in 3Q-4Q18. Trading activities have tapered in Jul 2018 MTD with equity ADV down to MYR2.4b (till 27 Jul). We maintain our earnings forecasts but raise our DPS forecast for the current year to reflect the 8sen special.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Cahya Mata Sarawak</column>
<column>4.100000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>With all 16 furnaces operating at full capacity, OMS has begun to look at Phase 2 for expansion. CMS also reiterated it is already looking at alternative sources of supply for its premix raw materials. Growth for FY18E remains intact, largely supported by OMS, construction and road maintenance. Our earnings, SOP-based TP and BUY call are unchanged.</column>
<column>Maintain BUY&#38;#13;</column>
<column>With all 16 furnaces operating at full capacity, OMS has begun to look at Phase 2 for expansion. CMS also reiterated it is already looking at alternative sources of supply for its premix raw materials. Growth for FY18E remains intact, largely supported by OMS, construction and road maintenance. Our earnings, SOP-based TP and BUY call are unchanged. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Phase 2 of OMS to take off?</column>
<column>The 16th furnace has been fired up as of 1 June 2018, bringing OMS to a total of 10 furnaces producing ferrosilicon and the remaining 6 producing manganese alloy. With production at the plant running at full capacity, OMS has begun to relook at Phase 2 of the plant, which was temporarily put on hold in view of the weak ferrosilicon prices in early-2016. To recall, Phase 2’s plans was originally supposed to involve a 565k MT p.a. manganese ferroalloy and sintered manganese ore plant costing e.USD150m. We believe new arrangements could be in the works and expect to hear further details in the quarters to come. </column>
<column>Addressing the supply concern for premix raw mat</column>
<column>The shortage of quarry aggregates and sand in Sarawak has been attributed to the steep spike in demand for the materials from Pan Borneo Sarawak Highway (PBSH). We understand from CMS that its two largest suppliers (HSL and Shin Yang) have stopped selling to CMS as there is insufficient aggregates and sand even for their own construction use. CMS is exploring alternative supply sources for the materials, not discounting that it could also potentially acquire an existing quarry. </column>
<column>FY18E growth intact</column>
<column>Our earnings forecasts remain unchanged. We believe the shortfall at the construction materials segment would be more than offset by the stronger contribution OMS. Earnings in 2H18 would also be supported by its construction and road maintenance division on the back of higher work progress at PBSH and road length maintained. In the mid-long term, i) Phase 2 of its OMS plant and ii) commissioning of its Integrated Phosphate Plant (40% stake) could be potential earnings wildcards. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Cathay Pacific</column>
<column>12.300000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1H18 core PATAMI of HKD7m is a big turnaround from a loss of HKD2,457m in 1H17. Yields are recovering and cost items apart from fuel are well contained. A DPS of HKD0.10 was declared. 2H is a seasonally stronger half and we believe Cathay is on track to meet our revised forecasts. We roll forward our base valuation year to 2019 and peg it to an unchanged 0.75x P/BV, and derive a TP of HKD12.30. We are unwilling to be a buyer as we see structural risks capping further upside.</column>
<column>U/G to HOLD, worst is over. Raise TP to HKD12.30</column>
<column>1H18 core PATAMI of HKD7m is a big turnaround from a loss of HKD2,457m in 1H17. Yields are recovering and cost items apart from fuel are well contained. A DPS of HKD0.10 was declared. 2H is a seasonally stronger half and we believe Cathay is on track to meet our revised forecasts. We roll forward our base valuation year to 2019 and peg it to an unchanged 0.75x P/BV, and derive a TP of HKD12.30. Despite the positive trends, we are unwilling to be a buyer as we see structural risks capping further upside.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Yield recovery suggests the worst has passed&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Yield growth was strong for passengers (+7.6% YoY) and cargo (+16.3% YoY). Management has been very clinical in its capacity deployment and successfully maintained its high overall load factor of 75.6% (+0.9ppt YoY) in 1H18. The current trend is the exceptionally positive premium cabin and cargo markets , which benefits Cathay as these are its key business strengths. Chinese carrier rivals also slowed down their capacity deployment in 1H18, thus easing off irrational competition and providing some degree of pricing power.     </column>
<column>Fuel is the industry’s bogeymen&#38;#13;</column>
<column>The volatile fuel price is the main risk for the industry at the moment. Cathay has hedged 45% of 2H18 fuel needs at an average price of USD80.50/bbl (Brent), which is slightly above current market levels. In 2019, it has hedged 29% of fuel needs at an average price of USD65/bbl. This means Cathay has some degree of upside protection relative to the China and Taiwan-based carriers, all of whom are not hedged.      &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Balanced risk-reward, HOLD</column>
<column>Despite the improving outlook, Cathay still faces structural issues. For instance, Hong Kong International Airport’s (HKIA) rising charges is becoming prohibitive for transit passengers and more Chinese mainline carriers are launching direct long-haul services. A fair value of 1SD below its mean reflects all these aforementioned risks, in our view.  </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>CGN Power</column>
<column>2.700063</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>1H18 results were largely in line with our forecasts. We expect new units, including Taishan unit 1 and Yangjiang Unit 5 to drive CGN’s earnings and operating cash flows in 2H18. With stronger cash flow, we expect a 4.7% dividend yield for FY19E. We believe commencement of Taishan unit 1 will lift market concerns over plant start-up, while progress with its A-share listing application could be a catalyst. Reiterate BUY with DCF-based TP of HKD2.70 (WACC 6.6%; LTD 2.0%).</column>
<column>Earnings improvement to be driven by new units&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1H18 results were largely in line with our forecasts. We expect new units, including Taishan unit 1 and Yangjiang Unit 5, will drive CGN’s earnings and operating cash flows in 2H18. In fact, operating cash flow rose 10% YoY in 1H18. With stronger cash flow, we expect a 4.7% dividend yield for FY19E. We believe commencement of Taishan unit 1 will lift market concerns over plant start-up, while progress with its A-share listing application could also be a catalyst. Reiterate BUY with DCF-based TP of HKD2.70 (WACC: 6.6%; LTG: 2.0%).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Operating cash flow rose by 10%&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Net recurring profit fell 4.3% YoY to CNY4,348m in 1H18. Revenue rose 7.5% YoY to CNY23b, mainly because wind power generation grew 9.2% YoY. The mild decline in profit was mainly due to the increase in overhaul cost at the Guangdong nuclear units. However, operating cash flow rose by 10% YoY to CNY14b.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Commencement of generation units on track</column>
<column>Yangjiang Unit 5 qualified for commercial commencement in Jul-18, while Taishan Unit 1 (the first GEN-III EPR unit) entered grid-connection phase in Jun-18. We believe commencement of CGN’s nuclear generation units is on track and these should start to generate cash flow. We forecast the FCF yield will double to 7.6% in FY19E, which could help boost the dividend yield to 4.7%.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Maintain BUY and DCF-based TP of HKD2.70</column>
<column>Given our forecast 14% ROE in FY18, in our view CGN appears undervalued trading at only ~0.6x FY19E P/BV. Likely catalysts include further rise in utilisation hours, approval of new units and A-share listing. The China Securities Regulatory Commission  accepted CGN’s A-share application in Jun-18. We believe listing could be completed by end-2018, and total net proceeds could be around 10% of total share capital, based on our estimates.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Biologic Products</column>
<column>83.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>CBPO announced that it rejected the USD118/sh bid from a consortium that includes the former CEO Gao, valuing it at c.USD3.9b. It also stated that CITIC capital withdrew its bid to acquire CBPO at USD110. Instead, CITIC will join a private placement whereby CBPO will issue 5.85m new shares at USD100.9 to Chairman Li, CITIC, Hillhouse and PW Medtech. The Consortium immediately responded by threatening legal action.Our SOTP-based TP of USD83 does not account for a takeover-related premium swing.</column>
<column>CBPO rejects one bidder, allies with another and issues new shares in private placement&#38;#13;</column>
<column>CBPO announced on Friday that it had rejected the 17 AUG USD118 per share bid from a consortium that includes the ousted CEO David Gao, GL Capital, Bank of China Investment and CDH, which values the firm at c.USD3.9b. It also stated that CITIC Capital withdrew its 11 JUN bid to acquire CBPO at USD110, valuing it at USD3.7b. Instead, CITIC will join a private placement whereby CBPO will issue 5.85m new shares at USD100.9 per share, for proceeds of USD590.3m to chairman David Li, CITIC, Hillhouse  and PW Medtech, the largest shareholder of CBPO. The consortium immediately responded by threatening legal action. It is rare to see such contests in Asia. Our SOTP-based TP of USD83 does not account for takeover-related premium share price swing.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Rejected USD3.9b bid from the consortium&#38;#13;</column>
<column>CBPO said that the board of directors unanimously rejected the bid from the consortium as “it did not reflect the intrinsic value of the company”. There was no evidence that CBPO engaged the consortium for discussion.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Issued 15% more shares in private placement</column>
<column>CBPO’s board had also agreed to issue 5.85m new shares (increasing the pre-issue share base by c.15%) at USD100.9 per share, for proceeds of USD590.3m, to a group of PE funds, including Centurium Capital (owned by chairman Li), CITIC, Hillhouse Capital and PW Medtech. This group will own 37.39% of CBPO after the placement. This placement is dilutive to all other existing shareholders. The share price dropped 15.85% on Friday, largely reflecting this dilution.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Consortium to mount legal challenge</column>
<column>The consortium issued a press release stating: “We will evaluate all our options, including legal action, to hold the Board accountable and ensure that they act in the best interest of all shareholders.”</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Datang Renewable</column>
<column>1.800000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>DTR’s 1H18 results were largely in line with our expectations, and affirm our view that lower curtailment will boost earnings. We expect earnings growth momentum to continue, supported by favourable policies, such as red-alert policies for curtailed regions. DTR will benefit especially as it has the largest exposure in these areas vs. its peers. Maintain BUY and DCF-based TP of HKD1.80 (WACC 9.9%; LTD 3.0%).</column>
<column>Earnings boosted by lower curtailment &#38;#13;</column>
<column>DTR’s 1H18 results were largely in line with our expectations, and affirm our view that lower curtailment will boost earnings. We expect earnings growth momentum to continue, supported by favourable policies, such as red-alert policies for curtailed regions (Fig.4). DTR will benefit especially as it has the largest exposure in these areas vs. its peers. Maintain BUY and DCF-based TP of HKD1.80 (WACC: 9.9%; LTG: 3%).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1H18 results in line, robust earnings growth&#38;#13;</column>
<column>DTR’s 1H18 revenue rose 26% YoY to CNY4,366m mainly driven by 30% YoY growth in wind power generation. Operating margin improved by 9.7ppt to 52.7% and attributable net profit surged 107.9% YoY to CNY947m. The improved profitability was mainly due to higher wind utilization hours, which grew by 19% or 181hrs to 1,122hrs in 1H18. The improvement in wind generation in Gansu and Jilin provinces was the main driver for DTR as 17% of its total capacity is located in these areas. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Tariff policies will be the focus&#38;#13;</column>
<column>According to m.bjx.com.cn, the National Energy Administration mentioned in its consultation paper that the feed-in tariff subsidy of existing wind farms could be unchanged for 20 years. According to the news, the government is also consulting the industry about potentially permitting wind producers to sell green certificates as a way to compensate them for excess wind power produced beyond the guaranteed utilization hours, whereas any shortfalls compared to the feed-in subsidy could still be collected from the Renewable Energy Fund. If this proposal is confirmed, it could remove policy overhang and improve wind farms’ cash flow, in our view.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Remains cheap, BUY&#38;#13;</column>
<column>DTR is trading at a P/E of 6.9x FY18E and we think it remains cheap considering our forecast 3-year earnings CAGR of 41.6% (from 2017 to 2020E). We expect catalysts will include additional favourable policies, improvement in utilisation hours supported by additional UHV lines and lower curtailment rates. Maintain BUY with DCF-based TP of HKD1.80.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Foods</column>
<column>4.950000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain BUY with TP unchanged at HKD4.95. We believe CF has more confidence in expanding its beverage sales than its competitors, which have conceded they have no solid strategy to succeed. Furthermore, CF should be a beneficiary as Coke re-energizes growth in China through numerous new product launches and greater online media exposure. CF’s 1H18 results support our thesis that it should benefit from its network refranchising and synergies will help improve profitability going forward.  </column>
<column>Leverage Coke’s strength and refranchising benefits </column>
<column>Maintain BUY. We believe CF has more confidence in expanding its beverage sales than its competitors, which have conceded they have no solid strategy to succeed. Furthermore, CF should be a beneficiary as Coke re-energizes growth in China through numerous new product launches and greater online media exposure. Meanwhile, CF’s 1H18 results support our thesis that it should benefit from its network refranchising and synergies will help improve profitability going forward (refer to our previous China Foods report for our thesis). Our forecasts and TP are unchanged, based on a target 11x FY18F EV/EBITDA, in line with peers. </column>
<column>Exciting launch pipeline across full market spectrum </column>
<column>For 1H18, CF’s volume sales grew 27% YoY but sales value rose 30% YoY. This is the first time sales value growth exceeded sales volume growth. Organic growth was 11%/12% YoY in terms of volume/value. We believe this demonstrates product-mix-upgrade efforts are bearing fruit, thanks to the launch of its “No Sugar” series and the introduction of modern cans for its fizzy drinks, as well as new products in other drinks categories. In fact, CF launched 28 new SKUs in 1H18 under 11 different brands; new products already account for 3%/6% of volume/ sales despite being launched only in 2Q18. CF indicated more new products under different categories will be launched from 2H18.</column>
<column>Synergy from new plants &#38;#38; regions just kicking in&#38;#13;</column>
<column>CF completed its refranchising project in Apr-17 and has now achieved complete coverage of northern and western China. Of note, its overall expenses ratio decreased by 2ppt YoY or 0.9ppt in organic terms in 1H18. This shows CF is working towards narrowing the profitability gap between the newly acquired plants and its existing plants; the EBIT margin difference has been reduced to 1ppt from 2ppt+ when those plants were consolidated from Apr-17. For example, CF has switched the IT system of new plants to its own system and has managed to save cost.  Meanwhile, CF has also managed to lower manufacturing cost per unit.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Awaiting positive updates as catalysts&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We believe news of progress by CF towards implementing its employee stock option and incentive programmes would cheer the market. Likewise, strong sales of its “Monster Energy Drink” would also boost investor sentiment as sales remain lacklustre to date. Turnaround of Monster Energy Drink sales would be positive as it would help broaden CF’s addressable market in China. CF added that it will keep dividend payout stable at 30%, though it could rise to 40-50% if net gearing improves. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Longyuan Power</column>
<column>7.799531</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>1Q18 net profit surged 67% YoY (PRC accounting) driven by strong wind generation growth of 33%; Wind cap. growth was relatively low at 5.9% YoY. The results support our thesis that operators are investing more cautiously in new wind capacity in order to help lower curtailments and raise profitability. Operators should also benefit from higher renewable energy demand from the recent policy consultation about Renewable Portfolio Standards (RPS). Reiterate BUY w/TP +10% to HKD7.80 on EPS increases.</column>
<column>Robust earnings growth in 1Q18&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1Q18 net profit surged 67% YoY (based on PRC accounting standard), mainly driven by strong wind generation growth of 33%; Wind capacity growth was relatively low at 5.9% YoY. The results support our thesis that operators are investing more cautiously in new wind capacity in order to help lower curtailments and raise overall profitability. Operators should also benefit from higher renewable energy demand from the recent policy consultation about Renewable Portfolio Standards (RPS). Reiterate BUY with DCF-based TP raised 10% to HKD7.80 (WACC:8.9%, LTG:3.0%), mainly due to an upwards revision to our earnings estimates after lifting utilization hours by 5% in FY18E and FY19E.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Generation rose 33% YoY in 1Q18&#38;#13;</column>
<column>LY’s 1Q18 PRC earnings rose 67% YoY to CNY1.9b, which was higher than our expectation. The main earnings driver was the 33% YoY growth in wind generation on the back of our estimated ~26% YoY increase in wind utilisation hours. The operating performance benefited from good wind resources (Fig. 12) and the curtailment improvement in 1Q. EBIT margin also expanded by 10ppt to 46.8% in 1Q18.   &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Undergoing RPS consultation; favourable policy&#38;#13;</column>
<column>In late Mar’18, China’s National Energy Administration released a consultation policy draft for RPS with the provincial RE targets set for both 2018 and 2020 (Fig 13). With these targets, we expect wind power demand to increase, driving up utilisation hours and reducing curtailments. The national curtailment ratio was 8.5% in 1Q18 compared to 12.1% in 4Q17. We expect the ratio to continue to trend down and we believe the government can achieve its target of 5% in 2020. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Reiterate BUY with higher TP of HKD7.80</column>
<column>LY is trading at 1.0x P/B and 9.0x P/E for FY18E, both below the 6-year historical means. Catalysts include favourable policies, details on Green Certificate, further improvement in utilisation hours driven by UHV lines and lower curtailment rates. We raised our utilisation forecast by 5% for both FY18E/19E due to the strong 1Q18 generation and the RPS policy. Reiterate BUY. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Mengniu Dairy</column>
<column>26.800000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>U/G to BUY from HOLD on a valuation/price basis after the 22% share price correction from mid-June which now factors in our concerns of pressure on FY18E EBIT margin. Management provided slightly higher sales guidance and confirmed the strategy for driving moderate operating margin expansion going forward. Accordingly, we raise sales and EBIT margin assumptions (+20-30bps pa vs flat previously), which lift our FY18-20F NPAT by 5%/5%/10% and our TP marginally to HKD26.80 due to a lower CNY est.</column>
<column>U/G to BUY on signs of slight uptick in EBIT margin </column>
<column>U/G to BUY from HOLD on a valuation/price basis after the 22% share price correction from mid-June which now factors in our concerns of pressure on FY18E EBIT margin. Management provided slightly higher sales guidance and confirmed the strategy for driving moderate operating margin expansion going forward. Accordingly, we raise sales and EBIT margin assumptions (+20-30bps pa vs flat previously; see Fig.’s 6-7), which lift our FY18-20F NPAT by 5%/5%/10% and our TP marginally to HKD26.80 reflecting a 4% lower CNY assumption. Our new TP remains pegged to a target 27x FY18F PER equal to 1 SD above its historical average.</column>
<column>Key is more marketing, rather than offering discounts</column>
<column>Mengniu’s 1H18 sales growth was driven by both higher volume and a better product mix (40%/60% volume/mix). Sales of high-margin drinks, including Milk Deluxe and room-temperature yogurt grew by strong double digits YoY. Meanwhile, Mengniu’s affirmation of its principle of not offering price discounts is encouraging; it also said it will enhance brand equity to drive sales growth. Looking ahead, marketing will be more skewed towards sports and away from entertainment. Management said the response to its brand survey has been positive so far, revealing its A&#38;#38;P’s effectiveness.</column>
<column>Early mover in emerging channels with strong partners</column>
<column>As sales channels are increasingly becoming fragmented, we believe Mengniu is well placed to capitalise on this trend. As an illustration, Mengniu ranks No.1 in online liquid milk sales with a 24% market share, based on Nielsen data. For B2B, Mengniu has strategic and exclusive co-operations with Huixiadan and LST1668, which are B2B e-commerce platforms under Tencent (700HK, Not Rated) and Alibaba (BABA US, CP USD178.5, HOLD, TP USD190). These will facilitate orders being placed to distributors from small shops. </column>
<column>More commitment to growing new businesses</column>
<column>Mengniu has identified several new growth drivers, including fresh milk, cheese, plant-based products, as well as overseas expansion. Of note, it is entering into the ASEAN market, and its new factory in Indonesia is scheduled to commence operation in 4Q18. Fresh milk in particular is being viewed as a game changer for the future as Mengniu can leverage its strong cold chain storage and delivery capabilities.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Mobile</column>
<column>77.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>With the valuation in the lowest P/E band in four years, we looked for but did not find enough in 1H18 results to become more positive. While a 12.5% increase in the interim DPS was a pleasant surprise, we believe it is prudent to standby and wait for a better day as we see headwinds picking up in 2H18. Our modestly lowered earnings estimates for 2018-2020 are 20-30% below consensus  (DCF-based TP also slightly lowered to HKD77). We await consensus reductions before considering a BUY.</column>
<column>HOLD as headwinds about to pick up in 2H18</column>
<column>With China Mobile (CM) shares trading in the lowest P/E band in four years (~11x 12M FWD basis), we looked for encouraging signs in 1H18 results to turn more positive on the stock. While a 12.5% increase in the interim DPS was a pleasant surprise, we believe it is more prudent to sit on the side line and wait for a better day as we see headwinds picking up rather than subsiding in 2H18. Our modestly lowered earnings estimates for 2018-2020 are 20-30% below consensus forecasts as we believe competitive pressure will lead to mobile revenue compression and an earnings decline (DCF-based TP also slightly lowered to HKD77). We would wait for consensus to factor in the risks before considering a BUY.</column>
<column>Mobile ARPU will fall further in 2H18&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1H18 ARPU is not the bottom; 1H18 ARPU fell nearly 7% from 1H17, but we forecast another 12% decline to CNY51.1 in 2H18. With the introduction of new nationwide unlimited data plans in 2Q18, and a 3% impact from the IFRS accounting change, we believe this is a more probable scenario. Our full-year revenue forecast is 3% below consensus. We believe there is downside risk to consensus for FY18-20, as the ARPU and mobile-sub market share risks haven’t been amply reflected.  &#38;#13;</column>
<column>May disappointment on final dividend &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Management did the right thing by increasing the interim dividend, but investors could be disappointed if the final dividend is not increased by a similar magnitude. However, CM needs to pay out 69% of 2018 net profit (based on our estimate) to increase the final dividend payout by 13% from 2017, which is unlikely, in our view. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>5G trials in 2H18 further reinforces capex risk</column>
<column>CM plans to test 5G applications in 2H18 as the initial standards have been set. This uncertainty poses some capex risk over the next two years. The company aims to roll out the 5G network in 2019 and eyes commercial launch in 2020. Management stated that 5G capex for 2018 is already included within the company’s guidance. We forecast CM’s capex to rise to 27% of sales in 2019 and peak at 29% in 2020, before declining in 2021.   </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Resources Beer</column>
<column>29.300000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>U/G to HOLD from SELL. We were surprised by the decent mix upgrade in 1H18, opex control and CRB’s strong confidence in further enhancement. We raise FY18/19/20F adjusted EBITDA (ex-impairment) by 11%/11%/16%. Our TP remains pegged to a target 15x FY18F EV/EBITDA (ex-impairment), at the high-end of the range vs. global peers, considering industry premiumization prospects in China. We roll forward our valuation to blended FY18-FY19E.</column>
<column>More room for cost savings; Raise TP 15% to HKD29.3</column>
<column>U/G to HOLD from SELL. We were surprised by the decent mix upgrade in 1H18, opex control and CRB’s strong confidence in further enhancement. We raise FY18/19/20F adjusted EBITDA (ex-impairment) by 11%/11%/16%. Our TP remains pegged to a target 15x EV/EBITDA (ex-impairment), at the high-end of the range vs. global peers, considering industry premiumization prospects in China. We roll forward our valuation to blended FY18-FY19E. We refrained from upgrading to BUY in view of a potential sales slowdown in 2H18 and raw material cost pressure in FY19E. </column>
<column>1H18 surprises: better sales mix and profitability</column>
<column>In 1H18, sales of its mid-end beer now account for 43% of total sales, up from 39% a year ago which we believe played a role (in addition to price hikes) in driving up ASP by 13% YoY. We estimate product mix upgrade should drive ASP up 5% YoY, which would represent a sharp acceleration from just 2-3% pa over the past few years. This would offset volume decline of 1.5% YoY, as CRB strategically reduces its focus on low-margin products, and as it has been encountering challenges in northeastern China. CRB reiterated that its sales are growing well in almost all regions.</column>
<column>Full premiumization game plan is underway</column>
<column>CRB will launch several more mid to high-end beer brands following the success of its “Brave the World Super X” and “Concept Series” launches. CRB believes it can increase its presence in the high-end market by leveraging both Heineken and its own brand cluster as these products cover the complete retail price range of CNY10-20+. CRB anticipates selling Heineken beer nationwide, but with more focus on eastern and southern China. This would complement CRB’s current competitive weakness. We are more convinced about its premumization game plan than before.</column>
<column>New norms: quality growth &#38;#38; lean sales management</column>
<column>To summarize, 1H18 confirms several new positives ahead: i) more focus on profit and less on volume sales; ii) accelerating capacity optimisation; and iii) leaner organisation structure. As such, we raise our adjusted EBITDA margin by 1.6-2.4ppt for FY18-20F on the back of both better gross margins and opex control. Upgrade to HOLD from SELL.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Telecom Corporation</column>
<column>4.500000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Reiterate BUY and raise DCF/SOTP TP by 5% on revisions to profit est.'s as we found mobile business resilient on continued strong sub growth and the fixed line revenue growth reaccelerated serendipitously in 1H18. IDC, Cloud, Big Data are not only helping to mitigate the declining broadband access revenues but are now large enough to contribute to growth. We raised our revenue est.'s mainly on a greater contribution from this segment, and our EPS est.'s from better selling cost management.</column>
<column>TP up 5% on solid mobile and now sexier fixed line&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Reiterate BUY and raise our DCF/SOTP based TP by 5% on upwards revisions to profit estimates (see Fig. 6) as we found mobile business resilient on continued strong sub growth and the fixed line revenue growth reaccelerated serendipitously in 1H18. IDC, Cloud, Big Data are not only helping to mitigate the declining broadband access revenues but are now large enough to contribute to growth. We raised our revenue forecasts for FY18-20 mostly on greater contribution from this segment, and better selling cost management drove our earnings estimates up 9-19%.  &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Leading mobile growth despite the falling ARPU&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We continue to be impressed with CT’s ability to manage mobile revenue growth of 10% (more if it wasn’t for IFRS accounting change) in the current pressured regulatory- environment. CT is able to generate solid growth because it gained 2% of subscriber market share in the last 12 months. ARPU continued to decline by 8% YoY in 1H18, but as long as the sub growth outpaces ARPU decline, mobile growth will continue, in our view.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>IDC &#38;#38; Cloud growth flying under the radar&#38;#13;</column>
<column>CT’s information &#38;#38; app segment saw 18% growth YoY and contributed 2.9pp of the total service revenue growth of 7pp in 1H18. This segment has been flying under the radar because of its small contributions in the past. But this is no longer the case, as it now makes up 18% of total service revenues. Not only is this contributing to revenue growth but the segment also helps to mitigate churn rates.  Because of its 59% triple play penetration, CT’s broadband churn rate is a mere 1.1%. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Solid net profit growth of 8%&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1H18 proved that CT is able to generate solid, consistent growth with both mobile and fixed line. For this reason, we now subscribe to a more constructive scenario for 2H18. While CT lacks the sex appeal at times because of its relatively larger fixed line network, the company is positioned to leverage its fiber to the home network. Given the current need for more defensive value ideas, we believe CT fits the bill. BUY.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>China Unicom</column>
<column>11.600000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Upgrade Unicom to BUY. The company is turning the corner by leveraging the mixed ownership benefits – a key transition the market has not yet fairly valued, in our view. Our initial concerns of a steep decline in ARPU in 2H18 have been allayed and we now believe in a soft landing scenario. 1H18 results were solid despite some tariff adjustments. We are more confident that Unicom’s earning rebound story will be unencumbered. We raise ARPU and revenue est.'s, earnings, and SOTP/DCF based TP 11%.</column>
<column>TP up 11% – Second time is just as attractive</column>
<column>Upgrade Unicom to BUY as we believe the company is turning the corner by leveraging the mixed ownership benefits – a key transition the market has not yet fairly valued, in our view. Our initial concerns about a steep decline in ARPU in 2H18 were allayed after our recent discussions with the company led us to believe in a soft landing scenario. 1H18 results were solid despite some of the tariff adjustments. We are more confident that Unicom’s earning rebound story will be unencumbered. We raise our ARPU and revenue estimates, which led us to increase our earnings estimates by 34% and 40% for 2018 and 2019, and lift our SOTP/DCF based TP by 11% to HKD11.60.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Strong 1H18 mobile and BB rev boosts confidence</column>
<column>Unicom’s revenue growth is supported by ARPU stability.  Mobile revenue grew 10% and fixed line 6% YoY in 1H18. We are impressed that fixed line is finally turning the corner with two consecutive quarters of growth. Mobile ARPU stabilized the last 12 months as data usage per sub more than tripled. Unicom has signed up 18 mil subs on unlimited data packages but saw little cannibalizations, which allays our previous concerns.      &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Earnings to triple in 2018&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Net profit in 1H18 was more than double 1H17, and 2H18 will look much more solid than 2H17. This will be driven not just by revenue growth but also from selling cost reductions, thanks to Unicom’s internet platform partners. Unicom is doing more with less thanks to its strategic partners.</column>
<column>Defensive with valuation support&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Looking for defensive ideas in the current turbulent market? Unicom fits the bill with an earnings turnaround and cheap valuation for downside protection. EV/EBITDA of 2.4x for 2019E is just too cheap to ignore.  Moreover, Unicom has a 21% stake in a recently listed tower company, which makes up 19% of Unicom’s current value. U/G to BUY.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>CIFI Holdings</column>
<column>7.000000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>1H18 results reaffirm our thesis that CIFI strikes a good balance between growth and profitability. Core net profit rose ~59% YoY in line with its positive profit alert announced earlier, and reached ~42% of our full-year forecast. With its quality land bank and prudent capital management we believe CIFI will stand out among peers when the operating environment becomes more difficult due to tightening in China. Maintain BUY and HKD7.00 TP, based on 40% target discount to 2018E NAV of HKD11.7/sh.</column>
<column>1H18 results solid and on target, maintain BUY  </column>
<column>1H18 results reaffirm our thesis that CIFI strikes a good balance between growth and profitability. Core net profit rose ~59% YoY, in line with its positive profit alert announced earlier, and reached ~42% of our full-year forecast. With its quality land bank and prudent capital management, we believe CIFI will stand out among peers when the operating environment becomes more difficult due to the tightening in China. CIFI is our only BUY in the sector given our 30% earnings CAGR for FY17-20E driven by its strong sales and steady margin outlook. Maintain BUY and TP of HKD7.00, based on a 40% target discount to 2018E NAV of HKD11.7/sh. Valuation is cheap, trading at ~62% discount to NAV, 1.5x SD below the 50% historical mean NAV discount.  </column>
<column>Strong contracted sales growth to meet FY18 target</column>
<column>CIFI’s 1H18 contracted sales rose ~40% YoY to CNY66b, meeting 47% of its CNY140b FY18 target. Contracted sales were largely driven by tier-2 cities (80% of total), such as Hefei (15%) and Chongqing (14%). We expect sales momentum to pick up in 2H with more saleable resources in tier-2 cities, such as Ningbo and Suzhou where tightening policies are less stringent. We maintain our FY18 contracted sales forecast and project 35% YoY growth.</column>
<column>Aggressive land banking with reasonable net gearing</column>
<column>Net gearing increased 18.1 ppt to 72% mainly due to aggressive land replenishment during 1H18, but this is still well below the 90% sector average. It entered 14 new cities and acquired 9.55m sqm GFA (+58.3% YoY, 11% via M&#38;#38;A) at an average cost of CNY6,276/sqm. We believe 1H18 offered a good land-banking window given less competition as developers faced a severe credit squeeze. The cost of the new land acquired is equivalent to only ~41% of contracted ASP in 1H18, providing sufficient buffer to maintain its target margin.   </column>
<column>Good balance between growth and profitability</column>
<column>Key highlights: 1) revenue surged ~64% YoY to CNY18.421b; 2) adjusted GM expanded to 33.7% (vs. 29.7% in FY17); 3) core profit rose ~59% YoY to CNY2.446b; and 4) declared an interim dividend of CNY6.09 cents/sh, up 40% YoY.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>CIMB Group Holdings</column>
<column>6.300000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>We have factored much of the IDR weakness into our forecasts, but any further depreciation could affect earnings translation from CIMB Niaga (Niaga) as would the risk of further rate hikes. We maintain our HOLD call on CIMB Group with an unchanged TP of MYR6.30, pegged to a FY19E PBV of 1.1x (ROE: 10%).</column>
<column>HOLD maintained</column>
<column>We have factored much of the IDR weakness into our forecasts, but any further depreciation could affect earnings translation from CIMB Niaga (Niaga) as would the risk of further rate hikes. We maintain our HOLD call on CIMB Group with an unchanged TP of MYR6.30, pegged to a FY19E PBV of 1.1x (ROE: 10%).</column>
<column>Rupiah translation weakness</column>
<column>The IDR has continued to weaken against the MYR and is now IDR3,600 versus IDR3,300 end-2017. As it stands, we had, during the latest results season, revised the average exchange rate for the year to IDR3,400 from IDR3,000 earlier on, and lowered contributions from Niaga to CIMB Group. Using IDR3,600 would cut our FY19E Niaga earnings by a further 6% and impact CIMB Group’s FY19E net profit by about -2%.</column>
<column>Further rate hikes</column>
<column>Having raised its 7-day repo rate by 100bps thus far this year, the immediate concern is of the possible need for more aggressive rate hikes by Bank Indonesia. This could be short-term negative on NIMs which run the risk of further compression, in our view. </column>
<column>Sensitivity of a 10bps cut in NIM</column>
<column>Niaga’s NIM compressed from 5.50% in 3Q17 to 5.03% in 2Q18. Our forecasts assume an average NIM of 5.02% for FY18 and 5.17% for FY19. Every 10bps cut in NIM would impact our FY19E earnings for Niaga by -4%, with a -1% impact on CIMB Group’s net profit. Currently, we expect Niaga to contribute to 19% of group earnings in FY18, 25% in FY19.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>CK Asset Holdings</column>
<column>62.800000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>CKA’s 1H18 underlying profit was largely in line with our expectation. The property business is on track and the infrastructure business contributed around 23% of total EBIT. Disposal of “The Center” likely increased CKA’s war chest for overseas expansion and its ambiguous business diversification. We believe diversification will  enlarge the NAV discount, although higher recurring income would make CKA more defensive and may boost the dividend. HOLD; shares fairly valued after est. revisions.</column>
<column>Diversification may deepen NAV discount but also increase recurring income</column>
<column>CKA’s 1H18 underlying profit was largely in line with our expectation. The property business is on track and the infrastructure business contributed around 23% of total EBIT. Disposal of “The Center” likely increased CKA’s war chest for overseas expansion and its ambiguous business diversification. We believe diversification will enlarge the NAV discount, although higher recurring income would make CKA more defensive and may boost the dividend. As such, maintain HOLD with the shares fairly valued on our revised target price, cut 6% to HKD62.8, based on an unchanged 45% NAV target discount. We lowered our 2018E NAV estimate by 6% to HKD114.1/sh to reflect risk of its exposure in the China Property market.   </column>
<column>Interim DPS raised by 12% to HKD0.47&#38;#13;</column>
<column>In 1H18, contracted sales achieved but not yet recognised were ~HKD78.4b, of which ~HKD57.7b was from HK, ~HKD17.7b from the Mainland and HKD3.0b from overseas. Recurring EBIT contribution increased by around 44% YoY to HKD7.4b, mainly due to the full-period earnings contribution from infrastructure projects. We believe the increase in recurring income could help boost dividend payout in the future, as demonstrated by the increase in interim dividend. However, until that happens, the shares price in current dividends, in our view.</column>
<column>More earnings from infrastructure business</column>
<column>Last year, CKA formed a JV with CKI (1038 HK, BUY), and CKA spent around HKD56b to acquire three infrastructure projects, including DUET, Reliance Home Comfort and Ista. In 1H18, the EBIT contribution reached HKD2.2b, or ~23% of total EBIT. We forecast CKA’s recurring EBIT in FY18E could reach ~HKD17.8b. We forecast the gross asset value (GAV) from non-property projects to reach 20% and it could be higher if CKA buys a stake in APA Group in Australia.  &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Targets to increase non-property recurring income</column>
<column>CKA is aggressively exploring buying opportunities overseas. One example is CKA formed a JV with CKI and PA (6 HK, HOLD) to propose buying APA Group (market cap: ~AUD11b). Another example is plans to buy London’s 5 Broadgate for ~GBP1b. We see the trends of expanding overseas and increasing non-property recurring income.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>CK Infrastructure</column>
<column>80.600000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>We believe the strength of CKI is to use cheap funding to acquire good quality projects and then improve operational efficiencies to deliver good returns to shareholders. This time, CKI entered into an economic benefits agreement with CKH (1 HK, Not Rated) whereby CKI will pay HKD7.2b for the cash flow stream of projects owned by CKH. Those projects are in fact CKI’s associates/JVs and already operated by CKI. We think this economic benefits agreement will increase CKI’s NAV. Reiterate BUY.</column>
<column>Positive on new income stream from the CKH deal&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We believe the strength of CKI is to use cheap funding to acquire good quality projects and then improve operational efficiencies to deliver good returns to shareholders. This time, CKI entered into an economic benefits agreement with CKH (1 HK, Not Rated) whereby CKI will pay HKD7.2b for the cash flow stream of projects owned by CKH. Those projects are in fact CKI’s associates/JVs and already operated by CKI. We think this economic benefits agreement will increase CKI’s NAV. Reiterate BUY on CKI and raise our SOTP-based TP to HKD80.6 to reflect the new income stream. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>CKI is the vehicle for infrastructure projects&#38;#13;</column>
<column>About seven years ago, CKI started to expand its overseas infrastructure portfolio for geographical diversification. Due to the limited strength of CKI’s balance sheet back then it formed a JV with CKH to acquire infrastructure projects, such as Northumbrian Water. Consolidating the minority interests in these projects makes sense as they are operated by CKI. But now we believe CKH is selling the economic benefits to CKI as CKH intends to acquire stakes of “Wind Tre S.p.A.” (telecom business in Italy). CKH is selling 90% of its economic benefits in the six projects (Fig.3) as follows: 40% being sold to CKA (1113 HK, HOLD, HKD55.95, TP HKD62.8), 30% to CKI (1038 HK, BUY) and 20% to Power Assets (6 HK, HOLD, HKD55, TPHK63). This could allow CKH to receive cash earlier to fund its stake acquisition of Wind Tre S.p.A. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Valuation for the six projects looks fair&#38;#13;</column>
<column>CKI will pay HKD7.2b to acquire 30% of the economic benefits in CKH’s stakes in the 6 projects. The net asset value of CKH’s stake in the 6 projects is ~HKD24b currently. Thus, we think HKD7.2b for CKI to acquire 30% of the economic benefits is fair. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Reiterate BUY and raise TP to  HKD80.6&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We forecast the average yield for the 6 projects will be 8% and due to the additional income from the 6 projects, we raise our FY18E and FY19E net profit slightly by 1.6% and 4.4%, respectively. We then marginally increase our TP from HKD79 to HKD80.6. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>DiGi.com</column>
<column>4.799083</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1H18 results were in line with our/consensus expectations, with revenue trends again remaining resilient. Unsurprisingly, management has raised its previously conservative 2018 revenue guidance. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged MYR4.80 TP.</column>
<column>Results in line</column>
<column>1H18 results were in line with our/consensus expectations, with revenue trends again remaining resilient. Unsurprisingly, management has raised its previously conservative 2018 revenue guidance. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged MYR4.80 TP.</column>
<column>Sequentially stable</column>
<column>Digi’s 2Q18 net profit of MYR384m (+7% YoY, stable QoQ) brings 1H18 net profit to MYR770m (+5% YoY), 52% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. 1H18 EBITDA of MYR1.5b (+5% YoY) was 51%/52% of our/consensus full-year forecasts respectively. The quarter saw Digi incurring a one-off MYR40m cost from an operating model shift (engaging an external network specialist and subsequently re-housing Digi’s in-house network staff to the vendor). This was offset by sequentially lower depreciation/amortisation charges. A second interim DPS of 4.9sen was declared, again representing c.100% payout ratio. </column>
<column>Healthy revenue trends </column>
<column>Overall, 2Q18 service revenue (pre-MFRS 15) was stable QoQ but up 2.1% YoY. Prepaid revenue continued its downtrend (-1.4% QoQ) from ongoing churn (partly pre-to-post migration). This was however offset by ongoing growth in postpaid revenue (up 0.7% QoQ) on the back of higher subscribers (+3% QoQ) amid slight ARPU contraction (-1% QoQ). EBITDA margin (pre-MFRS 15) contracted by 2.0ppt QoQ to 44.3% in 2Q18 owing to the operating model shift mentioned previously. </column>
<column>Guidance raised</column>
<column>Management has raised its 2018 guidance comprising 1) flat revenue (slight decline to flat previously), and 2) 46%-47% EBITDA margin (stable at 2017 levels of c.45% previously). This is unsurprising in our view as the previous guidance appeared conservative given Digi’s low 2017 base. Our earnings forecasts and MYR4.80 TP are unchanged. Our TP is based on a DCF assuming 6.7% WACC and 2% LT growth.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Eversendai Corp</column>
<column>1.050000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1Q18 core earnings came in below ours/consensus expectations. The oil &#38; gas segment saw recovery, reporting a small PBT of MYR1m compared to losses in 1Q17. However, this was offset by its other key segments which reported lower PBT contributions YoY. We lower FY18E earnings by 5% after adjusting for margins at the Middle East segment. Maintain HOLD with a lower TP of MYR1.05 pegged to unchanged 12x FY18 PER.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>1Q18 core earnings came in below ours/consensus expectations. The oil &#38;#38; gas segment saw recovery, reporting a small PBT of MYR1m compared to losses in 1Q17. However, this was offset by its other key segments which reported lower PBT contributions YoY. We lower FY18E earnings by 5% after adjusting for margins at the Middle East segment. Maintain HOLD with a lower TP of MYR1.05 pegged to unchanged 12x FY18 PER.</column>
<column>1Q18 core earnings flat YoY</column>
<column>Excluding a MYR8.4m unrealized forex gain and a one-off reversal of MYR3.2m for foreseeable loss, 1Q18 core net profit of MYR15m (flat YoY, -33% QoQ) met 21%/20% of ours/consensus full year estimates. YoY, its oil &#38;#38; gas division reported a recovery with a small PBT of MYR1m in 1Q18 (compared to losses of MYR5m in 1Q17; -37% QoQ), on the back of contribution from its offshore fabrication project for Saudi Aramco. However, its other key divisions of Middle East, India and Malaysia all reported weaker YoY contribution at the PBT level. </column>
<column>Lower FY18E earnings</column>
<column>EVSD has secured MYR716m of new jobs YTD FY18 (MYR534m as of end-Mar 2018), bringing its outstanding orderbook to MYR2b. We have already assumed MYR1.5b p.a. of job wins within our forecast years. Taking into account the weaker 1Q18, we lower our FY18 net profit forecast by 5% after adjusting for lower margins of 0.5ppts for its Middle East segment.</column>
<column>Balance sheet still stressed</column>
<column>Net gearing remains high at 0.94x as of end-March 2018 due to its financing of its lift boat contracts. Receivables and unbilled amount on work done also remain high at MYR1.58b due to the payment structure of its liftboats. The first liftboat is expected to be delivered to Vahana by the first week of June which could alleviate its balance sheet woes. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Gamuda</column>
<column>3.600000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>The proposed new SSP3 O&#38;M contract to Gamuda Water (GW) comes as no surprise as we have previously expected GW to retain the O&#38;M contract under the Selangor government. The letter of offer also sets out the Termination and Settlement agreement terms for the existing SSP3 O&#38;M and outstanding receivables owed by SPLASH to GW. Assuming a lower PBT contribution of MYR40m-50m p.a. from GW from the revised rates, our FY19E/FY20E earnings would be lower by ~2% for both years.</column>
<column>Maintain earnings forecasts, SOP-TP and HOLD</column>
<column>The proposed new SSP3 O&#38;#38;M contract to Gamuda Water (GW) comes as no surprise as we have previously expected GW to retain the O&#38;#38;M contract under the Selangor government. The letter of offer also sets out the Termination and Settlement agreement terms for the existing SSP3 O&#38;#38;M and outstanding receivables owed by SPLASH to GW. Assuming a lower PBT contribution of MYR40m-50m p.a. from GW from the revised rates, our FY19E/FY20E earnings would be lower by ~2% for both years. </column>
<column>Termination of existing O&#38;#38;M agreement with SPLASH</column>
<column>GW (80%-owned by Gamuda) has received a letter of offer from Air Selangor S/B setting out the termination of the existing operations and maintenance (O&#38;#38;M) agreement of the Sungai Selangor Water Treatment Plant Phase 3 (SSP 3) with SPLASH. The offer also sets out the settlement of the outstanding receivables (e.MYR700m end-June 2018) from SPLASH via a Termination and Settlement agreement to be entered between Air Selangor, SPLASH and GW. GW has until 27 Aug 2018 to accept the offer.</column>
<column>Details for payment of settlement sum&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Under the Termination and Settlement agreement, subject to completion of the SPLASH SPA, SPLASH will pay to GW under the existing SSP3 O&#38;#38;M an amount equal to 90% of the outstanding fee at a date to be mutually agreed on. The settlement of e.MYR630m (90% of the e.MYR700m SPLASH receivables) will be paid in two portions: i) an upfront payment of 10% (e.MYR63m) and ii) the balance 90% (e.MYR567m) to be settled in nine annual instalments (1st instalment a year later) plus 5.25% p.a. interest. Gamuda’s upfront portion will be e.MYR50m for its 80% stake in GW. </column>
<column>Revised rates under new O&#38;#38;M with Selangor state</column>
<column>The offer letter also proposes the execution of a new SSP3 O&#38;#38;M contract between GW and Air Selangor. Based on the Bursa announcement, the proposed bulk water supply rates under the new O&#38;#38;M agreement represent a 2sen/m3 reduction (see overleaf for details) as compared to the fees under the existing O&#38;#38;M agreement. Checks with Gamuda suggest that the PBT contribution from GW could amount to e.MYR40m-50m p.a based on the new rates. Assuming the new contribution from GW, our FY19E/FY20E Gamuda earnings would both be lower by ~2.0%.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Gas Malaysia</column>
<column>3.002193</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>GMB’s 1H18 results were in line, with volume again trending in accordance to seasonality. With a tariff surcharge already in place for 2H18, we see little downside risk to 2018 earnings. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged MYR3.00 TP. Risk-reward remains merely balanced presently.</column>
<column>Smooth sailing for now</column>
<column>GMB’s 1H18 results were in line, with volume again trending in accordance to seasonality. With a tariff surcharge already in place for 2H18, we see little downside risk to 2018 earnings. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged MYR3.00 TP. Risk-reward remains merely balanced presently.</column>
<column>Results in line</column>
<column>GMB’s 2Q18 net profit of MYR48m (+22% YoY, +20% QoQ) brings 1H18 net profit to MYR88m (+21% YoY), 51%/48% of our/consensus full-year forecasts respectively. A first interim DPS of 4.5sen (4.0sen in 2Q17) was declared, representing a DPR of 65%. GMB noted in its commentary that volume grew both YoY and QoQ (in line with seasonality). We estimate GMB’s 2Q18 spread at around c.MYR2.00/mmBTU, in line with our MYR1.95/mmBTU assumption. </column>
<column>Likely over-recovered on gas cost  </column>
<column>By our estimates, GMB again over-recovered on gas cost in 2Q18. This thus futher reduced the overall “under-recovery” position, leading to a QoQ reduction in receivables. With a tariff surcharge (MYR0.77/mmBTU) already in place for 2H18, we see little downside risk to 2018 earnings. We expect GMB to revert to a 100% DPR for 2018.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>Our earnings forecasts and MYR3.00 TP are unchanged. Our TP is derived from a sum-of-parts, with 1) the core business valued on a DCF assuming 8% WACC and 2% long-term growth, and 2) new ventures valued at 15x forward PER. Our base case remains that the IBR framework (inclusive of its pass-through mechanism) will continue. With share price having been relatively stable YTD, we see risk-reward as being merely balanced presently.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Genting Plantations</column>
<column>10.400000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>After a strong start to the year, 2Q18 results disappointed on accelerated fertilizing activities, low CPO ASP, and low FFB output. The cropping pattern changed somewhat in 1H18 but is likely to pick up strongly in 2H18. Coupled with lower fertilizing activities, we expect earnings to pick up sharply higher, especially in 4Q18. Retain BUY with an unchanged TP of MYR10.40 on unchanged 26x 2018 PER, its 5-year historical mean.</column>
<column>Looking forward to stronger 2H18</column>
<column>After a strong start to the year, 2Q18 results disappointed on accelerated fertilizing activities, low CPO ASP, and low FFB output. The cropping pattern changed somewhat in 1H18 but is likely to pick up strongly in 2H18. Coupled with lower fertilizing activities, we expect earnings to pick up sharply higher, especially in 4Q18. Retain BUY with an unchanged TP of MYR10.40 on unchanged 26x 2018 PER, its 5-year historical mean. </column>
<column>2Q core results below expectations</column>
<column>2Q18 headline net profit was MYR26m (-63% YoY, -74% QoQ). Stripping aside net FX losses of MYR8m, 2Q18 core net profit of MYR34m (-54% YoY, -62% QoQ) brings 1H18 core net profit to MYR124m (-16% YoY), which met just 39%/36% of our and consensus full-year estimates. 2Q18 earnings were dragged down by lower plantation EBITDA of MYR97m (-32% YoY, -36% QoQ) due to the unusually low FFB output growth (+5% YoY, -1% QoQ), low CPO ASP (-15% YoY, -4% QoQ), and accelerated fertilising activities. GENP has applied ~65% of its full year fertiliser requirement in 1H18 (1H17: ~47%). According to GENP, its 1H18 cost of production was 11% higher YoY at ~MYR1,800/t.</column>
<column>Growing property contribution </column>
<column>2Q18 downstream EBITDA grew 70% YoY (+982% QoQ) to MYR5m on improved biodiesel margin which offsets refinery losses. As for property, 2Q18 EBITDA slipped 28% YoY to MYR4m on lower progress billings (-12% YoY, -5% QoQ). 1H18 property sales grew 9% YoY to MYR58m while unbilled sales stood at MYR49m (+133% YoY). As for premium outlet JV, its profit contribution grew 67% YoY to MYR19m on GPO addition in 3Q17.</column>
<column>Earnings to play catch up, especially in 4Q18</column>
<column>We maintain our earnings forecasts, expecting stronger earnings in 2H18 especially in the 4Q18. This will be driven by stronger FFB output (as GENP still maintains at least 15% YoY group FFB growth target for 2018 vs MKE forecast of 20%), lower fertiliser cost and better downstream margins, to mitigate the present weak CPO ASP. GENP declared a first interim DPS of 4.75sen (1H17: 5.5sen) which will go ex- on 13 Sept 2018.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Globetronics Technology</column>
<column>2.400000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Despite 1H18 core earnings at 40% of our full-year forecast, the results are still above expectation. We expect a much stronger 2H18, fuelled by demand ramp at the sensor division in preparation for major smartphone launches in 3Q18. We raise our FY18-20 earnings forecasts by 2%-9%, on higher sensor volumes. Correspondingly, our TP is raised by 4% to MYR2.40, pegged on unchanged 18x CY19 EPS (average PER targets for tech stocks within our coverage). Maintain HOLD.</column>
<column>And, earnings to be back loaded, once again</column>
<column>Despite 1H18 core earnings at 40% of our full-year forecast, the results are still above expectation. We expect a much stronger 2H18, fuelled by demand ramp at the sensor division in preparation for major smartphone launches in 3Q18. We raise our FY18-20 earnings forecasts by 2%-9%, on higher sensor volumes. Correspondingly, our TP is raised by 4% to MYR2.40, pegged on unchanged 18x CY19 EPS (average PER targets for tech stocks within our coverage). Maintain HOLD.</column>
<column>Strong proximity, wearable, gesture sensors volume</column>
<column>2Q18 net profit of MYR9m fell by a sharper 39% QoQ (+48% YoY) than a revenue contraction of 17% QoQ as operating margin shrank by 4.6ppts QoQ. While a weaker QoQ 2Q18 was expected due to softer shipment for GTB’s light sensors (inventory rationalisation by a North American smartphone brand), we were pleasantly surprised by stronger-than-expected volumes for GTB’s proximity, wearable and gesture sensors. Alongside volume recovery for light sensors in preparation for major smartphone launches due out in Sep 2018, we expect GTB’s sensor revenue to pick up strongly from early 3Q18 onwards. </column>
<column>Raising FY18/19/20E earnings by 9%/4%/2%</column>
<column>We make upward adjustments in our proximity and wearable sensor volumes to incorporate strong 1H18 volume shipments. Besides that, we also raise our gesture sensor volumes, incorporating capacity expansion undertaken by GTB as required by its key sensor client, ams AG (AMS SW, Not-rated). From these adjustments (refer to Fig 4), we now expect GTB’s 2H18 earnings to jump by 63%-83% HoH to ~MYR40m-45m; recall that 2H17 earnings surged 2.7x HoH to MYR39m.</column>
<column>Valuations are fair</column>
<column>Despite our earnings upgrades, risk-to-reward for GTB remains balanced at 19x CY19 PER (18x ex-net cash of MYR96m as at end June 2018). Future catalyst  may come from mass adoption of new sensors by its key client or breakthrough in laser technology for automotive lighting.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Goodbaby International</column>
<column>4.300000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain BUY despite lowering est.’s and TP by 38% after the 1H18 earnings miss. The disruption to gb’s durable sales in China in 1H18 was caused by business integration delays and the bankruptcy of Toys ”R” Us but sales should normalise from 2H18 onwards. We cut FY18/19/20F core net profit by 38%/36%/35% due to lower margin assumptions on a lower FY18 base, and assuming slower-than-expected integration progress and additional opex. Our TP is based on an unchanged 20x FY18F PER (peer’s avg.).</column>
<column>1H18 missed on integration execution; Est.’s cut</column>
<column>Maintain BUY despite lowering estimates (Fig. 6) and our TP by 38% to HKD4.30 after the 1H18 earnings miss. The disruption to gb’s durable sales in China in 1H18 was caused by business integration delays and the bankruptcy of Toys ”R” Us but we expect sales should normalise from 2H18 onwards. We cut our FY18/19/20F core net profit by 38%/36%/35% due to lower margin assumptions on a lower FY18 base, and assuming slower-than-expected integration progress and additional opex. Our TP is based on an unchanged target 20x FY18F PER, in line with peer’s avg.</column>
<column>The good: CYBEX, new gb business, and ‘blue chips’ </column>
<column>CYBEX remains a sweet spot as sales grew strongly in all regions. We expect this trend to continue with new products in new categories given the strong new product pipeline, which will entrench its premium lifestyle brand positioning. Similarly, gb’s new non-durable goods sales also grew strongly in 1H18. For its blue-chips business, sales growth resumed in 1H18 demonstrating it can increase OEM/ODM sales at the same time it grows self-owned brands using its R&#38;#38;D edge.</column>
<column>The bad: fall in China durable sales, US operations</column>
<column>In China, 1H18 sales of gb’s juvenile product durables plunged 17% YoY because of the disruption to operations from the integration of the newly acquired non-durable business. Nonetheless, we believe these problems will pass and sales should start to recover from 2H18 onwards. In the US, the bankruptcy of Toys “R” Us impacted Evenflo and gb’s other toy sales, which hurt profitability given the channel’s high margins. That said, we expect the impact to abate as the company increases its presence in other channels with repositioned brands and products. </column>
<column>Short-term pain for long-term gain</column>
<column>Pro-forma non-GAAP revenue and operating margin rose by just 6% YoY in 1H18 due to a temporary change in segment mix, negative segment operating leverage, and CNY appreciation. But we believe GB can structurally improve its profitability considering its vertical business model, global supply chain and diversified brand portfolio.  </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Greentown China</column>
<column>7.300000</column>
<column>Sell</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Our SELL thesis is based on Greentown’s structural risks from its high exposure to third tier cities and high construction costs. We believe such risk will manifest through weaker contracted sales and inferior margins relative to peers. The company’s 1H18 results showed early signs that reinforce our concerns: it was one of the few Chinese developers that saw a GPM decline and weak contracted sales growth. Maintain SELL with TP cut 6% to HKD7.30 based on an unchanged 60% NAV discount. </column>
<column>Focus on margin decline not earnings beat; TP -6% </column>
<column>Our SELL thesis is based on Greentown’s structural risks related to its high exposure to third tier cities and high construction costs. We believe such risk will manifest through weaker contracted sales and inferior margins relative to peers. The company’s 1H18 results showed early signs that reinforce our concerns. Greentown was one of the few Chinese developers that saw a GPM decline in 1H18 (-1.5ppts YoY) and contracted sales rose only ~8% YoY. These validate our thesis that sluggish pre-sales growth and weak profit margins are key negative drivers for the stock. We would ignore the earnings beat as it was mainly due to stronger project bookings and disposal gains. Greentown has shown its vulnerability during all three property market downcycles since 2008. Maintain SELL and cut TP 6.4% to HKD7.3, based on an unchanged 60% target NAV discount. We lower our 2018E NAV estimate by 6.4% to HKD18.2 to reflect lower GPM and rising gearing concerns.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Contracted sales to miss FY18E target&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Greentown locked in only ~43% of its annual sales target of CNY110b in 1H18. We expect contracted sales to fall 8% YoY in FY18E to CNY95b, ~14% below its FY target as we expect slower momentum in 2H due to rising policy risks in tier-3 cities. Greentown has the highest exposure to tier-3 cities (~53% of its total land bank) within our coverage.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>GPM to remain under pressure in FY18-20E &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Greentown’s GPM declined further to only 18.1% in 1H18 (vs. 19.2% in 2017) mainly due to the acquisition of Jinan Yulan Garden. We expect GPM to remain well below the sector average at 18.4%/18.1% in 2018E/19E due to: 1) inactive land bank replenishment through M&#38;#38;A (25%) as land banking via M&#38;#38;A tends to be cheaper, and rising land cost-to-ASP ratio (41%); and 2) structural weakness from high construction cost due to its focus on high-end properties.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Excessive valuation plus low dividend yield&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Greentown’s payout ratio is only 15% of core profits, much lower than the 30% sector average. It’s also trading at 0.3 SD above its 62% historical mean NAV discount, which looks excessive considering its dividend yield should stay below ~3% for FY19-20E, significantly lower than the 5-6% market average. In addition, unlike other developers, it has no share buyback plans.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Guangzhou R&#38;F Properties</column>
<column>11.000000</column>
<column>Sell</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>GZ R&#38;F 1H18 earnings were in line with our expectation. Maintain SELL on R&#38;F as we believe it has greater refinancing pressure so we expect it will expedite contract sales at the expense of margins. We also are concerned about its exposure in Tier-3 cities as we expect more tightening measures. R&#38;F risks missing its full-year contracted sales target. Maintain NAV-based TP of HKD11 (60% discount to NAV). </column>
<column>1H18 in line, but balance sheet remains under pressure</column>
<column>GZ R&#38;#38;F 1H18 earnings were in line with our expectation. Maintain SELL on R&#38;#38;F as we believe it has greater refinancing pressure so we expect it will expedite contract sales at the expense of margins. We also are concerned about its exposure in Tier-3 cities as we expect more tightening measures. R&#38;#38;F risks missing its full-year contracted sales target. Maintain NAV-based TP of HKD11 (60% discount to NAV). </column>
<column>We worry it may miss its full-year sales target</column>
<column>1H18 core net profit increased by 156% YoY to CNY4.12b, in line with our expectation. The FY18E contracted sales target was unchanged at CNY130b, whilst it has achieved CNY57b in 1H18 (44% of the full-year target). The overall gross margin increased by 2.3ppt to 38.5%. However, we forecast the gross margin will drop to ~30% in 2019E as we expect it will speed up contract sales at the expense of margins. Interim DPS was CNY0.4, up 21% YoY.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Re-financing risk remains </column>
<column>We estimate R&#38;#38;F’s net gearing was 191% at end-1H18 with total short-term debt of CNY45b, up 58% YoY. The high net gearing and huge short-term debts are our concerns due to its re-financing risk. We forecast net gearing by end-2018 will be 151%. R&#38;#38;F’s effective cost of borrowing was 5.62% in 1H18 compared to 5.12% in FY17.</column>
<column>Asset quality is not good enough&#38;#13;</column>
<column>R&#38;#38;F has one of the largest exposures to Tier-3 cities among Chinese developers. We estimate around 50% of R&#38;#38;F’s total GFA is in Tier-3 cities.  We believe property prices in Tier-3 cities are vulnerable to decline by 5% in FY18E as we expect further tightening measures.  In our sensitivity analysis, for every 10% drop in property prices in Tier-3 cities, we estimate R&#38;#38;F’s net profit will decline by 8.7% in FY18E and NAV will fall by 10.3%. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Health &#38; Happiness Int'l</column>
<column>69.400000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Reiterate BUY. Strong 1H18 results and increased sales guidance reinforce our conviction of H&#38;H’s two-pronged structural growth story (i.e. adult &#38; baby nutrition and care products). Although EBITDA margin guidance was unchanged, we believe the increased brand building and channel investment will lay a more solid foundation to support multi-year growth. Our bullish projections are unchanged with TP based on SOTP (25x FY18F P/E for BNC and 15x FY18F EV/EBITDA for ANC).</column>
<column>More upbeat sales guidance reinforces BUY thesis</column>
<column>Reiterate BUY. The strong 1H18 results and increased sales guidance (Fig.1) reinforce our conviction towards H&#38;#38;H’s two-pronged structural growth story (i.e. adult &#38;#38; baby nutrition and care products). Although EBITDA margin guidance was unchanged, we believe the increased brand building and channel investment will lay a more solid foundation to support multi-year growth. Our bullish projections are unchanged as we believe they already adequately factor in the latest trend. Our TP is based on SOTP (25x FY18F P/E for BNC and 15x FY18F EV/EBITDA for ANC).</column>
<column>BNC: IMF solid, but it is more than just an IMF story</column>
<column>We believe H&#38;#38;H’s competitive advantage in the baby nutrition &#38;#38; care (BNC) space has been further entrenched as: i) it gained market share in the infant milk formula (IMF) category through both its core brand and organic formula; and ii) positive customer feedback and growing market presence of its probiotics and other paediatric care products. As it has a good reputation in the premium IMF market and strong access to the infant-store channel, we believe it can cross-sell more products to its customers.</column>
<column>ANC: exciting launch pipeline</column>
<column>Sales of adult nutrition &#38;#38; care (ANC) products (i.e., Swisse Wellness) rebounded in 2Q following the price hikes in 1Q. In Australia, Swisse held on to the No.1 position and gained further market share. In China, Swisse retained the No.1 spot in the online category. Overall, growth in ANC sales in China was encouraging, helped by collaborations with e-commerce platforms and a growing presence in the offline market. As it secured CFDA approval, it can enrich its offline product offerings, e.g., its “Calcium + Vitamin D” has received the blue-hat label. In 2H18, new product launches will include probiotics for adults, and pregnancy and infant products. </column>
<column>Deleveraging and “de-risking” </column>
<column>H&#38;#38;H’s cash-flow conversion and deleveraging were satisfactory in 1H18. AR/AP days were stable YoY, while inventory days normalised from abnormally low levels in 1H17. On a separate note, H&#38;#38;H is steadily reducing its FX risks through various initiatives (e.g., reducing net FX exposure mismatch and hedging USD debt). This should help reduce the drag on reported numbers should FX volatility worsen. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Henderson Land Development</column>
<column>59.359977</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>1H18 results were in line with our expectations. Solid recurring income and contracted sales should continue to support the healthy balance sheet and give HDL flexibility to recycle capital and accumulate more quality land, such as the two sites at Kai Tak. It has the largest amount of farm land among peer that could provide  further upside potential to its overall asset quality as we expect the government will speed up farm land conversion. Maintain BUY and TP of HKD59.36 (30% NAV discount).</column>
<column>Catalysts: capital recycling and farm land&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1H18 results were in line with our expectations. Solid recurring income and contracted sales should continue to support the healthy balance sheet and give HDL the flexibility to recycle capital and accumulate more quality land, such as the two sites at Kai Tak. It has the largest amount of farm land among peers, providing further upside potential to its overall asset quality as we expect the government will speed up farm land conversion. Maintain BUY and NAV-based TP of HKD59.36 (30% discount to NAV).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Solid 1H17 results, interim DPS up 4% YoY</column>
<column>1H18 underlying profit was HKD13.859b, up ~52% YoY, mainly due to ~72% YoY increase in property sales and a HKD6.255b gain from the disposal of investment properties. HK &#38;#38; China Gas (3 HK, Not Rated) contributed HKD1.99b in profit to HDL, up ~7% YoY. Net rental income in HK rose ~5% YoY to HKD2.785b. We think recurring income can help support dividend payouts; the 1H18 dividend was HKD0.5, up 4% YoY. Based on our calculation, HDL had 49 projects as at end-1H18 in which it has 80% ownership or above. These give HDL a total attributable GFA of ~4.4m sq.ft. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Improved land bank quality&#38;#13;</column>
<column>HDL sold the office building at 18 King Wah Road in North Point and a site in Tuen Mun Town for HKD17b. HDL bought two quality sites at Kai Tak  for ~HKD16b (HKD14,900/sq.ft.) in Feb’18. Redevelopment of the Kai Tak area could help increase the capital value of these two sites, in our view. In fact, three months earlier SHKP (16 HK, BUY) paid ~HKD25b (HKD17,800/sq.ft) for a site in Kai Tak. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Largest amount of farm land, our Top Pick&#38;#13;</column>
<column>HDL owns 45.3m sq.ft of farm land, the most among peers. We expect the government will speed up farm-land conversion and will probably use the co-development format (i.e. developers and government) to increase land supply in HK. It could help unlock the value of the farm land, which we have valued only at cost of about HKD500/sq.ft. We expect farm-land conversion will be the catalyst to the stock. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Hengan International</column>
<column>99.700000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Reiterate BUY. Hengan’s strong 1H revenue growth and decent OPEX savings helped fully offset higher input costs, reinforcing our belief that adoption of the small-teams sales model can increase sales and cost efficiencies. Near term catalysts: i) further ASP increases; and ii) further cost-efficiency gains. Our forecasts are unchanged but TP lowered 7% to factor in weaker CNY pegged to a target 25x 2018F P/E (unchanged), 1SD above its 22x historical avg. to reflect accelerating EPS growth.</column>
<column>Small-team approach; Re-rating story still playing out </column>
<column>Reiterate BUY. Hengan’s strong 1H revenue growth and decent OPEX savings helped to fully offset higher input costs, reinforcing our belief that adoption of the small-teams sales model can increase sales and cost efficiencies. We see near-term catalysts: i) further ASP increases following the hike in Jun-18; and ii) further cost-efficiency gains from rolling out the small-teams model firm-wide. Our forecasts are unchanged but TP lowered 7% to factor in weaker CNY pegged to a target 25x 2018F P/E (unchanged), 1SD above its 22x historical average to reflect accelerating EPS growth prospects. The shares are undervalued at 2SD below historical average PER with 4% dividend yield. </column>
<column>Double-digit revenue growth; e-commerce picking up </column>
<column>During 1H18, revenue grew by double digits, the first since 2013 due to improvement across all product offerings and channels. Management is now targeting to achieve a double-digit revenue CAGR in 3-5 years. E-commerce sales grew &#38;#62;60% YoY in 1H and made up 13% of total sales (1H17: 9%); the profitability of this channel has substantially improved. We also believe continually introducing better quality products has helped it stay relevant with consumers. Adding new categories and broadening its target customer base also helped to boost sales (e.g., it launched a new line to cater to white-collar women). On top of that, Hengan is extending its female hygiene care product offerings to beyond just sanitary napkins. </column>
<column>More upside in 2H18 </column>
<column>Hengan raised the ASP of its low-margin tissue products by 3-5% in Jun-18. The company expects further ASP increases in 2H18 as its products are still competitively priced against peers. As such, we expect it to replicate peer Vinda’s (3331 HK, HOLD, TP HKD15.6) positive GPM trajectory, as Vinda started to raise prices in 4Q17. Further, we expect additional opex savings from 2H18 onwards as it will start operating with small teams in different areas. Existing teams are expected to perform better, as half of the teams achieved their KPI (1H17 &#38;#60;20%) and the ratio is expected to improve to 80%.</column>
<column>Future upside and benefits from recent investments</column>
<column>Although revenue contributions from earlier acquisitions are insignificant, Hengan has gained both new product categories and international market exposure. We believe this allows it to look for new revenue streams and strengthens its leadership in the household &#38;#38; personal care market. Overall, we believe these investments will safeguard its multi-year development. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Hock Seng Lee</column>
<column>1.450000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>2Q18 results were below ours/consensus expectations on slower-than-expected progress billing at the construction segment. Our earnings for FY18E-FY20E are cut by 5%-15% after revising down our target job win for FY18E/FY19E. Outstanding orderbook of e.MYR2.5b should provide for near-term earnings visibility but timing of earnings recognition remains uncertain. Maintain HOLD with a slightly higher TP of MYR1.45 (rounded) after rolling forward valuations to mid-FY19.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>2Q18 results were below ours/consensus expectations on slower-than-expected progress billing at the construction segment. Our earnings for FY18E-FY20E are cut by 5%-15% after revising down our target job win for FY18E/FY19E. Outstanding orderbook of e.MYR2.5b should provide for near-term earnings visibility but timing of earnings recognition remains uncertain. Maintain HOLD with a slightly higher TP of MYR1.45 (rounded) after rolling forward valuations to mid-FY19.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Construction continues to see YoY growth</column>
<column>2Q18 net profit of MYR14m (+44 YoY, +3% QoQ) brought 1H18 net profit to MYR28m (+33% YoY), meeting 45%/43% of ours/consensus full-year forecasts. The shortfall against our forecast is due to the slower-than-expected construction progress. That said, the segment continues to see strong YoY growth, reporting an EBIT of MYR13m (+95% YoY, flat QoQ) in 2Q18, on the back of higher works recognition (+135% YoY, +21% QoQ) at major projects. Physical completion at its Pan Borneo Sarawak Highway Package 7 and the Miri Wastewater Project (Phase 1) stands at 30% and 18% respectively (from 25% and 15% as of end-Apr 2018). &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Stable from property&#38;#13;</column>
<column>YoY, property EBIT contracted by 6% (+4% QoQ) to MYR6m due to slower progress billing (-7% YoY, -11% QoQ) which is attributed to the timing of sales recognized in 2Q18. EBIT margin for the segment however remained relatively stable at 36.0% (+0.5ppts YoY, +5.1ppts QoQ). YTD FY18, HSL has launched MYR50m of new property projects comprising i) the gated residences for Phase 2 of Precint Luxe and ii) industrial lots at Phase 3 of its Vista Industrial Park (VIP).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Revising job win assumptions&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Having secured e.MYR101m of jobs YTD FY18, we believe our target of MYR500m for FY18 is a tall order with four months of the year remaining. Taking into account the change in landscape within the construction industry and on-going review of construction jobs, we revise down our FY18E/FY19E job win assumption by MYR200m/MYR300m to MYR300m/MYR500m respectively. Subsequently, our FY18E/FY19E/FY20E earnings are cut by 5%/11%/15% respectively. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Hong Leong Bank</column>
<column>19.450000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>HL Bank ended FY18 on a decent note, with core net profit up 14% YoY. Fundamentals remain impeccable and much as we like HL Bank, HLFG still provides cheaper entry to both the bank and insurance divisions of the HL group. Our forecasts are broadly maintained but our TP is raised marginally to MYR19.45 (+70sen) on an unchanged CY19E PBV multiple of 1.5x (ROE: 11% vs 10.9% previously). HOLD.</column>
<column>Cheaper exposure via HLFG</column>
<column>HL Bank ended FY18 on a decent note, with core net profit up 14% YoY. Fundamentals remain impeccable and much as we like HL Bank, HLFG still provides cheaper entry to both the bank and insurance divisions of the HL group. Our forecasts are broadly maintained but our TP is raised marginally to MYR19.45 (+70sen) on an unchanged CY19E PBV multiple of 1.5x (ROE: 11% vs 10.9% previously). HOLD.</column>
<column>Within expectations</column>
<column>HL Bank’s 4QFY18 core net profit of MYR626m (+7% YoY, +0.6% QoQ) took FY18 core net profit to MYR2.57b (+14% YoY). This was within expectations at 102% of our full-year forecast and consensus, respectively. Positives include NOII expansion, positive JAWS and very benign credit costs, which offset the slow growth in lending (+3% YoY) and NIM compression (-7bps QoQ). Bank of Chengdu continues to be a major contributor at 15% of group earnings in FY18, with profit contribution up a strong 47% YoY, primarily on lower credit costs. </column>
<column>Targets for FY19</column>
<column>Management’s targets for FY19 include the following: i) loan growth in line with industry (MKE: 3.5%), ii) NIM &#38;#62;2% (MKE: 2.02%); iii) CIR &#38;#60; 43% (MKE: 42.6%), iv) GIL &#38;#60; 1% (MKE: 0.9%) and v) ROE ~11% (MKE: 11%).</column>
<column>Manageable MFRS9 impact</column>
<column>HL Bank’s capital ratios remain comfortable with CET1 ratios of 12.6% and 11.9% at the group and bank entity respectively. The group’s preliminary assessment is of a 25% increase in allowances on Day 1 implementation of MFRS9 on 1 July 2018, with a manageable 13bps impact and a 4bps impact on total capital, which is manageable.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Hong Leong Financial Group</column>
<column>21.200000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>HLFG’s FY18 results were within expectations and we maintain our forecasts. At current prices, HLFG’s market cap of MYR21.3b is a large 20% discount to its share of HL Bank’s market cap i.e. MYR26.7b. On updating our RNAV computation, our SOP-derived TP is raised to MYR21.20 from MYR20.80. We continue to prefer HLFG as a cheaper exposure to HL Bank – BUY.</column>
<column>Raising SOP-derived TP to MYR21.20</column>
<column>HLFG’s FY18 results were within expectations and we maintain our forecasts. At current prices, HLFG’s market cap of MYR21.3b is a large 20% discount to its share of HL Bank’s market cap i.e. MYR26.7b. On updating our RNAV computation, our SOP-derived TP is raised to MYR21.20 from MYR20.80. We continue to prefer HLFG as a cheaper exposure to HL Bank – BUY.</column>
<column>FY18 results within expectations</column>
<column>HLFG’s 4QFY18 core net profit of MYR454m (+26% YoY, +5% QoQ) took FY18 core net profit to MYR1.84b (+14% YoY), which was within expectations. HL Bank accounted for 91% of group earnings, with insurance and investment banking making up the balance.</column>
<column>Decent showing by HL Bank </column>
<column>HL Bank’s 4QFY18 core net profit of MYR626m (+7% YoY, +0.6% QoQ) took FY18 core net profit to MYR2.57b (+14% YoY). Positives include NOII expansion, positive JAWS and very benign credit costs, which offset the slow growth in lending (+3% YoY) and NIM compression (-7bps QoQ). 18%-owned Bank of Chengdu continues to be a major contributor at 15% of group earnings in FY18, with profit contribution up a strong 47% YoY, primarily on lower credit costs. </column>
<column>Fast growth in HLA’s NBEV</column>
<column>70%-owned HLA saw reported pretax profit growth of just 3% YoY. However, excluding a one-off adjustment of MYR59m relating to a cut in the bonus payments on some of its products, pretax profit would have expanded 20% YoY. What is positive is that New Business Embedded Value (NBEV) expanded at a rapid rate of 24% YoY and management targets growth of &#38;#62;20% p.a, over the next three years. This is expected to be driven predominantly by the strong growth in higher value Investment Linked products, which saw premium growth of 27% YoY in FY18.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Hualan Biological Engin.</column>
<column>38.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Hualan reported respectable 1H18 results that suggests it is adapting well to the market environment but short of signalling a turnaround that we had hoped for. 1H18 revenue increased 18.6% but was 5% below our estimate and earnings met our estimate. There was no indication of improvement in end-user demand. We lower our estimates for Hualan but increase our DCF-based TP to CNY38 to reflect its lower working capital levels, improved EBIT margin and stronger selling capability. Maintain HOLD.</column>
<column>Affirm HOLD; increase TP 23% to CNY38</column>
<column>Hualan reported respectable 1H18 results that suggest it is adapting well to the market environment but short of suggesting an immediate turnaround that we had hoped for. 1H18 revenue increased 18.6% YoY to CNY1.2b but was 5% below our estimate of CNY1.3b, and earnings met our estimate. There was no indication of improvement in end-user demand but Hualan’s new direct sales force appears to be paying dividends. We lower our estimates for Hualan, but increase our DCF-based TP to CNY38 (WACC 9.61%, LTG 4%) to reflect  lower working capital requirement, as well as improved margins due to greater efficiencies and stronger selling capability. With the shares fairly valued on our revised estimates, we maintain HOLD. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>ASPs soft, product mix too niche&#38;#13;</column>
<column>ASPs declined or stayed flat for all key products putting pressure on revenue. IVIg sales declined by 16.9% indicating a 14% volume drop and 3% ASP drop. Sales of coagulation factors and hyper-immune Igs were strong, growing 93% YoY, with the former driven by strong demand, something that we would like to see in all product categories. However, we are weary that the product mix has become rather niche.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Balance sheet improved, strong cash flow</column>
<column>Hualan is managing its balance sheet well. The all-important finished goods (FG) inventory decreased from CNY335.4m (113 days of sales) at 1Q18 to CNY267.6m (93 days) at EO 1H18, a healthy level. Accounts receivables also decreased from 163 days at 1Q18 to 134 days at 1H18. CFFO for 1H18 was CNY381.7m, the strongest in years. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Hualan is managing its balance sheet well. The all-important finished goods (FG) inventory decreased from CNY335.4m (113 days of sales) at 1Q18 to CNY267.6m (93 days) at EO 1H18, a healthy level. Accounts receivables also decreased from 163 days at 1Q18 to 134 days at 1H18. CFFO for 1H18 was CNY381.7m, the strongest in years. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Hualan responded to the policy-driven curb in demand by building a direct sales force to compensate for its over-reliance on the distribution channel. This is the right thing to do but initially increased selling expenses to 15.5% in 2H17, hurting margins. Selling expense has by now stabilized to c.7% of sales with the number of reps stable at c.200 and some reps cross-selling both plasma and vaccine products, providing cost efficiency. This is a key factor in the improved margins in our new estimates.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Huaneng Renewables Corp</column>
<column>3.800000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>HNR’s 1H18 results were in line with our expectations. Robust earnings growth supports our view that a strong recovery in utilisation hours will further drive positive results going forward. Supported by government measures, such as guaranteed utilisation hours and the lifting of red-alert policies, we expect curtailment rates will decline further and remain at a low level. Maintain BUY and DCF-based TP of HKD3.80 (WACC 9% and LTG 3%).</column>
<column>Generation to drive profits; BUY </column>
<column>HNR’s 1H18 results were in line with our expectations. Robust earnings growth supports our view that a strong recovery in utilisation hours will further drive positive results going forward. Supported by government measures, such as guaranteed utilisation hours and the lifting of red-alert policies, we expect curtailment rates will decline further and remain at a low level. Maintain BUY and DCF-based TP of HKD3.80 (WACC 9% and LTG 3%). &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Wind power utilisation hours rose 11% YoY&#38;#13;</column>
<column>In 1H18, HNR’s revenue increased 12.5% YoY to CNY6,318m, mainly driven by the 14.8% YoY growth in wind power generation. Due to the robust growth in revenue, net profit was CNY2,349m, up 15.6% YoY. HNR’s wind power utilisation reached 1,229 hours in 1H18, up 11% YoY. The national curtailment ratio dropped to 9% overall in 1H18 from 14% in 1H17 (12% for all of 2017), and we expect this trend to continue in 2H18, which will help increase HNR’s utilisation hours.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Policies may help more&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We estimate 54.7% of HNR’s total wind capacity is in Zone 4, the highest among peers. Zone 4 regions are more profitable due to higher subsidies and minimal curtailment rates. But that means uncertainties about subsidies will also affect HNR more. However, we believe the government’s recently launched consultation will help ease such concerns. According to m.bjx.com.cn, the government mentioned during a consultation meeting that the feed-in subsidy of existing wind farms could be unchanged for 20 years. The news report added that if generation exceeds the guaranteed utilisation hours, wind producers could issue and sell green certificates as compensation, whereas any shortfalls compared to the feed-in subsidy could still be collected from the Renewable Energy Fund. If this proposal is confirmed, it could remove policy overhang and improve the cash flows of wind farms, in our view.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Maintain BUY; Attractively valued&#38;#13;</column>
<column>HNR is trading at 0.9x FY18E P/B and 6.4x FY18E P/E, both below the 6-year historical means. Catalysts are additional favourable environmental policies, further improvement in utilisation hours driven by UHV lines, and lower curtailment rates. Maintain BUY with unchanged TP of HKD3.80.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Hutchison China MediTech</column>
<column>45.000000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Fruquintinib, née Elunate, received CFDA marketing approval today for colorectal cancer as expected.  Fruq is the first approval on HCM’s innovative platform and marks the first oncology drug discovered &#38; developed in China, validating HCM’s capabilities in discovery, clinical development and business development. HCM is expected to book revenue from fruq in 4Q. We reiterate peak revenue estimate of USD1.1b (for LLY) and c.USD222m for HCM in royalty income. Affirm BUY and SOTP-based TP of USD45</column>
<column>Affirm BUY and USD45 TP</column>
<column>Fruquintinib, née Elunate® (爱优特®), received CFDA marketing approval today as a monotherapy for the treatment of metastatic colorectal cancer (mCRC), just as we expected.  Fruq is the first approved drug on HCM’s innovative platform and marks the first oncology drug discovered and developed in China. This is an important catalyst as this approval now establishes HCM’s creditability in discovery, clinical development and business development. HCM could start recording revenues as early as this November when its partner Lilly (LLY US, NR) is expected to launch fruq in China. Furthermore, the probability fruq’s regulatory approval in other indications (lung and gastric cancers) increases given the regulator’s familiarity of the drug and presumed safety data. Given this development, we are more confident of our peak revenue estimate of USD1.1b (for LLY) and c.USD222m for HCM in royalty income (Sec.3.5 of our initiation). Reiterate BUY and SOTP-based TP of USD45.</column>
<column>Approval triggers a development milestone payment&#38;#13;</column>
<column>The CFDA approved fruq for 3L mCRC patients who have progressed after prior fluropyrimidine, oxaliplatin and irinotecan-based chemotherapies with or without prior anti-VEGF (bevacizumab) or anti-EGFR (RAS wild type) (cetuximab) regimens (Fig 10 of our initiation). LLY will pay HCM USD13.6m as a milestone for this approval and HCM will receive 15-20% of sales as part of the royalty income. Fruq will go head-to-head with Bayer’s (BAYN GR, NR) Stivarga (regorafenib) in CRC. </column>
<column>Fruq has strongest clinical profile in China</column>
<column>As discussed in our 14 May note, fruquintinib has the best clinical profile among Chinese VEGFR inhibitors. The other two - apatinib from Hengrui (600276 CH, NR) indicated for gastric cancer and anlotinib from Sino Biopharm (1177 HK, NR) for NSCLC - are in-licensed from the US biotech company, AdvanChen. Apatinib and anlotinib are expected to generate sales of CNY2.4b (USD351m) and CNY900m (USD132m, for seven months) respectively in 2018. Lenvima (lenvatinib) from Eisai (4523 JP, NR) is also expected to enter China for liver cancers in 2018/19. We await real-world evidence of their effectiveness.</column>
<column>ASPs &#38;#38; Reimbursement</column>
<column>HCM and LLY are mum on their pricing as they expect to negotiate prices with the Chinese government for inclusion in the reimbursement formulary (NRDL). This will be key to the drug’s commercial success.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>IJM Corporation </column>
<column>2.100000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>IJM’s latest job win positively boosts its outstanding orderbook to e.MYR9.3b, further enhancing its medium-long term earnings visibility. No change to our earnings forecasts having imputed for job win potentials. Earnings downside could come from the review of its KVLRT 3 underground package and the on-going cost review of KVMRT 2. This is, however, priced in to an extent, we believe, with the weakness in its share price. Our unchanged MYR2.10 TP is SOP-based.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>IJM’s latest job win positively boosts its outstanding orderbook to e.MYR9.3b, further enhancing its medium-long term earnings visibility. No change to our earnings forecasts having imputed for job win potentials. Earnings downside could come from the review of its KVLRT 3 underground package and the on-going cost review of KVMRT 2. This is, however, priced in to an extent, we believe, with the weakness in its share price. Our unchanged MYR2.10 TP is SOP-based.</column>
<column>Secures office building job</column>
<column>IJM Construction S/B, a 100%-subsidiary, had on 4 Sept 2018 accepted an award from Affin Bank Bhd (Not Listed) for the construction of the superstructure works of a proposed 47-storey office building (Package 4 – Main Building Work) at the Tun Razak Exchange (TRX) for a total value of MYR505m. The construction period is for 26 months with expected completion by 4Q20.</column>
<column>Orderbook at e.MYR9.3b</column>
<column>The job win is IJM’s first announced job win of FY3/19, lifting its outstanding orderbook to e.MYR9.3b (based on outstanding orderbook of MYR8.8b as of end-June 2018). Assuming an 8% pretax margin, we estimate a net profit contribution of MYR31m (0.85sen EPS) over the construction period into FY21. We make no change to our earnings forecasts having imputed for MYR1b of new contracts in FY19E.</column>
<column>MYR2b job win target for FY19</column>
<column>IJM has set an internal target to achieve MYR2b of job wins for FY19. We believe this would likely come from other building jobs.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Inari Amertron</column>
<column>2.580000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>Broadcom’s Wireless division is expected to see a temporary single-digit earnings contraction in the coming year. Nonetheless, with 5G network on the horizon, Broadcom is expecting double-digit growth to return for its Wireless division from FYE10/20 onwards. We lower Inari’s FYE/619 net profit forecasts by 6% on lower RF revenue est.; FY20/21 forecasts remain. Our new TP is MYR2.58 (-3%) on an unchanged 22x CY19 EPS (+2SD). BUY.</column>
<column>Strong forward prospects from 5G adoption</column>
<column>The release of Broadcom’s results last night came with guidance for its Wireless division (anchor for Inari’s RF division); the Wireless division is expected to see a temporary single-digit earnings contraction in the coming year due to lack of RF upgrades in the North American smartphone launches in 2018. Nonetheless, with 5G network on the horizon, Broadcom is expecting annual platform upgrade to resume in 2019’s smartphones and double-digit growth to return for its Wireless division from FYE10/20 onwards. We lower Inari’s FYE/619 net profit forecasts by 6% on lower RF revenue est.; FY20/21 forecasts remain. Our new TP is MYR2.58 (-3%) on an unchanged 22x CY19 EPS (+2SD). BUY.</column>
<column>Revising RF rev forecast, positive sales mix change</column>
<column>For Inari, we now project only a 6% YoY revenue growth in the RF division in FY19 (+18% previously). This brings our overall revenue growth forecasts to MYR1.57b (+14% YoY)/ MYR1.91b (+22% YoY)/ MYR2.15b (+13% YoY) for FY19/20/21; -8%/-7%/-5% from previous forecasts. However, the change in sales mix (i.e. high-margin components such as fibre chip, mixed-signal traffic controller, IR LED) should lift group margins going forward.</column>
<column>Margins expected to expand</column>
<column>Recall that margin expansion for Inari in the recent two years (core NPM improved from 14.9% in FY16 to 17.5% in FY17, to 20.5% in FY18), were mainly driven by contribution of new subsidiaries (i.e. ISL, IIS, IOT). A reverse calculation of the margins at Inari’s Malaysian ops based on tax expense incurred by Inari implies to us that Inari has yet to apply/activate its entitled pioneer status for the new subsidiaries. Alongside better sales mix ahead, activation of pioneer status for these new subsidiaries would further enhance margins. We now expect Inari’s NPM to improve to 21.6%/23.4%/23.3% in FY19/20/21, from 21.1%/21.9%/22.1% previously. </column>
<column>Further indication for 5G adoption</column>
<column>Broadcom’s results and forward guidance of its Wired and Enterprise Storage divisions reaffirm our optimism of an imminent 5G adoption albeit on a small scale at the initial stage; we believe that 5G components will start to feature in 2019 smartphones and on a much larger scale in 2020. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>IOI Corporation</column>
<column>4.760000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>4QFY6/18 core earnings disappointed on lower-than-expected plantation contribution. Overall FY6/18 core earnings posted a decent 7% YoY growth. We are now looking at marginal core EPS decline in FY6/19 following our earnings downgrade. We also lower our TP to MYR4.76 on 28x FY19 PER (previously MYR5.13 on 28x FY18 PER), pegged at its 5-year mean as we roll forward our valuation base year. IOI declared a 2nd interim DPS of 4.5sen (ex-date: 4 Sep).</column>
<column>Lacks catalyst; HOLD for now</column>
<column>4QFY6/18 core earnings disappointed on lower-than-expected plantation contribution. Overall FY6/18 core earnings posted a decent 7% YoY growth. We are now looking at marginal core EPS decline in FY6/19 following our earnings downgrade. We also lower our TP to MYR4.76 on 28x FY19 PER (previously MYR5.13 on 28x FY18 PER), pegged at its 5-year mean as we roll forward our valuation base year. IOI declared a 2nd interim DPS of 4.5sen (ex-date: 4 Sep).</column>
<column>FY18 lifted by Loders disposal and FX gains</column>
<column>4Q headline profits of MYR36m (-89% YoY, -98% QoQ) was dragged down mainly by lower plantation earnings and unrealized FX translation losses on its USD debt. Adjusted for FX losses and FV loss on biological assets, its 4Q core PATAMI of MYR133m (-34% YoY, -47% QoQ) brings FY18 core PATMI to MYR1,081b (+7% YoY) but only met 94% /90% of our/ consensus full-year forecasts – below expectations. As for FY18 headline profits of MYR3,060m (+312% YoY), it was mainly lifted by a one-off MYR1,680m disposal gain of Loders Croklaan, and FX gain on USD debt (MYR318m). </column>
<column>Downstream offsets weaker upstream earnings</column>
<column>For FY18, downstream was the outperformer as downstream EBIT (including Loders’ contribution until it was disposed in Mar 2018) grew 88% YoY to MYR548m, driven by margin expansion to 4.6% (+2.5-ppts YoY). This offsets weaker plantation contribution with EBIT of MYR927m (-16% YoY) as lower CPO ASP (-8%) and PK ASP (-16%), and higher cost more than offset higher FFB output (+11% YoY). By our estimate, IOI’s upstream all-in operating cost of production per CPO tonne rose 15% YoY to MYR1,287/t due to rising costs and lower PK prices. </column>
<column>FY19-20E EPS cut by 6-8%</column>
<column>Following the results, we cut our FY19-20E EPS by 8%/6% respectively largely reflecting higher cost expectations. But we are keeping our FFB output, implying a YoY growth of 3.7% for FY19E. CPO ASP is also unchanged at MYR2,500/t for FY19E. We introduce our FY21E EPS. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>JD.com, Inc</column>
<column>33.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Three reasons why we are upgrading JD to a HOLD but not a BUY from the Street’s only SELL for the first time in our coverage history: 1) revenue growth remains more robust than we previously expected; 2) proven that margin expansion is possible but the magnitude of such increase and management execution under a competitive environment remain questionable; 3) Share price is near our DCF/SOTP based TP, suggesting limited downside.  Risk reward no longer favors shorting. TP raised by 3%.  </column>
<column>U/G from SELL to HOLD for the very first time &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Three key reasons why we are upgrading JD from the Street’s only SELL to a HOLD for the first time in our coverage history: 1) revenue growth remains more robust than we previously expected; 2) it has proven that margin expansion is possible but the magnitude of such increase and management execution under a competitive environment remain questionable; 3) Share price is near our DCF/SOTP based TP, suggesting limited downside. Risk reward no longer favors shorting, in our view. TP raised by 3% and earnings estimates revised (Figure 6.)  &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Revenue growth is slowing but sustainable &#38;#13;</column>
<column>JD’s revenue growth has in most quarters beaten our forecasts. We appreciate management’s ability to grow its marketplace platform leveraging its direct sales platform. While top line growth is slowing, we forecast 20%+ growth for the next three years. Its alliance with a number of global and local players will help to expand the company’s addressable market. However, we note the risk of the company chasing growth over profitability if the growth slows. And expectations are high as only the top end of JD’s 3Q18 revenue guidance range meets the consensus estimate.  &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Gross margin was resilient under pressure&#38;#13;</column>
<column>JD’s margin expansion story has been called into question since the 1Q18 margin disappointment. However, even in a heavy promotional quarter with higher loss contributions from its logistics business, JD’s GPM remained at about 13.3%. Once its 3PL reaches certain scale, there is upside risk to its gross margin, in our view. However, uncertainty over the timing prevents us from becoming more enthusiastic.  &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Higher magnitude of margin improvement needed </column>
<column>We believe JD needs to reach a level of profitability that provides investors a reasonable valuation argument. With even 1% non-GAAP net margin a reach for 2018, it is difficult for us to assess the company’s long-term margin potential. We think the operating margin has to turn positive and reach 3% before we can make a fair valuation comparison.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Kimlun Bhd</column>
<column>1.400000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>2Q18 core earnings came in below ours/consensus expectations, dragged by the construction segment on the back of margin compression. Precast however saw a QoQ recovery. Our FY18E-FY20E earnings are lowered by 9%-19% after revising our construction progress and margins. We derive a slightly lower TP of MYR1.40 pegged to 6x FY19 PER (-1SD) after rolling forward our valuation base year. Kimlun remains a HOLD.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>2Q18 core earnings came in below ours/consensus expectations, dragged by the construction segment on the back of margin compression. Precast however saw a QoQ recovery. Our FY18E-FY20E earnings are lowered by 9%-19% after revising our construction progress and margins. We derive a slightly lower TP of MYR1.40 pegged to 6x FY19 PER (-1SD) after rolling forward our valuation base year. Kimlun remains a HOLD.</column>
<column>Dragged by weak construction margins</column>
<column>2Q18 core net profit of MYR10m (-39% YoY, -29% QoQ) brings 1H18 core net profit to MYR24m (-17% YoY), accounting for just 32%/35% of ours/consensus full-year forecasts. The shortfall largely came from the construction segment which reported a weaker GP of MYR16m (-25% YoY, -34% QoQ) due to the weaker-than-expected margins (-3.7ppts YoY, -3.4ppts QoQ). This was attributed to the lower margin project mix within the quarter, despite the higher works recognition (+6% YoY, -9% QoQ).</column>
<column>Recovery from precast</column>
<column>The division reported a higher revenue of MYR48m in 2Q18 (+102% YoY, +52% QoQ) on the back of higher volume of i) precast products to the KVMRT 2 and ii) quarry products to the Pan Borneo Sarawak Highway project. GP for the division recovered 244% QoQ (+62% YoY) to MYR8m on the back of stronger margins (+8.8ppts QoQ). YoY however, margins were lower by 3.9ppts due to the larger portion of SBG and TLS supplied to KVMRT 2 and higher sales of quarry products which are generally lower in margins. We do expect the segment to continue to pick up in 2H18.</column>
<column>Expecting stronger 2H18</column>
<column>We expect 2H18 to be stronger supported by progress at major projects as well as the continued recovery from the precast segment. That said, we revise down our FY18E/FY19E/FY20E earnings by 19%/12%/9% after tweaking for construction progress and trimming construction margins by 1ppts for FY18E-FY20E due to the shortfall in 1H18. We keep our FY18E target job win of MYR700m/MYR200m for construction/precast with Kimlun having secured MYR310m/MYR150m respectively in YTD FY18. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>KPJ Healthcare</column>
<column>1.080000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>2Q18 earnings were within ours/consensus expectations with the YoY growth largely supported by its Malaysian division. However, Indonesia continues to see red with RS Bumi Serpong reporting weak patient figures. Potential start-up costs from the new Perlis, Bandar Dato Onn (BDO) and Miri hospitals could offset earnings accretion from the older greenfield hospitals that are about to breakeven/turn profitable. Our earnings estimates and RNAV-based TP of MYR1.08 remain unchanged.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>2Q18 earnings were within ours/consensus expectations with the YoY growth largely supported by its Malaysian division. However, Indonesia continues to see red with RS Bumi Serpong reporting weak patient figures. Potential start-up costs from the new Perlis, Bandar Dato Onn (BDO) and Miri hospitals could offset earnings accretion from the older greenfield hospitals that are about to breakeven/turn profitable. Our earnings estimates and RNAV-based TP of MYR1.08 remain unchanged.</column>
<column>Growth from the Malaysia segment</column>
<column>KPJ’s 2Q18 net profit of MYR43m (+28% YoY, flat QoQ) brought 1H18 earnings to MYR85m (+16% YoY), meeting ours/consensus FY18 forecasts at 52%/47% respectively. The YoY growth in 2Q18 was supported largely by the Malaysian segment which reported a higher PBT of MYR64m (+30% YoY, flat QoQ) which KPJ attributes to cost optimisation measures put in place, mainly at the greenfield hospitals undergoing gestation. As a result, PBT margin improved 1.7ppts YoY (+0.2ppts QoQ). We believe the stronger YoY growth could also potentially be due to the older greenfield hospitals that have broken even or turned PBT positive within 2Q18.</column>
<column>Indonesia still in the red</column>
<column>Indonesia reported wider losses of MYR2m in 2Q18 at the PBT level (from breakeven in 2Q17; MYR1m losses in 1Q18), mainly contributed by the lower number of outpatients (-12% YoY, -15% QoQ) and inpatients (-35% YoY, -23% QoQ) from RS Bumi Serpong Damai. The loss of patients could be a result of Bumi Serpong trying to diversify away from lower margin patients under the Indonesian National Health Insurance Scheme (BPJS).</column>
<column>No change to earnings&#38;#13;</column>
<column>The potential start-up costs from the new greenfield hospitals such as Perlis (opened May 2018), BDO (expected 4Q18/1Q19) and Miri (1Q19) could offset earnings accretion from the newly breakeven hospitals. The rule of thumb is around 3 years for greenfield hospitals to breakeven. We keep our earnings unchanged. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Kuala Lumpur Kepong</column>
<column>23.700000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>3QFY9/18 results disappointed largely on weak plantation earnings but we believe there was a net inventory build-up which could boost profits in the final quarter. Nonetheless, we conservatively lower our earnings forecasts by 5%-6%. Following which, we trim our TP to MYR23.70 (previously MYR25.00) on unchanged 26x FY18 PER based on its 5-year historical mean. Given limited downside, KLK remains a HOLD.</column>
<column>Expect a better final quarter</column>
<column>3QFY9/18 results disappointed largely on weak plantation earnings but we believe there was a net inventory build-up which could boost profits in the final quarter. Nonetheless, we conservatively lower our earnings forecasts by 5%-6%. Following which, we trim our TP to MYR23.70 (previously MYR25.00) on unchanged 26x FY18 PER based on its 5-year historical mean. Given limited downside, KLK remains a HOLD.</column>
<column>9MFY18 profit down 19% YoY</column>
<column>KLK’s 3QFY9/18 core net profit of MYR142m (-2% YoY, -21% QoQ) fell short on weaker-than-expected plantation earnings, and a higher than usual effective tax rate of 31% (due to non-deductible items), but mitigated by better-than-expected downstream contribution. This brings 9MFY18 core net profit to MYR643m (-19% YoY), which met just 63% /58% of our/consensus full-year forecasts.</column>
<column>Poor upstream, but still strong downstream  </column>
<column>3Q plantation EBIT fell 42% YoY (-26% QoQ) to MYR136m underpinned by lower plantation revenue (-28% YoY, -12% QoQ), and higher-than-expected cost of production. The lower revenue was achieved despite relatively flattish FFB output (+0.5% YoY, -3% QoQ) and only -14% YoY lower CPO ASP achieved (-4% QoQ). This leads us to believe there was a net build-up in inventory in 3Q that could boost sales in the 4Q. As for manufacturing, this division chalked up decent margins of 4% to bring in MYR99m in EBIT (-21% QoQ), a turnaround from a MYR5m loss a year ago. Its oleo division benefited from the low raw material cost. As for property, it delivered a decent EBIT of MYR8m on higher progress billing.</column>
<column>Earnings and TP revised downwards</column>
<column>Following the weak results, we lower our FY18-20E EPS by -5%/-6%/-5% mainly to account for lower output growth (FY18-20 output cut by -4%/-4%/-1%), higher cost, and higher effective taxes. Nonetheless, we expect a stronger final quarter earnings, aided in part by our anticipated net inventory drawdown, and still decent downstream earnings. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>KWG Property</column>
<column>9.500000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>KWG’s very aggressive FY18 sales target of CNY65b, up 71% YoY, carries downside risks. Its exposure in Greater Bay Area and the “staff co-investment scheme” could help accelerate project turnaround time. KWG has less refinancing risk as gearing is contained and the maturity of its next paper will be in Mar 2019. We initiate with HOLD rating and TP of HKD9.5/share (NAV disc. 50%). The 50% discount is based on +1SD above mean due to strong balance sheet and exposure to the Greater Bay Area.</column>
<column>Initiate with HOLD and TP of HKD9.5 </column>
<column>KWG has set a very aggressive sales target for FY18 at CNY65b, up 71% YoY. We think its exposure in Greater Bay Area and the “staff co-investment scheme” could help accelerate the pace of development. But the ambitious pre-sales target of 71% YoY growth carries higher risk of shortfall. However, we think KWG will have less refinancing risk as gearing is contained and the maturity of its next paper will be in Mar 2019. We initiate with a HOLD rating and TP of HKD9.5/share (NAV disc. 50%). The 50% discount is based on +1SD above mean due to the strong balance sheet and contracted sales growth driven by Greater Bay Area.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Partnership scheme to boost growth </column>
<column>The staff co-investment scheme came into effect in Aug 2017. With staff taking equity interest in its development projects, KWG expects faster turnaround time and the shorter development cycle to boost IRR. The scheme would allow staff a maximum 10% stake in the selected projects. Participation by senior management and most project-based mid-level staff would be mandatory. While it could shorten the construction cycle, quality control could be at risk. </column>
<column>Aggressive target on the back of strong landbank  </column>
<column>KWG has set a pre-sales target of CNY65b, up 71% YoY for 2018E. We think that it is supported by robust sellable resources of CNY110b, up 83% YoY. 27% of total saleable resources are in first tier cities and 65% are in second tier cities. While the market believes this is achievable, we are more circumspect. Our forecasts are largely in line (-3% to +2%) with the consensus of FY19E/20E. Even if contracted sales could grow at 71% YoY to the CNY65b target, the replenishment of landbank for the coming years will be challenging to maintain the momentum. </column>
<column>Healthy balance sheet; Low refinancing risk </column>
<column>KWG’s maturity of its next paper will be the 5-year USD dollar bond (USD600m) in early 2019. We do not expect difficulties in the refinancing as net gearing level is healthy at 63% for FY18E, in our forecast.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Lingkaran Trans Kota</column>
<column>5.100000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1QFY3/19 net profit of MYR55m was in line. LITRAK also declared a first interim DPS of 10sen (-33% YoY). As more dividends could be announced in the subsequent quarters based on its strong cash position, we keep our 25sen DPS estimate for FY19 for now. No change to our earnings forecasts and DCF-TP of MYR5.10.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>1QFY3/19 net profit of MYR55m was in line. LITRAK also declared a first interim DPS of 10sen (-33% YoY). As more dividends could be announced in the subsequent quarters based on its strong cash position, we keep our 25sen DPS estimate for FY19 for now. No change to our earnings forecasts and DCF-TP of MYR5.10.</column>
<column>1QFY19 within expectations</column>
<column>Litrak’s 1QFY19 net profit of MYR55m (flat YoY, +5% QoQ) was in line with our full-year forecast. Topline was lower by 2% YoY (-1% QoQ), mainly due to lower traffic volume at the LDP from the additional public holidays in connection to GE14 and festive toll discounts over the Hari Raya period. However, earnings came in flat YoY (higher QoQ) on the back of marginally higher PBT margins (+1.8ppts YoY/QoQ) as a result of lower finance cost.</column>
<column>Declares 1st interim DPS of 10sen</column>
<column>We believe LITRAK is still capable of paying higher dividends, above FY18’s 25sen/sh, especially with its strong gross cash position of MYR579m (110 sen/sh) as of end-June 2018. Historically, the stock has declared dividends in the first and third quarters of its financial years.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>No change to earnings&#38;#13;</column>
<column>No change to our earnings forecasts as we introduce our FY21E numbers. The stock still offers a decent yield of 4.9% based on our 25sen DPS p.a estimate.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Malakoff Corporation</column>
<column>1.127831</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>Malakoff’s 1H18 net profit was below expectation, with both taxes and associate income surprising negatively. A 99% DPR for 1H18 reaffirms our expectation for a 100% DPR for 2018. Malakoff’s dividend yield remains relatively attractive even after our earnings cut. Maintain BUY with a lower TP of MYR1.13 (-2%).</column>
<column>100% DPR still likely</column>
<column>Malakoff’s 1H18 net profit was below expectation, with both taxes and associate income surprising negatively. A 99% DPR for 1H18 reaffirms our expectation for a 100% DPR for 2018. Malakoff’s dividend yield remains relatively attractive even after our earnings cut. Maintain BUY with a lower TP of MYR1.13 (-2%).</column>
<column>Results below expectation</column>
<column>Malakoff’s 2Q18 net profit of MYR53m (-49% YoY, -1% QoQ) brings 1H18 net profit to MYR105m (-48% YoY), 38%/39% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. The miss relative to our forecasts, was due to 1) higher than expected taxes (62% effective tax rate in 2Q18) and 2) lower-than-expected associate contribution. A first interim DPS of 2.1sen was declared (2.5sen in 2Q17), representing 99% of 1H18 EPS.</column>
<column>No major operational concerns&#38;#13;</column>
<column>As expected, TBE was stable for 2Q18, delivering an availability factor of 92%. There was however a slight capacity payment shortfall at GB3. The regulator’s Jul 2018 operational logs indicate that one unit of TBP was under maintenance for the entire month. Separately, Malakoff announced that it will dispose its 20% stake in Lekir Bulk Terminal to Tenaga for MYR90m. This represents a historical PER of c.18x. </column>
<column>Lowering earnings </column>
<column>We lower our FY18/19/20 net profit forecasts by 14%/13%/16% respectively as we incorporate latest run-rates for taxes and associate income. With our EBITDA forecasts unchanged, our TP is lowered marginally to MYR1.13 (from MYR1.15). We expect management to maintain a 100% payout ratio for FY18. Our TP is based on a sum-of-parts, with each entity valued on a DCF (assuming 7.2% WACC for the Malaysia power plants).</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Maxis Bhd</column>
<column>5.898450</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1H18 results were in line, with both prepaid and postpaid posting sequential revenue growth in 2Q18. Management is maintaining its seemingly conservative 2018 guidance of an EBITDA decline, possibly in lieu of the high 2H17 base. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged TP of MYR5.90. We view risk-reward as being merely balanced presently.</column>
<column>Cautious guidance likely a base effect</column>
<column>1H18 results were in line, with both prepaid and postpaid posting sequential revenue growth in 2Q18. Management is maintaining its seemingly conservative 2018 guidance of an EBITDA decline, possibly in lieu of the high 2H17 base. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged TP of MYR5.90. We view risk-reward as being merely balanced presently.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Results in line</column>
<column>Maxis’ 2Q18 core net profit of MYR492m (+2% YoY, -6% QoQ) brings 1H18 net profit to MYR1,012m (+2% YoY), 51% of both our/consensus full-year forecasts. 1H18 normalised EBITDA of MYR2,019m (-9% YoY) was 50%/47% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. A 5sen DPS (unchanged YoY) was declared, in line. </column>
<column>Sequential revenue recovery </column>
<column>On a like-for-like basis (adjusting for the effects of MFRS 15), 2Q18 mobile service revenue grew by 1.6% from the low base in 1Q18. (Cumulatively, service revenue is still down 4.5% YoY in 1H18.). Both prepaid and postpaid registered sequential revenue growth, as ARPU expansion more than offset subscriber loss for prepaid, while ARPU and subscriber base expanded QoQ for postpaid. EBITDA margin (again on a like-for-like basis) trended down sequentially to 44.8% (-0.8ppt QoQ) on higher marketing and O&#38;#38;M costs.  With the recent spotlight on fibre broadband, management noted that access terms are presently being finalised, and details of new products could possibly be announced soon. </column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>Despite EBITDA being stable in 1H18, management has kept its 2018 EBITDA guidance (high single-digit decline) unchanged, citing possible uncertainties in 2H18 (we note there is possibly a base effect too, given the elevated margin in 2H17). Our earnings forecasts and MYR5.90 TP are unchanged. Our TP is based on a DCF, assuming 6.9% WACC and 2% long-term growth.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Mega First Corp. Bhd</column>
<column>4.200000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>Earnings came in above our expectations due to a lower effective tax rate within 2Q18. Core earnings grew 33% YoY in 2Q18, attributed to the ‘others’ division, and supported by construction profit from Don Sahong. Don Sahong construction continues to progress on schedule with the 80% completion target by end-2018 within reach. Our earnings forecasts and SOP-based TP are unchanged pending an update with management.</column>
<column>Maintain BUY</column>
<column>Earnings came in above our expectations due to a lower effective tax rate within 2Q18. Core earnings grew 33% YoY in 2Q18, attributed to the ‘others’ division, and supported by construction profit from Don Sahong. Don Sahong construction continues to progress on schedule with the 80% completion target by end-2018 within reach. Our earnings forecasts and SOP-based TP are unchanged pending an update with management. </column>
<column>Driven by ‘others’ division</column>
<column>2Q18 core net profit of MYR37m (+33% YoY, +10% QoQ) brought 1H18 core net profit to MYR71m (+29% YoY), above ours/consensus forecasts, at 59% of full-year, respectively. The outperformance was attributed to a lower effective tax rate of 15.9% in 2Q18 (-6.2ppts YoY, +0.5ppts QoQ). YoY, core earnings driver was the ‘others’ division which reported a small PBT of MYR1.3m (vs. losses of MYR8.2m/MYR6.7m in 2Q17/1Q18). </column>
<column>Don Sahong progressing well</column>
<column>Elsewhere, MFCB’s 2Q18 group earnings continue to be supported by Don Sahong, which reported a construction PBT of MYR44m (-4% YoY, +2% QoQ). Despite a higher physical completion of 8.3% in 2Q18 (2Q17: 7.9%), construction profit was lower YoY as a result of the strengthening of the MYR against USD affecting the translated figures in MYR terms. Cumulative physical completion has hit 63% as of end-June 2018, on track to hit its 80% completion target by end-2018. Civil works on the power house and overall embankment have both reached ~70% completion while the channel excavation is also near completion. The assembly of the first turbine is expected to be completed by 2Q19.</column>
<column>Resources hit by higher costs</column>
<column>Despite the higher YoY revenue of MYR37m in 2Q18 (+25% YoY, flat QoQ) on the back of higher sales of lime products (+32% YoY), PBT for the division was lower YoY at MYR5m (-15% YoY, -27% QoQ). MFCB alludes that this was due to i) lower ASPs (strengthening of MYR negatively impacted the USD denominated export selling price in MYR terms) and ii) higher petcoke and transportation costs. As a result, PBT margin for the division contracted by 6.3ppts YoY (-4.8ppts QoQ).</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>MMS Ventures</column>
<column>1.880000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>2Q18 net profit disappointed on lower-than-expected delivery of the wafer inspection equipment. Softer capex in FY18 by its key clients will likely be a drag to MMSV’s earnings. Nonetheless, we expect FY19 to be a year of strong recovery, guided by capex requirements by MMSV’s key clients. For now, we cut FY18/19/20E earnings by 23%/8%/7% and lower our TP to MYR1.88 (-7%), pegged on unchanged 13.5x CY19 PER (+1SD to 5-year mean of 9.5x). Maintain BUY.</column>
<column>Below expectations&#38;#13;</column>
<column>2Q18 net profit disappointed on lower-than-expected delivery of the wafer inspection equipment. Softer capex in FY18 by its key clients will likely be a drag to MMSV’s earnings. Nonetheless, we expect FY19 to be a year of strong recovery, guided by capex requirements by MMSV’s key clients (i.e. a global lighting MNC based in the Netherlands and Globetronics). For now, we cut FY18/19/20E earnings by 23%/8%/7% and lower our TP to MYR1.88 (-7%), pegged on unchanged 13.5x CY19 PER (+1SD to 5-year mean of 9.5x). Maintain BUY.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>A lean operation to weather through tough times&#38;#13;</column>
<column>2Q18 net profit of MYR2.8m (-30% QoQ, -69% YoY) took 1H18 earnings to MYR6.8m (-48% YoY), meeting only 38% of our initial full-year forecast. YoY, 2Q18 revenue fell 59% largely due to lower inspection equipment delivery. MMSV delivered 17 wafer inspection equipment in 2017 but none in 1H18; we expect this to pick up again in 2H18, in accordance to its clients’ capex requirements. The sharp YoY fall in 2Q18 revenue affected MMSV’s operational efficiency, causing a 6ppts YoY contraction in operating margins and a 69% YoY plunge in earnings. Positively, MMSV’s lean business model has allowed it to stay profitable amid a weak topline. A 1sen interim DPS was declared (ex-date: 24 Sep).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Earnings expected to rebound strongly in FY19</column>
<column>For FY19, we expect a strong 65% YoY increase in revenue, led by a jump in demand for inspection equipment as the camera flash module for the North American premium smartphone brand hits its replacement cycle again (typically, every two years); the possible emergence of triple rear camera may totally change the dynamics of the flash light module for smartphones. Also, we expect higher demand to come from MMSV’s exposure to ams AG via Globetronics (GTB MK, HOLD) in the sensor segment on adoption of 3D sensing and augmented reality, among others.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Valuation gap is still too large&#38;#13;</column>
<column>MMSV’s local automation equipment peers have recently re-rated on sector rotation as beneficiaries of a stronger USD; their valuations now average ~20x CY19 PER. MMSV however trades at just 11x CY19 PER (10x CY19 PER ex-cash), a ~45% discount to its peers. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Nissin Foods</column>
<column>5.300000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column></column>
<column>We hosted an NDR for Nissin Foods (NF) in HK last week following its 1H18 results. Investors are concerned with: i) NF’s weak distribution in China compared with peers; ii) pricing strategy; and iii) e-commerce plan. Investors asked how NF will achieve further sales growth in HK, when oper. leverage will boost margins, and progress on M&#38;A. We forecast double-digit sales CAGR for the next 3-5 years and look for the company to gradually increase the div. Our DCF-based TP of HKD5.30 is unchanged.</column>
<column>NDR: growth strategy - the key to watch &#38;#13;</column>
<column>We hosted an NDR for Nissin Foods (NF) in HK last week following its 1H18 results (1H18). Investors are concerned with: i) NF’s weak distribution in China compared with peers; ii) pricing strategy; and iii) e-commerce plan. Investors were also keen to find out how NF will achieve further sales growth in HK as it’s already a mature market. Investors also asked when positive operating leverage will kick in to boost margins, progress on M&#38;#38;A.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>China strategy: will speed up pace of growth&#38;#13;</column>
<column>NF is expanding distribution by increasing its sales forces, developing exclusive cross-over brands for certain retailers and selling “made in HK” Demae Iccho noodles in China. Together with its expanded capacity, these changes have speeded up sales growth. For pricing, NF has no plans to raise prices as its products are already priced above mainstream products. That said, its prices are becoming increasingly attractive as competitors are gradually raising prices. In terms of e-commerce, its sales are small, but its Tmall site, launched only in early 2017 already has 180,000 followers. On M&#38;#38;A, NF is seeking targets to strengthen its distribution.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>HK: more sales of high-price products + new categories&#38;#13;</column>
<column>NF said it achieved growth for existing products by increasing sales of high-margin noodles, like Bar Ramen and Cup Noodles Big, while exclusive cross-over branded products (eg, IPPUDO Cup for 7-11 CVS) helped to boost sales of other noodles. Also, it is consistently adding new flavours and healthy alternatives. In addition, its potato chips and granola have notched up good sales growth, underscoring its diversification efforts. As for HK, NF’s M&#38;#38;A targets are logistics and warehouse operators, as well as companies that can contribute new product categories.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Double-digit sales growth; margins to recover&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We believe NF is delivering on its plan to grow in both HK and China by leveraging existing and new product categories/businesses. We anticipate it will win a bigger share of the wallets of the more affluent population due to its strong brand and unique Japanese origin. Considering its small business base and expanding portfolio, we forecast double-digit sales CAGR for the next 3-5 years. Lastly, we also look for the company to gradually increase the dividend. Our DCF-based TP of HKD5.30 is unchanged.&#38;#13;</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>PECCA Group</column>
<column>0.970000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Despite QoQ improvement in 4QFY6/18, earnings disappointed ours and consensus expectations as we believe that Pecca’s manufacturing yield has not fully recovered from inefficiency due to a new batch of workers at higher costs and lower expertise. We cut FY19/20E earnings by 14% each to reflect (i) risk of lower TIV and (ii) higher labour cost from a minimum wage hike. On less sanguine outlook, we now peg Pecca at 13x CY19 PER, deriving a lower TP of MYR0.97 (-23%). </column>
<column>Headwinds ahead; D/G to HOLD</column>
<column>Despite QoQ improvement in 4QFY6/18, earnings disappointed ours and consensus expectations as we believe that Pecca’s manufacturing yield has not fully recovered from inefficiency due to a new batch of workers at higher costs and lower expertise. We cut FY19/20E earnings by 14% each to reflect (i) risk of lower TIV and (ii) higher labour cost from a minimum wage hike. On less sanguine outlook, we now peg Pecca at 13x CY19 PER (10% below our valuation peg for auto players within our coverage; vs. 14.5x previously), deriving a lower TP of MYR0.97 (-23%). </column>
<column>QoQ jump led by better production efficiency</column>
<column>Despite flattish sales QoQ (+1%), 4QFY18 net profit improved to MYR2.5m (+23% QoQ) and took FY18 earnings to MYR10.2m (-31% YoY); FY18 net profit met only 92%/88% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. QoQ profit improvement is attributable to better production yield (especially in sewing of the car seat covers). Recall that Pecca was hit by higher labour overtime costs which stemmed from (i) a sudden volume spike and (ii) lower production yield due to inefficiency of a new batch of inexperience foreign workers, both in 3QFY18. A final DPS of 3sen was declared this quarter; this brings FY18 DPS to 5sen – below expectations as we had expected FY18 DPS to hit 6sen.</column>
<column>Incorporating headwinds into forecasts</column>
<column>While we expect Pecca’s production yield to recover to its previous norm, we are also cautious of higher labour cost from the upcoming minimum wage hike; further details are likely to be revealed by end-2018. At the same time, auto industry TIV sales are expected to see a sharp decline in 4QCY18 after the SST kicks in by 1 Sep 2018. Beyond that, slower GDP growth expectation may dampen consumer sentiment especially for purchase of big ticket items such as cars in 2019.</column>
<column>HOLD for dividends</column>
<column>Despite little catalysts to earnings, we believe that Pecca’s huge cash war chest (MYR91m as at end-Jun 2018; 50sen per share or 56% of current market cap) could enable higher dividends, should there be no concrete capex or M&#38;#38;A plans. Dividend yield is 5.6% for FY19E (based on 70% DPR). </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Petronas Gas</column>
<column>19.501633</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>PTG’s 1H18 results were in line. Management’s acknowledgement of the likely use of historical cost for asset valuation effectively rules out the possibility of earnings (of transport and regas) remaining status quo, although this is unlikely to be the base case of investors, in our view. With the stock now approaching our TP, we downgrade PTG to HOLD (from BUY) with an unchanged MYR19.50 TP.</column>
<column>Earnings erosion likely? &#38;#13;</column>
<column>PTG’s 1H18 results were in line. Management’s acknowledgement of the likely use of historical cost for asset valuation effectively rules out the possibility of earnings (of transport and regas) remaining status quo, although this is unlikely to be the base case of investors, in our view. With the stock now approaching our TP, we downgrade PTG to HOLD (from BUY) with an unchanged MYR19.50 TP.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Results in line&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Excluding unrealised forex gain, PTG’s 2Q18 core net profit of MYR516m (+23% YoY, +8% QoQ) brings 1H18 net profit to MYR993m (+13% YoY), 53% of our/consensus full-year forecasts respectively. EBIT of all segments were in line. The QoQ uptick in net profit was due to further recognition of Pengerang-related tax incentives (effective tax rate of 15% in 2Q18). A 16sen DPS was declared in the quarter (unchanged from 1Q18), representing a 62% payout ratio. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Possibly using historical cost &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Negotiations with the regulator on TPA-associated tariff determination remain in progress, with talks currently revolving around the rate of return (the regulator employs a “NOPAT = rate of return x asset value” model). Management for the first time alluded to the likely use of historical cost (instead of replacement value) for asset valuation. This effectively signals possible earnings erosion going forward, thus ruling out our best case scenario of earnings remaining status-quo. We estimate c.1/3 of PTG’s earnings could be at risk in the worst case scenario. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Downgrade to HOLD &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Our earnings forecasts and MYR19.50 TP are unchanged. Our TP is based on a 50% probability of an adverse outcome (halving of transportation and regasification EBIT) to our DCF (6.8% WACC and 2% long-term growth). With the stock now approaching our TP, we downgrade PTG to HOLD (from BUY). Risk-reward remains merely balanced for now.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Power Assets Holdings</column>
<column>63.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD, and cut TP by 9%. We believe PA lacks catalysts following distribution of the third special dividend in Apr 2018 as we don’t think it can afford another round. However, we forecast PA will maintain a stable DPS of HKD2.80/share. Without a large net cash balance, we think it’ll be unlikely for PA to make any material acquisitions in the near term. We revise down our SOTP-based TP after factoring in distribution of the special dividend in April.</column>
<column>Inexpensive yield play</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD, and cut TP by 9%. We believe PA lacks catalysts following distribution of the third special dividend in Apr 2018 as we don’t think it can afford another round. However, we forecast PA will maintain a stable DPS of HKD2.80/share. Without a large net cash balance, we think it’ll be unlikely for PA to make any material acquisitions in the near term. We revise down our SOTP-based TP after factoring in distribution of the special dividend in April. </column>
<column>We expect stable DPS, but no special dividend</column>
<column>After total special dividends of HKD18.5/share or HKD39.5b (three rounds in total), we forecast net cash balance will drop to HKD5.7b at end-2018. Thus, we don’t believe there’ll be any more special dividends. However, we expect PA will keep its regular DPS at HKD2.80 in FY18E. It will lead to a cash outflow of around HKD6.0b annually. </column>
<column>Unlikely to make substantial acquisitions</column>
<column>Given its limited business scope, PA wasn’t involved in the acquisition of Reliance Home Comfort and Ista with CKI (1038 HK, BUY). We think there’s less of a chance we’ll see PA involved in a substantial transaction given we think the net cash is not large enough to buy sizable projects like the UK Power Network, especially since we forecast PA will maintain its stable dividend payout of HKD6.0b in FY18E. </column>
<column>Prefer CKI over PA</column>
<column>Even though we don’t expect any catalysts, share price looks inexpensive as we forecast it could provide a 5% dividend yield in FY18E. We prefer CKI rather than PA as we believe CKI will have more possible M&#38;#38;A catalysts and financial support from CKA (1113 HK, HOLD).</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Public Bank</column>
<column>22.700000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>While 1H18 results were within expectations, management remains cautious amid a still challenging operating environment, and it has toned down its loan growth and NIM guidance for the year. What is positive, nevertheless, is that Public Bank’s healthy capital position has afforded it the ability to raise its dividend payout ratio. We trim FY18-20E earnings by 1-3% but maintain our HOLD call and MYR22.70 TP (FY19E PBV of 2x, ROE: 14%).</column>
<column>A cautious outlook</column>
<column>While 1H18 results were within expectations, management remains cautious amid a still challenging operating environment, and it has toned down its loan growth and NIM guidance for the year. What is positive, nevertheless, is that Public Bank’s healthy capital position has afforded it the ability to raise its dividend payout ratio. We trim FY18-20E earnings by 1-3% but maintain our HOLD call and MYR22.70 TP (FY19E PBV of 2x, ROE: 14%).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Challenging environment in 2Q18</column>
<column>Public Bank’s net profit of MYR1.4b in 2Q18 (+5% YoY, -1% QoQ) took 1H18 net profit to MYR2.8b (+9% YoY). This was within expectations at 49% of our full-year forecast and consensus. The operating environment was challenging in 2Q18 - annualized loan growth was a subdued 4% while NIM contracted 9bps QoQ. NOII contracted 5% YoY and JAWS was negative. As such, 2Q18 operating profit expanded just 0.5% YoY. Positively though, credit costs improved YoY amid stable asset quality.  </column>
<column>Expectations toned down</column>
<column>Management cautions of a still challenging operating environment and has trimmed its 2018 domestic loan growth forecast to 4-5% from 5% previously (MKE: 4.8%). It also guides for a low to mid-single digit NIM compression (from a marginal compression before), due to funding cost competition. Our FY18-20 forecasts are trimmed by 1-3% to factor in higher NIM compression, balanced off by lower credit cost expectations. Our FY18E ROAE of 14.6% is within management’s expectation of 14-15%. </column>
<column>Higher dividend payout</column>
<column>What is positive is that the group’s CET1 ratio is comfortable at 12.7% end-June 2018. As a result, Public Bank has been able to raise its dividend payout ratio (DPR) to 44% in 1H18 versus 40% in 1H17, and it declared a higher interim DPS of 32sen in 1H18 versus 27sen in 1H17. Our forecast assumes a DPR of 45% for FY18 onwards.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>RCE Capital Bhd</column>
<column>1.950000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>RCE’s moderate loan growth is healthy and sustainable, in our view, with preservation of asset quality being a top priority. Meanwhile its funding structure continues to improve and the ability to issue longer term debt at lower rates should enhance margins. Valuations are undemanding with the stock trading at a prospective CY19 PER of just 5.9x, and P/BV of just 0.9x. Dividend yield of &#62;4% provides support. Our TP of MYR1.95 pegs on a CY19 P/BV of 1.1x (CY19E ROE: 15.8%).</column>
<column>Decent valuations, paced growth</column>
<column>RCE’s moderate loan growth is healthy and sustainable, in our view, with preservation of asset quality being a top priority. Meanwhile its funding structure continues to improve and the ability to issue longer term debt at lower rates should enhance margins. Valuations are undemanding with the stock trading at a prospective CY19 PER of just 5.9x, and P/BV of just 0.9x. Dividend yield of &#38;#62;4% provides support. Our TP of MYR1.95 pegs on a CY19 P/BV of 1.1x (CY19E ROE: 15.8%). </column>
<column>Current pace of loan growth is healthy</column>
<column>That loan growth has moderated to 6-7% is healthy, in our view, as is the fact the average loan size per borrower has reduced over time, for these ensure that the emphasis is on preserving asset quality. RCE’s asset quality has been stable with an NPL ratio of about 4.2%, while its loan loss coverage of 185% is comfortable. Management expects loan growth to track above the banking system’s loan growth and we currently impute loan growth of 7% in FYE3/18 versus industry loan growth of 4.5%.</column>
<column>Funding structure has improved</column>
<column>RCE’s funding structure has improved over time and remains stable. As at end-June 2018, long-term funding (term loans and Sukuk) accounted for 80% of total debt versus just 56% in FY16. The MYR900m Al-Dzahab programme was fully issued in March 2018 at an average funding cost of 5.51% and management is looking at a new MYR2b ABS Sukuk SPV to be issued sometime in Oct/Nov 2018, at an indicative cost of 5.46%. If so, this would be positive in ensuring that funding cost is lowered.</column>
<column>Immaterial impact from recent Government moves&#38;#13;</column>
<column>The new Government’s move to review the appointment of political appointees and to dissolve several committees/commissions will have minimal impact on RCE, whose exposure to contract workers and the said government bodies represents just 0.6% of its total loans. Neither will the pledge to move the minimum salary up to MYR1,500/mth within five years have a significant impact, for RCE’s loans to civil servants earning less than MYR1,500/mth make up less than 1% of its loan portfolio.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>RHB Bank</column>
<column>5.900000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>No major surprises in RHB’s 2Q18 results, the only drawback being the scaling back of management’s loan growth guidance. Our FY18 ROE estimate of 9.8% is nevertheless in line with management’s target of 9-10% (10.2% in 1H18). We maintain our HOLD call and TP of MYR5.90, pegged to a FY19E PBV of 0.9x (FY19E ROE: 9.9%).  </column>
<column>ROE target attainable&#38;#13;</column>
<column>No major surprises in RHB’s 2Q18 results, the only drawback being the scaling back of management’s loan growth guidance. Our FY18 ROE estimate of 9.8% is nevertheless in line with management’s target of 9-10% (10.2% in 1H18). We maintain our HOLD call and TP of MYR5.90, pegged to a FY19E PBV of 0.9x (FY19E ROE: 9.9%).  &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Within expectations&#38;#13;</column>
<column>RHB’s 2Q18 core net profit of MYR570m (+14% YoY, -4% QoQ) took 1H18 core net profit to MYR1.2b (+16% YoY). This was 51%/54% of our full-year forecast/consensus – within our expectations but above consensus, in our view. Encouragingly, NIM was stable QoQ, positive JAWS persisted and credit costs were lower QoQ. Loan growth however was just 2% annualized while CASA contracted.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Loan and CASA growth guidance trimmed &#38;#13;</column>
<column>In light of the 2Q performance, management now guides for slower loan growth for the year of 3-4% versus 6% before and CASA growth of 4-5% versus 10% before. Other targets remain intact, including the ROE guidance of 9-10% for the year. Our forecasts are maintained, incorporating a loan growth estimate of 4.5% for FY18 and an FY18 ROE of 9.8%. Management guides for NIMs to soften HoH and to average around 2.23% for FY18 – this is in line with our estimate.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Higher interim DPS &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Management declared an interim DPS of 7.5sen for 1H18 (5.0sen for 1H17). The group’s capital position is comfortable with a group CET1 ratio of 14.5% and 12.4% at the bank level. Management nevertheless expects to maintain its payout ratio of 30%, which is in line with our estimates. We forecast an FY18 DPS of 18sen versus 15sen in FY17.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Sarawak Oil Palms</column>
<column>3.100000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>2Q18 earnings disappointed on lower-than-expected output, CPO ASP and higher cost. We cut FY18-20E EPS by 33%/26%/21% mainly on lower output forecasts. Following our earnings cut, we downgrade SOP to HOLD (from BUY) with a lower TP of MYR3.10 (previously MYR4.62) pegged at an unchanged 14x 2018 PER, its 3-year historical mean. Downside is limited by its current adjusted EV/planted ha of MYR21,000 which is below replacement cost of ~MYR25,000/ha.</column>
<column>Downgrade to HOLD</column>
<column>2Q18 earnings disappointed on lower-than-expected output, CPO ASP and higher cost. We cut FY18-20E EPS by 33%/26%/21% mainly on lower output forecasts. Following our earnings cut, we downgrade SOP to HOLD (from BUY) with a lower TP of MYR3.10 (previously MYR4.62) pegged at an unchanged 14x 2018 PER, its 3-year historical mean. Downside is limited by its current adjusted EV/planted ha of MYR21,000 which is below replacement cost of ~MYR25,000/ha.</column>
<column>Double whammy of lower price and output</column>
<column>2Q18 core net profit of MYR11m (-84% YoY, -60% QoQ) brings 1H18 core profit to MYR37m (-73% YoY), meeting just 20% of our full-year forecast. 2Q18 earnings were affected mainly by lower on CPO ASP achieved (-16% YoY, -8% QoQ), lower FFB output (-2% YoY, +14% QoQ) and higher cost. We estimate its 1H18 all-in cost of production at MYR1,997/t (+34% YoY) which was above expectation. This could be partly due to frontloading of certain costs and (trading) losses at its refinery. Also, fertiliser application in 1H18 was ~65% of full-year’s requirement.</column>
<column>Stronger 2H18 output but likely to miss projection </column>
<column>Due to cropping pattern change, 1H18 FFB output fell 5% YoY and met just 38% of our full-year forecast, below historical 1H:2H ratio of 44:56. We think output will likely pick up strongly in 2H18. Nonetheless, we believe there is downside to our 2018’s FFB growth projection of 16% YoY to 1.6m MT.  We now cut our FFB output forecasts by 0.17m MT p.a for FY18 to FY20. This implies a growth of only 4% for FY18, but FY19-20 YoY growth forecasts are relatively unchanged at 11% and 9% respectively.   </column>
<column>Long term appeal but lacks short term catalyst </column>
<column>Following our output revisions, we cut our FY18-20E EPS forecasts. Still we expect stronger 2H18 earnings on stronger output, lower cost and higher downstream contribution. While we continue to like SOP for its medium term growth prospect with ~8% 2017-20 3-year CAGR in FFB output, driven by its relatively young oil palm trees of ~11 years, there is lack of short term catalyst to drive up share price for now.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Semiconductor Manufacturing Int'l Corp.</column>
<column>6.900000</column>
<column>Sell</column>
<column></column>
<column>Maintain SELL and lift TP slightly to HKD6.9, still based on 0.8x 2018F P/BV (8-yr bottom to factor its possible lossmaking outlook). 2H18 sales growth should be muted based on its full-year guidance. Firm is unlikely to be profitable at operating level in the next few years without government subsidies. Only reason to own SMIC shares is to gain China domestic semiconductor exposure, in our view.</column>
<column>Won’t be profitable on its own before 2020</column>
<column>Maintain SELL and lift TP slightly to HKD6.9, still based on 0.8x 2018F P/BV (8-yr bottom to factor its possible lossmaking outlook). 2H18 sales growth should be muted based on its full-year guidance. Firm is unlikely to be profitable at operating level in the next few years without government subsidies. Only reason to own SMIC shares is to gain China domestic semiconductor exposure, in our view.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>A muted 2H18 outlook&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Even after its better-than-expected 2Q18 wafer revenue guidance (+17% QoQ), SMIC maintained its 2018F sales guidance of high single-digit % YoY growth. This guidance implies SMIC’s 2H18 wafer revenue will be flat to down slightly HoH. This echoes our view that only demand for mid- to low-end smartphones is recovering for inventory rebuild, while sell-through remains uncertain. 2H18 gross margins are also likely to slide to mid- to high-teens % due to surging depreciation cost and ASP erosion, and 2H18 is unlikely to be profitable at the operating level. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Operating loss all the way before 2020?&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We believe SMIC will remain at operating loss in 2019-2020. Pricing pressure for matured 300mm foundry will become more severe because UMC’s 28nm will be fully depreciated starting 2020. Its domestic competitors are also expanding 300mm capacity. On the other hand, SMIC’s COGS and R&#38;#38;D expenses are unlikely to fall, especially since the firm is speeding up its 14nm progress. We estimate SMIC’s gross margin will stay at &#38;#60;20% and operating expense will be USD800m-1b before government’s R&#38;#38;D funding. SMIC needs to reach USD5b+ revenue to be profitable at operating level and we think this is unlikely before 2020. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Buy for exposure or buy for value creation?&#38;#13;</column>
<column>SMIC’s transition will take years, in our view. Thus, the shares are unlikely to create value for investors. To gain China domestic semiconductor exposure amid the favourable policy environment is the only reason investors would want to long the shares. Fundamentally, we do not suggest investors to own the shares.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Shimao Property</column>
<column>22.500000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Reiterate HOLD w/unchanged est.'s and NAV based TP of HKD22.50, applying a 50% discount in line with third tier market developers. We forecast slower earnings growth than the sector average 35% due to Shimao’s more risk averse investment approach and relatively high exposure to tier-3 cities (ranked #3 within our coverage). Shimao over-expanded 3 yrs ago and suffered from poor earnings, which has led to its current more prudent approach to land investing. Still, 1H18 results showed improvement.</column>
<column>Solid 1H18 results but fairly valued; Maintain HOLD </column>
<column>Reiterate HOLD with unchanged estimates and NAV based TP of HKD22.50 after applying a 50% discount, in line with third tier market developers. We forecast slower earnings growth than the sector average 35% due to Shimao’s more risk averse investment approach and relatively high exposure to tier-3 cities (ranked #3 within our coverage). Shimao over-expanded 3 years ago and suffered from poor earnings, which has led to its current more prudent approach to investing in land. Still, 1H18 results confirmed that Shimao’s profit growth is gradually recovering. Core net profit rose ~20% YoY to CNY4.4b and reached ~48% of our full-year forecast and GPM is gradually expanding (up 1.4 ppt YoY to 31%). Gearing increased but remains reasonable, mitigating potential market risk and positioning the company for relatively more aggressive growth to meet more stringent margin requirements for new land bank.</column>
<column>Resilient pre-sales growth to meet FY18 target</column>
<column>Shimao’s 1H18 contracted sales rose ~60% YoY to CNY72.3b, meeting 52% of its CNY140b FY18 target. Contracted sales were mainly driven by Fujian province with CNY26.2b. We expect sales momentum to stay robust amid the CNY190b saleable resources mostly in tier-1 cities, such as Beijing, Guangzhou and Shenzhen in 2H18. We maintain our FY18 contracted sales forecast of CNY140b and project a 40% YoY growth. </column>
<column>Reasonable gearing offers flexibility in land banking </column>
<column>Net gearing increased 1.7 ppt to 62.7% on aggressive land banking in 1H18, but this is still below the 90% sector average. It acquired 48 plots with 7.73m sqm GFA (+71% YoY) at an average cost of CNY5,966/sqm. About 40% of the land acquired was through base price auction, acquisition and cooperation. The cost of the new land acquired is equivalent to only ~37% of contracted ASP in 1H18, providing sufficient buffer to maintain its target margin. </column>
<column>Good balance between growth and profitability</column>
<column>Key highlights: 1) revenue rose 18.8% YoY to CNY42.5b; 2) GPM expanded to 31.0% (vs. 30.4% in FY17); 3) core profit rose 20.2% YoY to CNY4.4b; 4) core NPM expanded to 14.3% (vs. 14.0% in FY17); and 4) declared an interim DPS of HKD50 cents, up 25% YoY.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Sime Darby Bhd</column>
<column>2.450000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>FY6/18 core earnings of MYR866m (-7% YoY) was within our expectations at 99% but beat consensus at 108%. We keep our FY19/FY20 earnings forecasts, projecting flattish growth of 1-3%; optimism behind rising orderbook at the Industrial division (led by uptick in mining cycle of Australasia) to be substantially offset by softer outlook for Motors division (on softer consumer sentiment). Our SOP-based TP is unchanged at MYR2.45. SDB is currently fairly valued; maintain HOLD.</column>
<column>Within ours but beat street’s estimates</column>
<column>FY6/18 core earnings of MYR866m (-7% YoY) was within our expectations at 99% but beat consensus at 108%. We keep our FY19/FY20 earnings forecasts, projecting flattish growth of 1-3%; optimism behind rising orderbook at the Industrial division (led by uptick in mining cycle of Australasia) to be substantially offset by softer outlook for Motors division (on softer consumer sentiment). Our SOP-based TP is unchanged at MYR2.45. SDB is currently fairly valued; maintain HOLD.</column>
<column>4QFY18 lifted by dividend from BMW Malaysia </column>
<column>4QFY18 core net profit of MYR297m (+49% QoQ, -20% YoY), took FY18 core earnings to MYR866m (-7% YoY); much stronger QoQ core earnings was boosted by a MYR121m dividend from BMW Malaysia. For the full-year, stronger PBIT led by the Industrial division (core PBIT jumped 60% YoY to MYR434m) was offset by lower interest income (-80% YoY to MYR104m). Notably, FY18 headline earnings included various negative one-offs amounting to MYR252m [mainly from impairment of distribution rights &#38;#38; inventory write-down for Vietnam’s Motor division (MYR149m) and impairment on equity interest in E&#38;#38;O (EAST MK, Not Rated; MYR103m)]. Full-year DPS of 8sen (88% DPR) was in line. </column>
<column>Some good, some bad</column>
<column>Industrial order book continues to show improvement for the second consecutive quarter (+17% QoQ to MYR2.7b), led by the Australasia region (order book: +27% QoQ to MYR1.8b). Robust mining activities alongside short-term spike from the construction sector in the Australasia region is expected to drive earnings growth for SDB in FY19. On the other hand, we are cautious for the Motors division which has seen lower overall volume sales, especially in the Australia and New Zealand region despite on-going product refreshment; trade tensions in the China region may hamper sentiment of big-ticket item buyers in FY19, affecting SDB’s largest market for the Motors division (44% of FY18 volume sale). </column>
<column>Fairly priced</column>
<column>We see limited earnings upside for SDB in FY19. Key lookout for the upcoming year is the possible disposal of its ports asset as part of a rationalisation plan to further unlock values for the group.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Sime Darby Plantation</column>
<column>5.350000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Sprawled over 11,000 ha, Carey Island (CI) estate is an important showpiece of SDPL’s integrated business model. This prime piece of real estate is also potentially the site of Klang Valley’s third port in 10 years’ time after Northport and Westport. We were privileged to visit its estates, mill, biodiesel and Jomalina refinery with a group of investors recently. We maintain our HOLD call and unchanged TP of MYR5.35 on an unchanged 30x 2019 PER, implying a P/RNAV of 0.6x.</column>
<column>A visit to SDPL’s showpiece </column>
<column>Sprawled over 11,000 ha, Carey Island (CI) estate is an important showpiece of SDPL’s integrated business model. This prime piece of real estate is also potentially the site of Klang Valley’s third port in 10 years’ time after Northport and Westport. We were privileged to visit its estates, mill, biodiesel and Jomalina refinery with a group of investors recently. We maintain our HOLD call and unchanged TP of MYR5.35 on an unchanged 30x 2019 PER, implying a P/RNAV of 0.6x.</column>
<column>Even better connectivity when WCE is ready</column>
<column>Currently most accessible via South Klang Valley Expressway (SKVE), CI’s accessibility will be further improved when the West Coast Expressway (WCE) is completed in 1-2 years. In years to come, there are plans to build an interchange within the CI estate where SKVE cuts across currently. When this happens, it will further boost the real estate value. </column>
<column>CI, a showpiece of SDPL’s integrated model  </column>
<column>CI is home to one of SDPL’s best performing estates in Malaysia with FFB yields of ~29t/ha (FY6/18) with OER of 23-24%. Given its discipline of short harvest-to-mill time, it is capable of producing one of the best quality oil with low free fatty acid (FFA) content. These premium oils are channelled to its Jomalina refinery which in turn produces specialty oils that command premium pricing. At times, some lower quality, non-food grade oils are channelled to its biodiesel plant for supplies to Petronas and Shell to meet the national B7 mandates. </column>
<column>Can only accrete in value over time </column>
<column>SDPL has owned this CI estate for decades now. It is held in the books at historical value, estimated at less than MYR1psf. Today, we estimate its unconverted agricultural land value to be in excess of MYR5psf as this prime real estate will be a natural extension of development from Klang city in the coming decades. For now, SDPL is not in a hurry to develop this showpiece, home to its high-yielding estates, R&#38;#38;D centre, plantation academy, mills, kernel crushing plant and biodiesel plant.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Sino Land Company</column>
<column>13.400000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>D/G to HOLD from BUY with TP slashed 23% to HKD13.40 after applying a higher target 45% NAV discount to reflect our concerns of Sino’s comparatively high land replenishment cost amid weakening physical market sentiment in HK. However, its solid balance sheet (~HKD20b net cash) and fair valuation at 45% NAV discount keeps us from a double D/G to SELL. Sino aggressively acquired six sites in FY18, boosting its landbank by 1.2m sqft. </column>
<column>High-land-cost risk, but balance sheet still strong&#38;#13;</column>
<column>D/G to HOLD from BUY with TP slashed 23% to HKD13.40 after applying a higher target 45% NAV discount to reflect our concerns of Sino’s comparatively high land replenishment cost amid weakening physical market sentiment in HK. However, its solid balance sheet (~HKD20b net cash) and fair valuation at 45% NAV discount keeps us from a double D/G to SELL (see Fig. 3 for est. revisions). Sino aggressively acquired six sites in FY18, boosting its landbank by 1.2m sqft. Also, the 100% FY18 profit growth was attributable to a one-off gain. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>FY18 results in line, propped up by one-off gain</column>
<column>The FY18 underlying net profit of HKD11b, up 100% YoY, was in line with our estimate. The profit growth was mainly due to the HKD5.7b one-off gain from disposing its 80% stake in The Palazzo in Chengdu. In fact, revenue from property sales (incl. Associates and JV’s) slumped 41% YoY to HKD8.9b. Also, gross rental income rose by 3.3% YoY to HKD4b for FY18, largely in line with our expectation. Going forward, three residential projects are expected to be launched in 2H 2018, such as Grand Central in Kwun Tong that will boost sales (already included in our estimates).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Aggressive land replenishment increases risk </column>
<column>Sino became more aggressive in replenishing its landbank in FY18. Sino (or together with a consortium) acquired six sites in FY18 (1.2m sqft in total). However, we think land costs were relatively high and in fact the site it acquired in Cheung Sha Wan was dubbed the “Land King” for residential units due to the record price paid. We have widened our target NAV discount from 30% to 45% (in line with the 5-year avg.; see Fig. 4) to reflect recent weakening in market sentiment and our cautious view towards physical property prices in HK (already risen 14% thus far in 2018). We are also using a 45% target NAV discount for CKA (1113 HK, HOLD, HKD56.80, TP: HKD62.8) and NWD (17 HK, BUY, HKD10.66, TP HKD14.6). &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Risks to our D/G: Kwun Tong project could be a catalyst&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We expect the Kwun Tong project (~2,000 units) will be launched in 2H18. We believe the whole project will be divided into two phases and each batch will consist of at least 200 units. This is to comply with new government policies requiring a minimum of 20% of each batch of a project being made for presale. While we expect the pricing won’t be aggressive, a strong sell-through rate could be a catalyst. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Sun Hung Kai Properties</column>
<column>122.000000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>We turn cautious towards SHKP due to the greater adverse impact of a possible vacancy tax and increasing China macro risks. We cut TP 22% to HKD122 after applying a higher target 45% NAV discount (vs. 30% previously) and D/G to HOLD. It appears the possible vacancy tax has adversely impacted SHK’s sales strategy. Also, we expect CNY depreciation and rising economic risk in China will impact its China business. We believe strong recurring rental income and attractive div. will support the shares.</column>
<column>Heightened risks to prices/sales; TP cut 22%</column>
<column>We have turned cautious towards SHKP due to the greater adverse impact of a possible vacancy tax and increasing China macro risks. Accordingly, we cut TP 22% to HKD122 after applying a higher target 45% NAV discount (vs. 30% previously) and downgrade to HOLD. It appears the possible vacancy tax has adversely impacted SHK’s sales strategy</column>
<column>Policy impact uncertainty lowering sales/prices&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Uncertainty regarding the government policy, i.e. possible vacancy tax, appears to be driving inventory clearing by developers. SHKP’s pricing for some projects has already become more conservative in order to maintain strong sell-through rates, such as for the project Cullinan West II. SHKP may also convert some units into rental apartments to avoid the potential vacancy tax, such as ~100 units in Park Yoho Napoli and one tower of “Victoria Harbour” (~140 units).</column>
<column>Risks from China exposure </column>
<column>We estimate around 16% of SHKP’s NAV is from China. We expect CNY depreciation will affect the NAV and income going forward from translation risk. In addition, we have a bearish view on China and a negative view on China’s property market. As a result, we expect exposure in China will lead to a larger NAV discount. </column>
<column>FY19 HK sales target in line with our expectation</column>
<column>SHKP’s FY19E HK sales target of HKD42.5b is in line with our expectation, and the medium-term annual property sales target remains HKD40b. SHKP’s FY18 underlying profit was up 17% YoY to HKD30.4b, in line with our expectation (Fig. 1). The total DPS reached HKD4.65, up 13.4% YoY. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Sunway Construction Group</column>
<column>2.300000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>2Q18 results came in below ours/consensus expectations largely dragged by weak contribution from the precast division as a result of higher steel bar prices. This is despite the stronger showing from the construction segment on the back of high works recognition. Our earnings and TP (15x FY19 PER, -1SD) are unchanged pending an update with management.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>2Q18 results came in below ours/consensus expectations largely dragged by weak contribution from the precast division as a result of higher steel bar prices. This is despite the stronger showing from the construction segment on the back of high works recognition.</column>
<column>Precast continues to drag earnings</column>
<column>2Q18 net profit of MYR36m (flat YoY and QoQ) brought 1H18 net profit to MYR72m (+3% YoY), meeting just 45%/43% of ours/consensus full-year forecasts. The shortfall in 2Q18 was contributed by the precast segment which reported a lower EBIT of MYR2m (-59% YoY, -37% QoQ), impacted by higher steel bar prices which were above the price during the tender stage. As a result, EBIT margin for the segment fell by 11.2ppts YoY (-2.7ppts QoQ) in 2Q18.</column>
<column>Construction still supporting growth&#38;#13;</column>
<column>YoY, construction continues to see growth, reporting an EBIT of MYR40m (+12% YoY, +2% QoQ) in 2Q18. This is in-line with the topline growth supported by higher works recognition mainly from the KVMRT 2, Parcel F and Putrajaya projects. EBIT margin for the division also remained stable at 7.8% (-1.4ppts YoY, -0.2ppts QoQ.). SCG’s outstanding orderbook stood at MYR5.8b as of end-Jun 2018. </column>
<column>Targeting MYR1.5b of job wins for FY18</column>
<column>Having secured MYR854m of new jobs (incl. precast) as of end-Jun 2018, we believe SCG’s internal job win target of MYR1.5-2b in FY18 is achievable. We believe this would largely be supported by the internal property developments within Sunway Group. Our earnings forecasts have assumed MYR1.5b of job wins for FY18. However, we do see downside risk to our earnings with the cost review of the KVLRT 3 and extended duration of its construction period (from 2021 to 2024).</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Ta Ann</column>
<column>2.700000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>2Q18 results disappointed on low CPO ASP, output and higher cost. The worse seems to be over for its timber division on rising prices, and higher log export quota in 2H18. We are keeping our earnings forecasts, anticipating better prospects in 2H18. Ta Ann is still a HOLD with an unchanged MYR2.70 TP on 13x FY18 PER, 5-year historical mean.</column>
<column>But timber division provides hope for 2H18</column>
<column>2Q18 results disappointed on low CPO ASP, output and higher cost. The worse seems to be over for its timber division on rising prices, and higher log export quota in 2H18. We are keeping our earnings forecasts, anticipating better prospects in 2H18. Ta Ann is still a HOLD with an unchanged MYR2.70 TP on 13x FY18 PER, 5-year historical mean.</column>
<column>Oil palm division underperformed</column>
<column>Adjusted for FV change in biological assets, 2Q18 core PATMI of MYR14m (-60% YoY, +229% QoQ) brings 1H18 core PATMI to MYR18m (-76% YoY) which met just 20% of our/consensus full-year estimates. 2Q18’s disappointment came from its oil palm division whereby PBT fell 64% YoY (+107% QoQ) to MYR20m on lower CPO ASP (-17% YoY, -4% QoQ), lower FFB production (-10% YoY, +21% QoQ), and higher cost. 1H18 FFB output was only 37% of our full-year forecast. The output shortfall is due to unusual change in cropping pattern in 1H.  As for cost, we estimate its 1H cost of production to be on the high side at MYR1,839/t (+35% YoY). We suspect fertilising application has been accelerated in 1H18.</column>
<column>Timber division returned to the black</column>
<column>Timber division returned to the black after three quarters of losses with MYR3m PBT in 2Q18 (flat YoY, 1Q18: -MYR7m). YoY, higher log ASP (+20% YoY, +2% QoQ – in MYR), and plywood ASPs (+12% YoY, +6% QoQ – in MYR) offset lower export logs volume (-47% YoY, +34% QoQ) and lower plywood sales volume (-12% YoY, -12% QoQ).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>The worse seems over for timber division&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We understand Ta Ann is able to raise its log export quote to 40% (from 20%) in 2H18 for those certified FMU area, covering ~149k ha (or 39% of total licensed area). And with better weather (1H18 output affected by heavy rainfall), we expect stronger timber contribution in 2H18. Coupled with stronger FFB output and lower operating costs at the oil palm division, we are keeping our earnings forecasts for now anticipating better prospects in 2H18. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Tan Chong Motor</column>
<column>1.800000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Strong results should persist into 3Q18, riding on high sales period sparked by lower car prices from GST zero-rating. However, beyond that, we are cautious on (i) lower sales with the return of SST and (ii) weaker margins due to higher USD/MYR forex rate. Nonetheless, we raise FY18 core net profit forecast by 57% having factored in the stronger 1H18. With earnings continuity, we now value TCM using PER multiples, pegging it at 13x CY19 EPS. Our new TP is MYR1.80 (-16%); D/G to HOLD.</column>
<column>Positive earnings surprise in 1H18</column>
<column>Strong results should persist into 3Q18, riding on high sales period sparked by lower car prices from GST zero-rating. However, beyond that, we are cautious on (i) lower sales with the return of SST and (ii) weaker margins due to higher USD/MYR forex rate. Nonetheless, we raise FY18 core net profit forecast by 57% having factored in the stronger 1H18. With earnings continuity, we now value TCM using PER multiples, pegging it at 13x CY19 EPS (10% discount to our average PER peg for the auto stocks within our coverage). Our new TP is MYR1.80 (-16%); D/G to HOLD.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Better sales mix lifted the day</column>
<column>2Q18 core net profit of MYR21m (+186% QoQ) took 1H18 core earnings to MYR28m (vs core loss of MYR54m in 1H17), representing 82% of our initial FY18 forecast. The much better results were largely because of margin expansion, driven by (i) better sales mix, helped by stronger sales of higher ASP models (i.e. X-Trail, Serena S Hybrid) and (ii) lower imported component cost from a soft USD/MYR forex. Headline net profit included a negative one-off of MYR12m, mainly from a MYR9m inventory write-off. Elsewhere, we are comforted that TCM was able to take advantage of the GST zero-rating period to further reduce its inventory to MYR1.0b (-6% QoQ), freeing up working capital for future models. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Raise FY18/19/20E earnings by 57%/14%/14%&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Factoring in a stronger-than-expected auto EBITDA in 1H18, we raise our core FY18E earnings by 57%; we now expect auto EBITDA margin to hit 5.2% in FY18 from our earlier expectation of 4.7%. As for FY19/20, we also raise auto EBITDA margin assumption to 5.3%/5.5% from 5.1%/5.2% respectively, resulting in a 14% increase in core earnings for each year. The quantum of our earnings upgrade in FY19/20 has taken into account a weaker MYR which was seen in the recent month. The benefit of a stronger MYR against USD and JPY from 1H18 should gradually diminish as we enter 4Q18 (USD/MYR averages 4.06 beginning 2H18 vs 3.94 in 1H18). &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Risk-reward balanced&#38;#13;</column>
<column>While we do not foresee any clear near-term re-rating catalyst, we also see limited downside to share price as TCM’s P/NTA valuation remains undemanding at 0.4x. HOLD for now; share price have gained 20% YTD.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Telekom Malaysia</column>
<column>3.695102</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1H18 results were below expectations, with the miss arising from a combination of MSAP-related provision and higher taxes. With share price having recovered from its recent trough, we downgrade to HOLD (from BUY) with a lower TP of MYR3.70 (-5%) post our earnings revisions.</column>
<column>Risk-reward merely balanced now</column>
<column>1H18 results were below expectations, with the miss arising from a combination of MSAP-related provision and higher taxes. With share price having recovered from its recent trough, we downgrade to HOLD (from BUY) with a lower TP of MYR3.70 (-5%) post our earnings revisions.</column>
<column>A miss from provision and taxes</column>
<column>TM’s 2Q18 core net profit of MYR156m (-25% YoY, +48% QoQ) bring 1H18 core net profit to MYR261m (-40% YoY), 39%/40% of our/consensus full-year forecasts respectively. The miss was attributable to 1) MYR88m of MSAP (Mandatory Standard Access Pricing) provision (new lower rates had to be backdated to Jan 2018), and 2) higher-than-expected taxes (43% effective tax rate in 2Q18) possibly from the non-recognition of Webe tax losses. No dividend was declared, a deviation from past practice. </column>
<column>Unsurprisingly lowering guidance  </column>
<column>Segmental revenue (by product) was largely in line except Data, where the MSAP provision manifested in the form of revenue shortfall. We caution against extrapolating the provision amount going forward, as volume from access seekers would likely increase significantly with the new higher-speed plans. Management has unsurprisingly lowered FY18 guidance to -1% to flat revenue growth and c.MYR1b EBIT (3.5%-4.0% revenue growth, stable EBIT previously). Separately, management has now made its basic 30Mbps fibre broadband plan (60GB quota) available to all (B40 households previously). </column>
<column>Downgrade to HOLD </column>
<column>We lower our FY18/19/20 earnings forecasts to by 8%/5%/5% to reflect the new run rate for wholesale revenue and a higher tax rate for FY18. Consequently, our DCF-derived TP (assuming 7.4% WACC and 2% LT growth) is lowered to MYR3.70 (from MYR3.90). Downgrade to HOLD (from BUY) with the share price now near our revised TP. We still expect TM to discontinue with its minimum MYR700m dividend policy.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Tenaga Nasional</column>
<column>15.997288</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1H18 results were in line as 2Q18 non-fuel costs expectedly trended up sequentially. Tenaga again under-recovered on generation costs. Share price has recovered from its recent trough following the imposition of a tariff surcharge for 2H18, thus risk-reward appears merely balanced for now. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged MYR16.00 TP.</column>
<column>Sequential earnings decline as expected</column>
<column>1H18 results were in line as 2Q18 non-fuel costs expectedly trended up sequentially. Tenaga again under-recovered on generation costs. Share price has recovered from its recent trough following the imposition of a tariff surcharge for 2H18, thus risk-reward appears merely balanced for now. Maintain HOLD with an unchanged MYR16.00 TP.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Results in line </column>
<column>Tenaga shifted its financial year-end from Aug to Dec in 2017, thus YoY comparisons are not available. 2Q18 core net profit (ex-forex) of MYR1.41b (-31% QoQ) brings 1H18 core net profit to MYR3.44b, 52%/48% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. As expected, 2Q18 non-fuel costs trended higher sequentially, and included a MYR207m impairment charge for Gama Enerji (its Turkey associate). A 30.3sen interim DPS was declared, reflecting a 50% DPR for 1H18. </column>
<column>Improved generation mix  </column>
<column>We estimate 2Q18 generation grew c.4.4% YoY on the back of a corresponding 3.1% demand growth. Coal’s proportion of 2Q18 generation increased by 4.0ppt to 57.8%. With coal prices still elevated, Tenaga under-recovered by MYR245m in the quarter (sequentially lower, possibly due to the improved mix). Should coal prices continue to remain high throughout 2H18, a tariff surcharge would likely be required again in 1H19. This could again be part-funded by the balance of the Electricity Industry Fund. </column>
<column>Maintain HOLD </column>
<column>Our earnings forecasts and TP are unchanged. Our TP of MYR16.00 is derived from a DCF, assuming 7.5% WACC and 1% long-term growth. We are still slightly wary that the street has not yet fully digested the likely earnings step-down in RP2. This is however offset by the longer-term possibility of an expansion of Tenaga’s valuation multiple, as doubts over the pass-through mechanism dissipates further.  </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>TH Plantations</column>
<column>0.740000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>THP recorded core losses in 2Q18, mainly on low CPO ASP and high cost of production. We expect earnings to play catch up in 2H18 on higher FFB production and lower fertilizing cost. We maintain earnings forecasts for now pending an update with management. Given the lack of short term catalyst, THP remains a HOLD but on a lower TP of MYR0.74 (-17%) based on updated 0.5x trailing P/NTA, pegged at -2SD of 5-year mean (previously 0.6x trailing P/NTA, on unchanged -2SD of 5-year mean).</column>
<column>HOLD at best&#38;#13;</column>
<column>THP recorded core losses in 2Q18, mainly on low CPO ASP and high cost of production. We expect earnings to play catch up in 2H18 on higher FFB production and lower fertilizing cost. We maintain earnings forecasts for now pending an update with management. Given the lack of short term catalyst, THP remains a HOLD but on a lower TP of MYR0.74 (-17%) based on updated 0.5x trailing P/NTA, pegged at -2SD of 5-year mean (previously 0.6x trailing P/NTA, on unchanged -2SD of 5-year mean).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Dragged by low CPO ASP&#38;#13;</column>
<column>2Q18 headline net profit was MYR0.2m (-99% YoY, -94% QoQ). Adjusted for fair valuation gain on biological assets, 2Q18 reported a core loss of MYR7m (2Q17: +MYR10m, 1Q18: +MYR0.6m) dragging 1H18 into a core loss of MYR6m (1H18: +MYR28m). 2Q18 core loss was dragged by lower CPO ASP of MYR2,275/t (-15% YoY, -3% QoQ), mitigated by higher FFB output growth (+5% YoY, +14% QoQ). &#38;#13;</column>
<column>All-in cost of production remains high&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1H18 FFB production (+9% YoY) accounted for 41% of our full-year forecast, within historical 1H:2H ratio. Hence, we are keeping our FY18’s FFB growth forecast of +9% YoY. As for cost, we estimate THP’s 1H18 all-in cost of production at MYR2,347/t in 1H18 (+5% YoY), perhaps on higher fertilisation application made in 1H18. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Earnings estimates unchanged for now&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Pending an update with management, we make no changes to our earnings forecasts as we anticipate stronger earnings in 2H18 on seasonally stronger FFB output. Earnings risk is on the downside given the present weak CPO price; our forecasts impute MYR2,450/t ASPs for FY18. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>TIME dotCom</column>
<column>8.546357</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>1H18 results were slightly ahead with costs running below expectations.  The retail segment remains the main growth driver, but could experience some near-term headwinds in the form of heightened price-led competition. Maintain HOLD with a slightly raised MYR8.55 TP (+1%) post our earnings revisions.</column>
<column>Awaiting retail broadband response</column>
<column>1H18 results were slightly ahead with costs running below expectations.  The retail segment remains the main growth driver, but could experience some near-term headwinds in the form of heightened price-led competition. Maintain HOLD with a slightly raised MYR8.55 TP (+1%) post our earnings revisions. </column>
<column>A slight beat</column>
<column>TDC’s 2Q18 net profit of MYR65m (+81% YoY, +3% QoQ) brings 1H18 net profit to MYR128m (+44% YoY), 56%/55% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. The beat, relative to our forecast, was primarily cost-induced, with margins coming in c.2ppt higher than our assumption. Elsewhere, MFRS 15 resulted in a pre-tax gain of MYR11.3m in 1H18 with customer acquisition costs now being amortised (instead of expensed previously). </column>
<column>Revenue trends intact </column>
<column>Revenue trends were as expected. There were one-off data centre-related sales of MYR3.1m, excluding which 2Q18 wholesale revenue would still have grown both QoQ (+9%) and YoY (+12%). On a sequential basis, enterprise revenue contracted (-2%), while retail saw slower growth (+6%). Retail revenue is still up 76% YoY in 1H18, contributing c.18% to TDC’s revenue. Separately, TDC has yet to announce its response to the lower retail fibre broadband price points recently introduced by competitors. Management noted that excessively low price points could lead to overall lower reinvestment by telcos, thus running counter to the government’s aim of driving penetration. </column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>We raise our FY18 earnings forecast by 8% as we raise our margin assumption to reflect the latest run-rate (our FY19-20 forecasts are unchanged). Our TP is raised slightly to MYR8.55 (MYR8.50 previously). Our TP is derived from a DCF, assuming 8.2% WACC and 2% long-term growth. We have yet to incorporate the impact from potential pricing changes (retail segment) in our forecasts.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Tingyi</column>
<column>12.370000</column>
<column>Sell</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain contrarian SELL w/Street low TP due to near-term challenges. Although there was progress in 1Q, weak full-year guidance was unchanged. Management also warned of a higher base of comparison in 2H and that FY18 will hinge on how consumers respond during the peak summer season to its beverage ASP hike made in 1Q18. Long-term positives are management’s emphasis on strengthening the brand, improving product innovation, managing channel adjustments and improving return metrics.</column>
<column>Positives priced in; Near-term risks remain&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Maintain contrarian SELL due to near-term challenges and risks. Although there was good progress in 1Q, weak full-year guidance was unchanged. Management also warned of a higher base of comparison in 2H and that FY18 will hinge on how consumers respond during the peak summer season to its beverage ASP hike made in 1Q18. Nonetheless, long-term positives are management’s emphasis on strengthening the brand, improving product innovation, managing channel adjustments and improving return metrics. Our Street-low TP of HKD12.37 is still pegged to a target 25x FY18F PER, on par with the peer group average due to its scale and bumpy earnings profile.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Growth to taper, more brand investment required</column>
<column>Solid 1Q18 profit was driven by the ASP hike in noodles (Oct 2017), a positive product mix, and several initiatives to improve beverage margins (ie, content reduction and ASP hikes). However, sales growth of both its noodles and beverages underperformed the industry. We remain concerned about the erosion of its beverage product mix and market-share losses (per AC Nielsen). On SG&#38;#38;A expense, the CEO emphasized the company will invest in brand cultivation and channel infrastructure in 2018. While this will be positive longer term, A&#38;#38;P could increase in 2H18 as a result.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Initiatives for growth sustainability&#38;#13;</column>
<column>At the Shanghai IR day, business pillar heads presented strategies on improving sales, supply chain management, food safety and HR. Key initiatives include: i) boosting sales by enriching product specifications and enhancing customers’ consumption frequency; ii) reducing its procurement, direct labour, logistics and utilities cost; iii) improving channel inventory; iv) flattening distribution layers in core business districts to improve its presence in specialty channels and to also reduce shipping costs; v) actively exploring B2B potential; vi) formulating joint-business plans with its modern trade (MT) partners. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>On-going asset revitalization&#38;#13;</column>
<column>As Tingyi continues to pursue an asset-light model by revitalising its idle assets, management expects further cash inflows. Revitalization includes consolidation of manufacturing resources, idle asset sales/disposals and outsourcing. This reduced the effective tax rate in 1Q18 as profitability at the plant level increased and also will lift its ROA in the future. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>TSH Resources </column>
<column>1.140000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>TSH’s core earnings caught up sharply in 2Q18 after a slow start to the year. 1H18 core earnings were within our expectations, but above consensus. We expect further pick up in 2H18 earnings on lower fertilising cost. Given the lack of short term catalyst, TSH remains a HOLD with an unchanged TP of MYR1.14 on unchanged 19x 2018 PER, pegged at -1SD its 5-year historical mean.</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD&#38;#13;</column>
<column>TSH’s core earnings caught up sharply in 2Q18 after a slow start to the year. 1H18 core earnings were within our expectations, but above consensus. We expect further pick up in 2H18 earnings on lower fertilising cost. Given the lack of short term catalyst, TSH remains a HOLD with an unchanged TP of MYR1.14 on unchanged 19x 2018 PER, pegged at -1SD its 5-year historical mean.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>2Q18 core earnings within estimates&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Besides lower CPO ASP, 2Q18 headline net profit fell 84% YoY to MYR4.1m (-77% QoQ) on FX losses, and higher-than-expected effective tax rate of 55% (due to under provision in respect of prior year deferred income tax). Stripping aside FX losses, TSH’s 2Q18 core net profit of MYR23.6m (-1% YoY, +160% QoQ) brings 1H18 core net profit to MYR33m (-30% YoY), meeting 40%/49% of our (within)/consensus (above) full-year forecasts. 2Q18’s palm EBIT fell 21% YoY to MYR33.8m (+56% QoQ) on lower CPO ASP of MYR2,283/t (-14% YoY, -1% QoQ), despite higher FFB production (+25% YoY, +22% QoQ).&#38;#13;</column>
<column>FFB production ahead of estimates for now&#38;#13;</column>
<column>1H18 FFB production (+24% YoY) accounted for 51% of our full-year forecast, and is above historical trends 1H:2H ratio of 45:55. 1H18’s growth is above our FY18’s +11% YoY growth forecast; we understand production at the Indonesia estates experienced unusually strong production growth in 1H18 (+29% YoY). It remains to be seen if such strong growth can last till end 2018, which may provide upside to our existing forecasts. As for cost, we estimate TSH’s 1H18 all-in cost of production to be at MYR1,726/t (-3% YoY). &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Earnings forecasts unchanged&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Pending an update from management, we are maintaining our earnings estimates for now. We expect stronger earnings in 2H18 on lower cost of production (on lesser fertilizing activities in 2H18) to mitigate present low CPO ASP. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Uni-President China</column>
<column>10.200000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain BUY. UPC’s solid 1H18 results support our thesis its strategy of disciplined sales growth, cost rationalization and tactical market share gains will help improve profitability and sales visibility. Our forecasts are unchanged with TP still based on a target 12x FY18 EV/EBITDA, 1SD above its historical average to reflect the improving earnings growth outlook. Senior management will be in HK on 14 Aug for an analyst briefing</column>
<column>Strong 1H18 reinforces new strategic direction</column>
<column>Maintain BUY. UPC’s solid 1H18 results support our thesis its strategy of disciplined sales growth, cost rationalization and tactical market share gains will help improve profitability and sales visibility. Our forecasts are unchanged with TP still based on a target 12x FY18 EV/EBITDA, 1SD above its historical average to reflect the improving earnings growth outlook. Senior management will be in HK on 14 Aug for an analyst briefing.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Noodles margin at all-time high; sales outlook good&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Noodles sales grew 8% YoY in 1H18 thanks to the double-digit growth in the sales of its high-end “Soup Da Ren” (c. 22% of noodles sales). The better sales mix drove operating margin for noodles to an historical high of 5.4%, and UPC sees further upside in the future via the launch of innovative new products and better cost control. Recall, UPC has divided up its sales team in two with one team focusing on products priced above CNY5, which we believe can speed up its product-mix enhancement. In terms of mainstream noodles, management has confidence in its nationwide launch of “Teng Jiao” pepper noodles given encouraging feedback from certain regions.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Beverage unit improved overall, except juices&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Management reiterated that it’s not as confident about its beverage unit as it is towards it noodles division. But it added that its tea drinks, milk tea and coffee sales have been recovering nicely. The beverage unit was dragged by very weak juice sales in 1H18. Of note, UPC said despite tremendous efforts, achieving sales growth will remain challenging for its lemonade “Classmate Xiaoming” drink in FY18. On a separate note, UPC reduced sales rebates in 1H (applicable to traditional products only) but management reassured us sales volume continued to grow in 1H. This indicates to us its new sales rebates are being well taken up by customers.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Eyes new categories, collaborations and channels&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Several innovative drinks products have launched, such as high-end fruit drink “Fruit Trio” and instant milk tea with pudding “REMIX”. Meanwhile, UPC is collaborating with well-known F&#38;#38;B producers, such as Jiang Xiao Bai and Zhou Hei Ya to explore the youth and catering channels. Last but not least, we note UPC will focus on three new categories: 1) convenience meal (eg, its “Lazy Time” hotpot pack) and snacks; 2) soy milk; and 3) hot drinks. Overall, if successful, we believe this will help diversify revenue in the future and help better differentiate it from peers. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>V.S. Industry</column>
<column>1.950000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>9MFY7/18 earnings fell short at just 63%/57% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. The fall in earnings stemmed from both revenue decline (discontinuation for Keurig’s products) and higher costs (for a new beauty care products in the pipeline). Taking these into account, we cut our FY18/19/20 net profit forecasts by 16%/10%/9%. Correspondingly, our TP is lowered to MYR1.95 (-10%), pegged on an unchanged 16x CY19 PER (10% below our average PER target for our tech coverage). </column>
<column>Below expectations</column>
<column>9MFY7/18 earnings fell short at just 63%/57% of our/consensus full-year forecasts. The fall in earnings stemmed from both revenue decline (discontinuation for Keurig’s products) and higher costs (for a new beauty care products in the pipeline). Taking these into account, we cut our FY18/19/20 net profit forecasts by 16%/10%/9%. Correspondingly, our TP is lowered to MYR1.95 (-10%), pegged on an unchanged 16x CY19 PER (10% below our average PER target for our tech coverage). </column>
<column>Bite the bullet in 2HFY18 to …</column>
<column>3QFY18 core earnings of MYR21m (-54% QoQ, -59% YoY) took 9MFY18 core net profit to MYR115m (-6% YoY). In 3QFY18, the revenue shortfall (-21% QoQ) due to discontinuation of two high ASP Keurig single-serve coffee models was further exacerbated by higher costs (COGS was 3.3ppts higher QoQ) incurred for (i) an upcoming beauty care product (Jul 2018), (ii) a new precision filter production line (100%-owned Skreen Fabric) and (iii) robotics automation; these resulted in a 54% QoQ fall in earnings. The higher costs incurred were mainly for the hiring of foreign workers in preparation for mass productions. With a few new products in the pipeline, we expect VSI’s margins to remain suppressed in 4QFY18.</column>
<column>… reap higher profitability in FY19</column>
<column>3QFY18 results was not all gloom and doom; press release by the company suggests that they were able to renegotiate terms with their key clients to ease recent cost pressures (mainly labour, due to foreign worker levy). We understand that this adjustment would take effect in mid-4QFY18; further clarity on the quantum would likely be revealed in an analyst briefing in early July. Also, investment into robotics automation and Skreen Fabric’s capacity are moves to enhance future profitability. We are comforted that these factors would help VSI recover some margins in FY19, putting it back on track for a growth trajectory.  </column>
<column>Position for FY19’s growth; maintain BUY</column>
<column>VSI’s share price have retraced 24% in the last one month, pricing in most of the negatives on the stock; trading at 11.6x CY19 PER now. We view this as an opportunity for a re-entry given that VSI is still projected to grow earnings by 15% CAGR from FY17A-20E and the worse is likely over. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Vinda International</column>
<column>15.600000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Maintain HOLD. We keep our earnings despite 1H18 sales/EBITDA/NP reaching 48%/55%/52% of our FY18. This is to reflect CNY weakness since June, which eroded the FX tailwinds in 1H18 (sales +16% YoY vs. FX-adjusted +8%). Meanwhile, while its gross margin recovered QoQ for two straight quarters, we believe we could see a pause amid weaker CNY (major COGS in USD) and operating margin retreating HoH in 2H18 due to higher OPEX. Our TP remains pegged to 23x FY18F P/E.</column>
<column>Rising FX risks and halt to margin recovery</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD. We keep our earnings despite 1H18 sales/EBITDA/NP reaching 48%/55%/52% of our FY18. This is to reflect CNY weakness since June, which eroded the FX tailwinds in 1H18 (sales +16% YoY vs. FX-adjusted +8%). Meanwhile, while its gross margin recovered QoQ for two straight quarters, we believe we could see a pause amid weaker CNY (major COGS in USD) and operating margin retreating HoH in 2H18 due to higher OPEX. Our TP remains pegged to 23x FY18F P/E, in-line with its long-term trading avg. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Stronger volume vs. fading ASP hike effect</column>
<column>We believe majority of FX-adj. revenue growth came from two rounds of ASP hikes implemented in Oct 2017 and May 2018. As competitors have followed with their own price hikes, we expect its tissue paper volume to improve in 2H18. Nonetheless, with FX tailwind fading, we believe reporting revenue growth should fall to 11% in 2H18. That said, going into the traditional 4Q peak season, we will see the ASP effect abate due to high base. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Elevated pulp price and surge in SG&#38;#38;A&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Management expects wood pulp prices to stay high in the foreseeable future due to fairly rigid supply/demand outlook. Given 80% of Vinda’s sales come from tissue paper, we believe it has to do more to reduce margin volatility, for example by lifting sales contribution from high-margin products, eg. its Tempo brand is launching the toilet roll category in China which commands considerably higher profitability than Vinda-branded toilet rolls. Tempo brand makes up less than 10% of its tissue sales. Given new launches and capacity, we expect OPEX/sales to rise 30bps YoY in 2H vs 1.7ppt drop in 1H.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>E-commerce strength diminishing; Asia exposure risks&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We expect its e-commerce (EC) sales contribution to stay in the low 20% range in near to medium term against fast growth in past few years. This is because its peers are rapidly catching up. As such, we believe the slowing EC sales momentum will cap its China growth rate. On a separate note, we believe the upcoming reintroduction of SST (sales and service tax) by 1 Sep in Malaysia could add risks to sales (its Asia exposure ex-China is ~20% of sales, but disclosure remains limited). </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Vipshop Holdings </column>
<column>15.200000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>If the market was looking for Tencent’s Midas touch on VIPS, it did not show in 2Q18. However, we remain steadfast in our thesis that VIPS has a good chance of recovering its margins to past levels and eventually will be a beneficiary of additional traffic through the Wechat and JD channels.  While uncertainty and weak results of last two quarters led to a sell down, we believe the upside potential is significant and the risk low at the current price level. Reiterate BUY with lowered estimates.</column>
<column>BUY: TP lowered 16% but the thesis is intact &#38;#13;</column>
<column>If the market was looking for Tencent’s Midas touch on VIPS, it did not show in 2Q18. However, we remain steadfast in our thesis that VIPS has a good chance of recovering its margins to past levels and the company eventually will be a beneficiary of additional traffic through the Wechat and JD channels. While uncertainty and weak results of last two quarters led to a sell down, we believe the upside potential is significant and the risk low at the current price level. We have lowered our non-GAAP earnings estimates by 21%/12%/9% for 2018 to 2020. Even after cutting our DCF based TP by 16%, upside is 99%, in our view.   </column>
<column>2Q18 was a tough quarter – missed expectations &#38;#13;</column>
<column>VIPS met its own revenue guidance for 2Q18 only near the bottom of the range. Operating margin further compressed, but the company did flag the potential in 1Q18. Considering that the share price has plummeted 37% in 3 months, the continuing weakness is not a surprise, but the magnitude was. Management’s below consensus 13-18% YoY sales growth guidance for 3Q18 did not help, but we note that 4Q is a seasonally strong season for apparel.      &#38;#13;</column>
<column>Margins can expand with time&#38;#13;</column>
<column>We know the weak gross margin was the culprit for the operating margin sliding further in 2Q18. This was due to: 1) competitive pressure leading to heavier promotions; and 2) 3rd party logistics of 1.1% of sales. In addition, fulfilment and marketing costs as a % of sales rose sequentially. Figure 2 shows that if the company is able to rein in these costs to prior levels (we believe it can), operating margin can potentially return to 5%.</column>
<column>Traffic is rising but ARPU for new users lower&#38;#13;</column>
<column>JD and Tencent channels accounted for 24% of new customers.  Followers of VIPS on JD platform increased to 1.5 mil from just 500K in 1Q18. The number of active users grew 6% YoY from flat in 1Q18, rev/buyer up 12%, and orders up 31%. However, revenue per order was down 10% YoY. Early signs of turnaround are showing; monetization is not.    </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>ViTrox Corp</column>
<column>6.800000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>ViTrox once again broke its revenuerecord (MYR96m in 4Q17) as sales trounce all expectations, hitting MYR105m (+36% QoQ, 35% YoY) in 2Q18. We expect 2H18 to be much stronger HoH as floor space constraint eases following ViTrox’s move into Campus 2.0. We raise our FY18-20 earnings forecasts by 4%-5% to incorporate the stronger-than-expected 1H18. Pegged on an unchanged 22x CY19 PER (30% premium against peers; +1SD), we raise our TP MYR6.80 (+5%); reiterate BUY.</column>
<column>Just the tip of the iceberg</column>
<column>ViTrox once again broke its revenue record (MYR96m in 4Q17) as sales trounce all expectations, hitting MYR105m (+36% QoQ, 35% YoY) in 2Q18. The solid results were driven by volume growth across all divisions, due to positive acceptance from a wider customer base. We expect 2H18 to be much stronger HoH as floor space constraint eases following ViTrox’s move into Campus 2.0 (3x bigger than Campus 1.0). We raise our FY18-20 earnings forecasts by 4%-5% to incorporate the stronger-than-expected 1H18. Pegged on an unchanged 22x CY19 PER (30% premium against peer valuations; +1SD), we raise our TP MYR6.80 (+5%); reiterate BUY.  </column>
<column>Stellar results in 2Q18; even stronger results ahead</column>
<column>1H18 revenue accounted for 48% of our initial full-year projection – above expectations as we only expected 1H18 sales to make up 39-41% of 2018 forecast, in consideration of a much stronger 2H18 once ViTrox moves into Campus 2.0. At the bottomline, ViTrox’s 2Q18 core earnings also hit a record high of MYR28m (+40% QoQ, +51% YoY), bringing 1H18 core net profit to MYR49m (+28% YoY) or 50% of our initial 2018 projection. The stronger-than-expected results in 1H18 were mainly from much higher ASPs recorded in the MVS-S and AOI product segments whereby ASPs grew by 22% and 14% respectively against 2017’s ASPs, likely due to new product launches or add-ons; we initially projected flat ASP for MVS-S and 3% ASP decline for AOI.</column>
<column>Raise FY18/19/20 forecasts by 5%/4%/4%</column>
<column>Pending further clarity in today’s analyst briefing, we leave our volume projections untouched for now. Nonetheless, we raise FY18-20 net profit forecasts by 4%-5% expecting ASP hikes in the aforementioned product segments to sustain. Our revised earnings forecasts still assume a 55%/ 40% utilisation (unchanged) of capacity in 2018/2019 (refer to Fig 5). </column>
<column>Unlocking its new potential</column>
<column>ViTrox was able to breach the MYR100m-level in its quarterly revenue sooner than we thought, likely due to strong telco infrastructure demand for its ABI products, ahead of 5G network adoption. Persistent hit above this level would be symbolic and could potentially unlock another level of operational scale, translating to higher profitability. </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Want Want China</column>
<column>8.740000</column>
<column>Buy</column>
<column>Yes</column>
<column>Maintain BUY with a new TP, now pegged at 24x FY19E P/E, intact at 1SD above its 7-year average. This is a change from our blended FY17-18E P/E when it had a December year-end. We also introduce new forecasts following the change in its financial year-end to March. Expect catalysts from a sustained sales and profit recovery on the back of WWC’s Hot-Kid milk sales. Healthier channel inventory and strengthening market presence should support its sales momentum. </column>
<column>Better sales; margins to recover next&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Maintain BUY with a new TP, now pegged at 24x FY19E P/E, intact at 1SD above its 7-year average. This is a change from our blended FY17-18E P/E when it had a December year-end. We also introduce new forecasts following the change in its financial year-end to March. Expect catalysts from a sustained sales and profit recovery on the back of WWC’s Hot-Kid milk sales. Healthier channel inventory and strengthening market presence should support its sales momentum. ASP increases of 5-10% were implemented in April/May for its Hot-Kid milk, which together with abating raw materials cost pressure, bode well for margin recovery. Relaxing birth control in China is expected to enlarge its addressable market in future.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Hot-Kid on a roll&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Hot-Kid milk sales grew 10% YoY in 2HFY3/18, sustaining their 10% growth in 1HFY3/18 vs a negative CAGR during 2014-3M17. Growth came from all channels: single digits for traditional; high teens for modern trade and more than doubling for e-commerce. New packaging and designs through IP collaboration and digital marketing helped. Retail channel inventory declined five days YoY to 26, improving the freshness of its products.&#38;#13;</column>
<column>Emerging opportunities &#38;#13;</column>
<column>We see better growth prospects for WWC’s food sales than the past few years. Trusted for its product safety, WWC is expanding its presence in the sub-market for infants and toddlers in maternity stores as it has small exposure previously. In addition, its rice-cracker export sales have been growing by double digits YoY. This could become its new sales driver. Also, we believe its new corner-seal bags, non-fried rice potato chips and room-temperature ice creams etc can help sustain its food-sales momentum. &#38;#13;</column>
<column>CSR initiative to incubate products &#38;#13;</column>
<column>We are also impressed by its new “Wonderland project”. This is a CSR initiative to cultivate young entrepreneurs. WWC has invited students from colleges in China and Taiwan to submit their business plans. It will provide production support to those selected. It intends to invest over CNY100m in business incubation. Although this has no P&#38;#38;L contributions, we believe incubation could bring about innovation for WWC and energise its future product offerings.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>Yashili International Holdings</column>
<column>1.600000</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>Maintain HOLD with revised estimates. While we believe Yashili is on track for a recovery in FY18, we remain subdued due to its questionable long term growth outlook. YSL has an unproven track record, despite having dairy giants as its strategic shareholders. Overall, we would wait for indications YSL has established a competitive edge before turning positive. We maintain our TP of HKD1.60 but revise down the multiple to 1.7x FY18F (LT avg.) from 2.4x (peer avg.) to reflect low quality growth.</column>
<column>Turning around, but too early to be excited; Prefer H&#38;#38;H</column>
<column>Maintain HOLD with revised estimates. While we believe Yashili is on track for a recovery in FY18, we remain subdued due to its questionable long term growth outlook. YSL has an unproven track record, despite having dairy giants as its strategic shareholders. Overall, we would wait for indications YSL has established a competitive edge before turning positive. We prefer H&#38;#38;H (1112HK, BUY, HKD52.65, TP HKD69.4) given its well-established presence. We maintain our TP of HKD1.60 but revise to the long-term avg. 1.7x FY18F EV/EBITDA from the peer group average 2.4x as the earnings growth will be mainly driven by low quality factors (i.e., bulk milk powder business). We revise up our estimates, including FY18/19/20E net profit by 8%/39%/19%.</column>
<column>Operating leverage to drive margin recovery </column>
<column>We expect strong revenue growth to continue in FY19-20E (ie 20-25% pa), albeit moderating from 41% YoY in FY18E. We believe YSL will be one of the beneficiaries of the tightening in regulations for infant milk formula (IMF). In addition, as it has strategically put more focus on the fast-growing organic milk and goat milk segments, we believe it can outgrow the PRC IMF market. Meanwhile, YSL has also expanded its base milk powder sales to Danone. We anticipate stable GPMs ahead as the mix upgrade within IMF will be offset by sales of low-margin base powder milk. But with higher utilisation, we expect positive operating leverage to drive profitability. </column>
<column>But we need to see more sustainable sales drivers…</column>
<column>YSL has five good brands that target different market segments and they cover the full spectrum of price ranges. However, its sales channel weakness remains a key concern; we note its IMF business in 1H18 was entirely driven by new POSs that were added, whereas same-store sales likely continued to decline. Given its late entry into the baby store channel, we think it still has room to expand sales through network expansion over the next few years, but its long-term growth outlook remains questionable.</column>
<column>Stronger cash flow, but no special dividend likely</column>
<column>Net operating cash flow turned positive in 1H18 due to improving AR &#38;#38; inventories. Its net cash position improved further. However, we note YSL plans to increase capex going forward (e.g., for upgrading production facilities). In addition, it’s also exploring M&#38;#38;A opportunities. As a result, we expect no upside to the dividend payout or a special dividend.  </column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column>YTL Power</column>
<column>1.050379</column>
<column>Hold</column>
<column></column>
<column>FY18 results were above our expectation but below consensus, with Wessex outperforming and PowerSeraya again struggling. More importantly, there was no negative surprise on dividend. Maintain HOLD with a higher MYR1.05 TP (+24%) with Tj Jati A now included in our SOP. In our view, risk-reward remains merely balanced presently. YTLP’s share price recovery in recent months has, to some extent, been aided by its share buybacks.  </column>
<column>Dividend came through </column>
<column>FY18 results were above our expectation but below consensus, with Wessex outperforming and PowerSeraya again struggling. More importantly, there was no negative surprise on dividend. Maintain HOLD with a higher MYR1.05 TP (+24%) with Tj Jati A now included in our SOP. In our view, risk-reward remains merely balanced presently. YTLP’s share price recovery in recent months has, to some extent, been aided by its share buybacks.  </column>
<column>Above our expectation, but below consensus</column>
<column>YTLP’s 4QFY18 core net profit of MYR207m (+2% YoY, +47% QoQ) brings FY18 core net profit to MYR622m (-8% YoY), 15% above our forecast, but 9% below consensus respectively. The beat relative to our forecast, was due to higher-than-expected contribution by Wessex and the associates, along with lower-than-expected holding-co losses. A 5sen DPS was declared (unchanged YoY), in line with our expectation. </column>
<column>Mixed segmentals</column>
<column>For the quarter, PowerSeraya’s pre-tax profit contracted by 84% QoQ, which management attributed to lower tank leasing margins. Wessex’s pre-tax profit meanwhile rose 30% QoQ from opex efficiency gains. Earnings for both the Malaysia IPP and the mobile division were largely routine. Separately, YTLP disclosed that progress has been made towards achieving financial close for Tj Jati A (recall PPA terms was finalised in Mar 2018). </column>
<column>Maintain HOLD</column>
<column>We raise our FY19/20 earnings forecasts by 10%/9% respectively to reflect latest run-rates, and introduce FY21 forecasts. We raise our TP to MYR1.05 (85sen previously) as we 1) roll over our DCF base year, and 2) incorporate Tj Jati A (value is similarly weighted by percentage completion just like that of Attarat Power) into our SOP.  Maintain HOLD, we view risk-reward as being merely balanced presently.</column>
<column></column></row>
<row>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column>
<column></column></row></table></xmloutfile>